<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manage on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/manage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Manage on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/manage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A civilized city can&#39;t tolerate stray dogs, it&#39;s better to control the uncivilized dog owners than to keep arresting them. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you hear me wailing? But I still have to cry out for my pain, bloodshed struggle, when bat after bat hit me on my body my head, do you know my blood tears themselves blurred my eyes, struggle, fear, blood dripping miserable barking tumbling try to stand up and fall down convulsions and gasp for breath mournful grief pale face, they howl, the whole world should listen to.
Recently, a city is now fighting and catching dogs again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Programming Cat [UNK] Chen Wanqing: The Real Barrier of an Enterprise Is Its Organizational Capability </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</guid>
      <description>Originally created by Azaka. Mustard pile view of education.
Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, speaks at the GET2020 conference on March 23rd.
♪ By Mustard Pile Ataku
♪ Editorial｜Mustard Pile View Education
On November 23rd, at the GET2020 Education Technology Conference hosted by Mustard Pile, with the theme of &amp;ldquo;Or Leap in the Abyss: Confidence and Development in Education&amp;rdquo;, Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, gave a keynote speech on &amp;ldquo;Organizational Thinking in Education Enterprises&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>