<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stray on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/stray/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stray on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/stray/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Say &#34;No&#34; to Uncivilized Behavior】Don&#39;t Let Stray Dogs Become a Problem </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the reporter saw many stray dogs scurrying around the community in Qing Qi, which not only affects the cityscape, but also brings potential problems to the residents. I hope that dog owners do not abandon their pets, but also hope that the relevant departments to manage stray dogs.
Please consciously comply with →
The &amp;ldquo;Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region Regulations for the Promotion of Civilized Behavior&amp;rdquo; Article 24 of the city in the built-up areas of keeping dogs, to comply with the following code of conduct: (d) do not abuse, abandoned dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [90-second method] Feeding dog food? That&#39;s a legal liability, too. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</guid>
      <description>Stray dogs and cats can always be found in the streets, and most of them have experienced hardships and a rough fate. Fortunately, there are many kind-hearted people who will provide these homeless little ones with a full meal or even temporary shelter. **Wild shovelers, be aware that improper feeding can lead to legal risks! ***
Related Cases
On September 20, 2019, Zanzan, a man in his 60s in Zunyi, was knocked down by a dog on his way home and was diagnosed with multiple right-sided rib fractures, and was rated as having a Grade 10 disability after treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>