<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Years on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/years/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Years on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/years/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A guide dog with cancer fought to the death to return to its owner after dying (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</guid>
      <description>Guide dog Kermit is pictured with his blind owner, David.
A dog is man&amp;rsquo;s friend. A recent story from the United Kingdom proves this old adage once again. An eight-year-old guide dog named Kermit, who was suffering from cancer, did his best at the end of his life, trying with every fiber of his being to get his blind owner, David, from Birmingham to his home in Huddersfield before collapsing and taking his last breath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A year ago, a 54-year-old man died of rabies in Zhejiang province after being bitten by a wild dog without vaccination. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ede33dee64408423dcf102c0b85969df/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ede33dee64408423dcf102c0b85969df/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the Emergency Department of the First Affiliated Hospital of Zhejiang University School of Medicine treated a 54-year-old Tiantai man who died of rabies one year after he was bitten by a wild dog and spent a week in the EICU (Emergency Intensive Care Unit). The lesson of blood and tears is heartbreaking.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been almost a year since I was bitten by a wild dog, how can a person just lose it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alibaba&#39;s employee doubling appraisal categorized as a &#34;wild dog hound.&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/145228cb230ad3d3ab74c940d1e5b3f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/145228cb230ad3d3ab74c940d1e5b3f2/</guid>
      <description>Reporter Wei Heping
The rapid expansion of employees often leads to a dilution of corporate culture, a problem that Alibaba Group, amid rumors of an IPO, has had to face.
&amp;ldquo;Alibaba employees have grown from 4,000 last year to 6,000 today, and according to the company&amp;rsquo;s human resources plan, it will reach 8,000 by the end of the year.&amp;rdquo; Deng Kangming, senior vice president of Alibaba Group, revealed in an interview with reporters a few days ago that after the rapid growth of the number of employees in the past few years, the number of employees in the group will double this year compared to last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat addiction, cat ownership &#34;causes poverty&#34;? The &#34;cat economy&#34; is being boosted by young people. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</guid>
      <description>Cats are cute and can be carried around. Nowadays, cats as pets are more and more sought after by young people, cat breeding, go to the cat coffee jerk cat, &amp;ldquo;cloud sucking cat&amp;rdquo; has become the daily life of many young people.
For cats, the wallet is &amp;ldquo;thin &amp;ldquo;.
&amp;ldquo;I may not eat, but the cat must eat well.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hard earned living for cat owners.&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Cat Slave&amp;rdquo; They use all kinds of witty passages to ridicule the daily life of cat ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s so warm, I&#39;ll eat this dog food! Zhaotong netizens quickly give their blessings to this Hunan couple! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7fda1c501fb31043fc936385d41e6f45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7fda1c501fb31043fc936385d41e6f45/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s so warm, I&amp;rsquo;m eating this dog food! Zhaotong netizens quickly give their blessings to this Hunan couple! 2020-11-23 20:00 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Media
These two days
Hou Changliang who has been teaching for 10 years and Lei Yudan who has been teaching for 4 years.
Haizi Xiangyangping Primary School in Yiliang, Zhaotong
Video inviting students to witness their wedding photos goes viral online
Hou Changliang, 34, is from Shaoyang, Hunan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>