<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>New on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/new/</link>
    <description>Recent content in New on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/new/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A Hong Kong Poodle tested positive for a new crown and currently has no associated medical conditions. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e47a662cd33c21d5ac0716dc7c649ad3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e47a662cd33c21d5ac0716dc7c649ad3/</guid>
      <description>According to the Hong Kong East Daily News, the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department (AFCD) of the Hong Kong SAR Government said on Friday that it received a poodle whose sample tested positive for the new coronavirus.
The department said the poodle is from Tsuen Wan, and its owner is a close contact of the confirmed new cases of crown, so the poodle was sent to the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department last Friday (20) to undergo quarantine, and the sample taken showed positive results for the new crown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BMI New Poem: &#34;One Hundred Sheep Flying Over My Head </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/89d3ff21c1b9cc1ff61a2dabff05eff8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/89d3ff21c1b9cc1ff61a2dabff05eff8/</guid>
      <description>BMI New Poem: &amp;ldquo;One Hundred Sheep Flying Over My Head
2020-11-27 17:07:45 Source: Nextpoint.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New scenes and such are weak? Let [UNK] Wild Dog tell you a little secret! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d2fb8bcd1b17cb89cc2607352408ece3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d2fb8bcd1b17cb89cc2607352408ece3/</guid>
      <description>Wang Yi, Founder of the 10 Billion Dollar Institute, Executive Director of Xi Guan Capital
Preface: This article began in late 2018, when China&amp;rsquo;s economy was in a state of crisis due to trade between the U.S. and China, capital chill in the primary market, and shrinking budgets for brand owners. When people forwarded the &amp;ldquo;2019 Advertising Agency Transformation Plan,&amp;rdquo; they asked, &amp;ldquo;In 2019, when people are tightening their belts, what is the way forward for advertising agencies?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>