<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cats on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/cats/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cats on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/cats/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> &#34;Yang&#39;s cat has been found, and they say it&#39;s used in this way, so come in and learn!&#34; Hahaha  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9be737e8c125821694a7f9cac80afa7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9be737e8c125821694a7f9cac80afa7b/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I found a hot search on Weibo: #Yang Gao&amp;rsquo;s cat is lost#.
It is known that the golden gradient layer, called Tangerine, is a little baby raised by Yang Gao.
But on November 11, the little tangerine, which was placed in a relative&amp;rsquo;s home, suddenly ran away from home.
When she learned the news, her sister sent out a message at midnight asking for help: &amp;ldquo;Just be safe and don&amp;rsquo;t wander the streets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A &#34;cat&#34; came to the house, with a fierce temper, and alarmed the police! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ab96a690d1a8b2ace91977c641067c37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ab96a690d1a8b2ace91977c641067c37/</guid>
      <description>Source: City Scene Chongqing News Channel
May not be reproduced without permission.
On November 24, a cat came to a resident&amp;rsquo;s home in Bai Shi Yi, Chongqing Hi-Tech Zone, and at first the resident wanted to tease the cat, but later, he had to call the police for help, what kind of cat still needs police action?
The cat, whose face resembled that of a leopard, also had spots and stripes that differed from those of a typical domestic cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A 4-year-old baby is as big as a pregnant woman and has 2 pounds of parasite fluid pumped out of her body! If you don&#39;t know this, don&#39;t keep pets with your kids! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</guid>
      <description>The director found that since when, jerking cats and rabbits has successfully led the new trend of child-skating.
A lot of parents like to take their babies to a variety of Netflix &amp;ldquo;cat jerking museum&amp;rdquo; to enjoy family time.
It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to play with cats and dogs.
The most important thing is to make sure that you have the right tools to do so.
01*
** 9 year old girl with multiple unexplained lumps on her body** **Causes related to cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A cat triggers an entrepreneurial boom </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c4d3c4439cfe0aeee30b7e54c8a22e08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c4d3c4439cfe0aeee30b7e54c8a22e08/</guid>
      <description>**The reason for this is because of the fact that you can&amp;rsquo;t get a good deal of the money you&amp;rsquo;re going to need for your own business.
When she woke up early in the morning, Maomao used to pick up her cell phone and shoot short videos of the eight cats in the house, and sent them to the &amp;ldquo;family cat foster&amp;rdquo; group she had formed one by one to report to the parents that the &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; was safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A stray cat climbs 25 floors every day and knocks on doors asking for food, how does he do it? How to remember the floors </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/35da6127cb17fedb905e6174f298bd88/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/35da6127cb17fedb905e6174f298bd88/</guid>
      <description>For example, a domestic cat will become a stray cat after being abandoned, and a stray cat will gradually become a domestic cat after being adopted, so in everyone&amp;rsquo;s subconscious mind, stray cats and domestic cats are the same kind of animal.
But as I understand more and more about stray cats, I find that stray cats and domestic cats are simply 2 different kinds of animals.
Because stray cats are so smart, they sometimes do things that would surprise a human being like me, but recently, I was shocked by a stray cat, and it happened to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat addiction, cat ownership &#34;causes poverty&#34;? The &#34;cat economy&#34; is being boosted by young people. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</guid>
      <description>Cats are cute and can be carried around. Nowadays, cats as pets are more and more sought after by young people, cat breeding, go to the cat coffee jerk cat, &amp;ldquo;cloud sucking cat&amp;rdquo; has become the daily life of many young people.
For cats, the wallet is &amp;ldquo;thin &amp;ldquo;.
&amp;ldquo;I may not eat, but the cat must eat well.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hard earned living for cat owners.&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Cat Slave&amp;rdquo; They use all kinds of witty passages to ridicule the daily life of cat ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat enjoys your groping, just like you? Wrong, wrong, wrong! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f43d5ed6862abcb918cc1c5be540b7fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f43d5ed6862abcb918cc1c5be540b7fe/</guid>
      <description>Only by getting to know it can you make it like you more.
Careful shovelers may find that, for a cat that is not yet familiar or bad-tempered, or when the owner is not in a good mood, touching its belly, paws, tail and other sensitive parts of the cat is likely to result in a beating.
Cat: Don&amp;rsquo;t touch me!
But touching the top of the head and chin usually does not attract &amp;ldquo;blood&amp;rdquo;, as if the top of the head and chin is the &amp;ldquo;immunity zone&amp;rdquo; of the shovel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat mummies, with live kittens? [UNK] Why a cat sacrifice? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b5ecb786a8f99a61bd37b51525f5c00b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b5ecb786a8f99a61bd37b51525f5c00b/</guid>
      <description>This blogger looks like a cat lover. However, cat mummies do have kittens, and many of them are kittens. Many of the cat mummies unearthed in Saqqara today are CT scanned to reveal the remains of a whole cat inside. (Ugh, that&amp;rsquo;s a sad answer) Not all cat mummies contain a cat. Sometimes there are only a few bones, and sometimes there is no cat at all, but cloth, resin, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cats are fierce too! A 4-ton wild elephant in Thailand broke into a residential area to steal food and was scared off by the roar of a pet cat. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/de8e6a684866d91f0abb180c10909e5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/de8e6a684866d91f0abb180c10909e5a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 21:35:04 Source: Six Dimensions Nature
Report
In the food chain, herbivores have an instinctive fear of carnivores. In general, herbivores will choose to hide when they encounter carnivores. The wild elephant is dozens of times the size of a pet cat, so is the pet cat too fierce, or is the wild elephant too alert?
Description: The elephant is a wild male elephant. The elephant is also quite famous in the area, because at night, this elephant will go around breaking into people&amp;rsquo;s homes, looking for food, the local residents can not do anything, because wild elephants are protected animals, can only notify the relevant authorities, to drive it into the jungle again, but can not harm the elephant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cats with a short life span often have these six characteristics. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</guid>
      <description>A cat&amp;rsquo;s lifespan depends on many factors, but they all manifest themselves physically. Generally, cats with short life span tend to have these 6 characteristics, hopefully your cat will have none of them.
 Overweight  In both humans and cats, obesity can lead to many diseases. For example, diabetes, heart disease and other problems.
How can you tell if your cat is overweight? You can touch your cat near the chest with your hand, and if you can&amp;rsquo;t feel the ribs, then it can be said to be obese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs and cats playing around accidentally catch fire! The next scene is a stunner! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</guid>
      <description>Dogs and cats playing around and getting burned! The next scene is a stunner! 2020-11-26 17:00 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
Recently, a surveillance video caused a lot of discussion among netizens.
In the video, dogs and cats are playing in the living room.
The cat&amp;rsquo;s tail accidentally caught on an open flame on the table.
The dog runs away immediately at the sight of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you even hold the cat in the wrong position, it&#39;s no wonder the cat likes you! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e54dcc50554b6b7aabe217a333404c21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e54dcc50554b6b7aabe217a333404c21/</guid>
      <description>Some owners complain that their cats are not allowed to be kissed or hugged, as if they have a white wolf. Have you ever thought that if you even hold your cat in the wrong position, the cat will feel uncomfortable and like you? Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a look at the common ways to hold a cat wrong!
Common Errors in Cat Holding
 Carry-On  Some cats are heavier than others, and it is still a bit hard to hold them with one hand, so some owners will choose to carry them on their shoulders, which is very effortless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Little Milk Cat Becomes a Fat Uncle after Adulthood, Netizens Take a Look at the Color: Orange Cat&#39;s Gene Isn&#39;t Bragging </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3a540b72fdfd3a4950104dca808691ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3a540b72fdfd3a4950104dca808691ed/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 06:16:22 Source: Flowers, plants and pets
Report
Cats are the most common animals in our lives, even if we don&amp;rsquo;t have cats at home, we are still likely to meet stray cats on the road.
Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t own a cat, you are still likely to meet stray cats on the road. What do the stray cats you see look like? Even though they are fed by their mothers, many stray cats are still relatively thin and weak, and their pitiful appearance makes people want to take them home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Maine cat is facing Yi Yun Qianxi, is your cat the same model as the star? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</guid>
      <description>They are agile, a little sleepy, like to lick their own hair clean, and have a maverick personality. They are not always obedient to their masters, and are more like two equal friends than subordinates. Is the cat the same as the star?
1 Dusk. British Shorthair
British Shorthair cats are round and chubby, with short, coarse and well-developed limbs, a short, dense coat, a big head and a round face that looks cute, gentle and calm, very friendly and easy to feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Mutant &#34;Weird&#34; Sphinx Cat, So Gentle! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ea605cf97e57ef538a2f6310cc2b566a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ea605cf97e57ef538a2f6310cc2b566a/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s like something out of the movie &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo;. It, with its unique and bizarre shape, has a scowl written all over it. It, with wrinkles as if it were a genetic mutation monster. It, the Sphinx cat.
The Sphinx, also known as the Canadian Hairless Cat, is loved beyond words by some people, while those who are used to furry cats may find the Sphinx&amp;rsquo;s appearance too frightening. The Sphinx is gentle, intelligent and agile, and is loved by people with cat hair allergies, but the Sphinx is not completely hairless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The night life of cats is much more exciting than yours.  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago, Weibo was ablaze with a spoof video from YouTube.
In the cat&amp;rsquo;s first view, a mysterious day goes by unbeknownst to the shovelers.
As soon as the good cat in the video leaves the house-
Money is easy to rob.
The Hammer Man Hammering Away
But what the stupid humans don&amp;rsquo;t know is that the content of this video is actually not all that bad - it&amp;rsquo;s a spoof!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a70df66667aae83914a0e0e96fe68fdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a70df66667aae83914a0e0e96fe68fdb/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow?
Time：2015-03-24 21:10 Source：hongwang.com Editor：Mao Qingqing
Chuanbei Online Core Tip: What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow? &amp;mdash;
Meowers, an Internet buzzword, dubs cats as aliens who come to Earth from the distant planet Meow from outer space and use their cute appearance to trick humans into trusting them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who should get the pets in a divorce? The judge ruled this way for the emotional well-being of the dogs and cats! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d1ac4c72fa376c96f5564729d989657a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d1ac4c72fa376c96f5564729d989657a/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why don&#39;t many people want to own a Garfield? The reason is too real, no money can really afford it! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3edd5e20964eae089e7a71c0e214a71a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3edd5e20964eae089e7a71c0e214a71a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 17:00:48 Source: War Cheat Sheet
Report
I&amp;rsquo;m sure most people really like Garfield! Garfield not only looks cute, but also has a very cute personality. The Garfield I&amp;rsquo;ve seen is super clingy and never messes up, and when there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to do, he just lies quietly by the side and sleeps and stares, so he&amp;rsquo;s really a good pet. However, my friends who have had cats for many years have told me that many people are actually reluctant to raise Garfield, although they are indeed very pleasant to look at, but they can&amp;rsquo;t afford to do so because they are too realistic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You know what? The &#34;clinginess&#34; of male and female cats is not the same! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fc6588b59a52efe7dd81476f9db2a70f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fc6588b59a52efe7dd81476f9db2a70f/</guid>
      <description>Why are other cats so clingy, but your cat is a bit cold and impersonal?
No matter how nice you are to your cat, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to want to come near you.
In fact, the degree of a cat&amp;rsquo;s clinginess is related to many factors.
For example, the gender of the cat, the temperature of the weather, and whether the cat has needs.
-01
Male cats are more clingy than female cats.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>