<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wildlife on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/wildlife/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wildlife on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/wildlife/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A state builds an &#34;animal overpass&#34; to protect wildlife on the highway (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cf4421d707b2eed410e849d30c551de9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cf4421d707b2eed410e849d30c551de9/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 13:15:06 Source: Overseas.com
Report
Utah State Government&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Animal Crossover&amp;rdquo; (Social Media)
Overseas.com, November 28, 2011. According to CNN (CNN) local time on the 27th, the Utah state government has built a wildlife &amp;ldquo;overpass&amp;rdquo; in order to protect local wildlife and reduce the risk of wildlife encountering traffic accidents on the highway. The bridge has reportedly seen initial results in a short period of time.
Wildlife crossing an overpass (video clip)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Adorable! Zoo wildlife health check for winter </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e326bb20f5996bfbc4272420a917905e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e326bb20f5996bfbc4272420a917905e/</guid>
      <description>On November 26, Shandong Qingdao Forest Wildlife World conducted a physical examination of kangaroos, ring-tailed lemurs, lion cubs, golden pythons and other primate, carnivorous, herbivorous, omnivorous and two-reptile wildlife. A veterinarian is giving a physical examination to a kangaroo.
According to the introduction, as the temperature gets cooler after winter, small animals are more prone to gastrointestinal diseases, colds and other symptoms. Qingdao Forest Wildlife World carries out physical examinations and preventive measures for wild animals through physical observation, temperature measurement by auscultation, blood sampling, ultrasound testing, vaccination, feeding deworming drugs and other methods to ensure the health and safety of wild animals in winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> City Forestry Bureau Jointly Launches Wildlife Protection Publicity Campaign (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/21e9f3c66f695bcb797853305e76d1af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/21e9f3c66f695bcb797853305e76d1af/</guid>
      <description>Dajiang.com/Fuzhou Headlines Client News Correspondent Xiaofen Huang and Min Li Report: In order to further enhance the awareness of wildlife protection, on November 26th, the Fuzhou Forestry Bureau joined the Linchuan District Forestry Bureau, the City Public Security Bureau Forest Public Security Branch and the City Wildlife Protection Association to launch a wildlife protection campaign with the theme of &amp;ldquo;Protecting wildlife according to the law and building a green ecological home&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Global Neocrown Outbreak Affects Wildlife Conservation </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c05644cffe85e45e22fe4c2501a7eba6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c05644cffe85e45e22fe4c2501a7eba6/</guid>
      <description>Dan Zhao
According to the Washington Post, wildlife refuges and ecotourism around the world are facing new threats as a result of the new crown epidemic, and the impact on wildlife and people is being felt and is expected to be far-reaching.
As a result of epidemic prevention and control measures such as border closures and visa restrictions in many countries, most of the world&amp;rsquo;s tourist destinations have been forced to shut down, including national parks, game reserves and wildlife sanctuaries in Africa, Asia and elsewhere, resulting in a significant decline in wildlife tourism revenues and a cutback in funding for programs that support wildlife conservation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Guangdong Cracks Down on Illegal Wildlife Markets and Trade, Has Dealt with 3,045 People </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7a723606a239f75c8d2631e6948c87d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7a723606a239f75c8d2631e6948c87d8/</guid>
      <description>Guangdong Crackdown on Illegal Wildlife Markets and Trade, Dealt with 3,045 People
JinYang.com by Hou MengFei 2020-11-26
As of November 6, more than 300,000 business establishments such as markets, restaurants and hotels have been cleaned up and fixed, and 2,085 cases involving wild animals have been established and 3,045 people have been dealt with.
Yangcheng Evening News Media reporter Hou Mengfei
On November 26, the reporter learned from the 26th meeting of the Standing Committee of the Provincial People&amp;rsquo;s Congress that: at present, Guangdong has continuously issued a number of policies and documents to ban all wildlife, and crack down on illegal wildlife markets and trade practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gulou&#39;s First Case of Criminal Attached Civil Lawsuit for Wildlife Protection Opens in Court </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d016cf3a513b356fc22aecbfdb832ad5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d016cf3a513b356fc22aecbfdb832ad5/</guid>
      <description>Fuzhou News Network, November 27th (Fuzhou Daily Reporter) (Lai, Zhichang) Recently, Gulou District, the first case of criminal wildlife protection incidental civil public interest litigation case in court. The Gulou District Procuratorate to illegal acquisition, sale of precious and endangered wildlife crime on the case of the defendant Lin Mou public prosecution.
It is understood that, in May this year, Lin Mou through the network channels to buy a &amp;ldquo;sapphire&amp;rdquo; spider, and in a website to publish information for sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New Tianshui-Wildlife Rescue in Action </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/693ff091ec8917b41c5777adbc999c25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/693ff091ec8917b41c5777adbc999c25/</guid>
      <description>Save the Wildlife We&amp;rsquo;re on the Move
New Tianshui-Tianshui Daily reporter Yan Rongfang
Introduction:
The mountains and rivers are lush, the air is clean and fresh, and the rivers and lakes are shallow. In recent years, as the city&amp;rsquo;s ecological civilization further promote the construction of ecological environment continues to improve, a large number of wild animals have come to Tianshui &amp;ldquo;settled&amp;rdquo;, some trapped, single or injured &amp;ldquo;in distress&amp;rdquo;. The wild animals also wandered into residential areas, industrial zones, schools and other places, and were found to be rescued by citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>