<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pet on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/pet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pet on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/pet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A dog that is the sole pet of the wealthy &#34;queen of misery&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</guid>
      <description>123
There are a lot of rich people in the pet world, and there is a number one price tag. The $375 million German Shepherd, Gunther IV, and also Toby Rimes, the dog world&amp;rsquo;s celebrity poodle, are worth $12 million, one rich and the other impeccably beautiful.
WEALTH
Unlike them, today&amp;rsquo;s story is about a dog who is famous not only for his wealth, but also for his surprising way of being spoiled, for his owner who left a huge inheritance to his dog but not to his grandchildren, which is also the origin of his owner&amp;rsquo;s nickname &amp;ldquo;the queen of miserliness&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How quickly can I get my family pet to accept a newly adopted cat? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b372b498dbab3169f62f8dd2046ad267/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b372b498dbab3169f62f8dd2046ad267/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, people can be addicted to having a pet, and in the early stages, they may just have a cat or a dog, but after a while, they feel that one pet is too lonely again, and at this time, they may think of having a second pet. However, many people have some concerns before getting a second pet, that is, there may be fights between the new pet and the aboriginal pet, especially if the second pet is a cat, after all, cats are still theoretically solitary animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is this &#34;cat&#39;s nest&#34; too luxurious? Silicon Valley Pet Cats Live in $1,500 Apartments </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/559440e623c10da58705f77083acde88/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/559440e623c10da58705f77083acde88/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pets also acupuncture, facial recognition Market size may exceed $240 billion! Netizens: Stop cloud sucking cats! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/550363696e2d5d7ccd87c914b7817962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/550363696e2d5d7ccd87c914b7817962/</guid>
      <description>CCTV Financial News November 26, 2020 As more and more pets come into the home, many industries are heating up, such as veterinary hospitals, which are becoming more and more numerous, and which have changed a lot from previous years.
Pet care &amp;ldquo;just in time &amp;ldquo;.
Over 15,000 veterinary hospitals on the ground.
On Sunday, the busiest day of the week came at an animal hospital located outside the North 4th Ring Road in Beijing, where a chinchilla&amp;rsquo;s teeth were pulled and a corgi&amp;rsquo;s acupuncture was administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&#39;s Mouth with His Own Hands </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</guid>
      <description>RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&amp;rsquo;s Mouth with His Own Hands
** CCTV news:** Recently, a 70-year-old man in Florida was walking his dog when an alligator suddenly emerged from a pond, grabbed the dog, and dragged it into the water. In a rush, the owner jumped into the pond, grabbed the alligator, and used his hand to break the alligator&amp;rsquo;s mouth open, and the dog was able to escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sending 4 cats to herd sheep, but when I went to see them again, I was disgusted: This is a very good lazy thief! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aba68643b6890fe0b68fa104adf168ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aba68643b6890fe0b68fa104adf168ad/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 13:00:30 Source: Veterinarian Videos
Report
What a beautiful picture of the sky and the wilderness, the grass blowing in the wind and the cows and sheep. If possible, the veterinarian would like to get away from the chaotic city and go to the grassland to graze cattle and sheep. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what kind of environment you live in, it&amp;rsquo;s important to be open-minded, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of sheepdogs, so has anyone heard of sheepdogs and cats?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The China Pet Consumption Trend Report 2019: Which &#34;shovelers&#34; are busy &#34;jerking off&#34;? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7b2ccf57e175f206095ae1e70a562bc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7b2ccf57e175f206095ae1e70a562bc3/</guid>
      <description>On November 19, Fan Tianyang, General Manager of Pet Procurement Department of Jingdong Retail Consumer Products Division, released the 2019 China Pet Consumption Trend Report (the &amp;ldquo;Report&amp;rdquo;) at the China International Pet &amp;amp; Aquarium Show (CIPS) Gala Dinner. According to the Report, China&amp;rsquo;s pet market has continued to expand in recent years, and the pet industry will continue to maintain a growth rate of over 14% in the next 3-5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The pet dog [UNK] cleans meticulously, the pet cat follows along full of curiosity </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e21637f5f5800ea3e5ae20c45987dcf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e21637f5f5800ea3e5ae20c45987dcf1/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-22 22:45:10 Source: Surprise Nature
Report
I&amp;rsquo;ll give you a full review.
Famous actress Christy 2020 posted on her personal social media platform on November 22, 2020 at 17:33 PM.
My booBoo help me hahahahaha!
At the same time, Zhong Li Ti also dried out a short video for 0:44 seconds, in which Zhong Li Ti mainly filmed the family&amp;rsquo;s pet dog dog to clean up their own, there are pet cats interspersed with back and forth, in short, this is a very loving, super warm picture and video, we&amp;rsquo;ll see it below!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>