<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Management on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/management/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Management on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/management/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Canine infestation control becomes a new test of urban civilization </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</guid>
      <description>The number of stray dogs without an owner is soaring, and the dog problem is poking at the city management &amp;ldquo;pain points &amp;ldquo;.
Dog control becomes the new test of urban civilization.
The reason why stray dogs have gradually become a &amp;ldquo;problem&amp;rdquo; in many cities is that owners have abandoned their dogs, lost their pets, and the uncontrolled breeding of stray dogs.
● As the number of urban pet dogs increases, the social problems caused by dog ownership are becoming more and more serious, and many deep-seated problems have not been fully exposed, nor have they attracted the attention of the legislative, law enforcement and epidemic prevention departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jiuquan Horsehair Mountain: &#34;1234&#34; Education Rectification Work System as the Leading System to Play the &#34;Safe Song&#34; at the Borderline </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ee898e6101a3ab41df5d7dc2f260bc5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ee898e6101a3ab41df5d7dc2f260bc5b/</guid>
      <description>Jiuquan Horsehair Mountain: &amp;ldquo;1234&amp;rdquo; Education Rectification Work System as the Overall Leader, Playing the &amp;ldquo;Safe Song&amp;rdquo; at the Border Frontline 2020-11-28 11:19 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
Sounding the &amp;ldquo;Safe Song&amp;rdquo; at the Borderline
The people&amp;rsquo;s business, the hair will rise; the people&amp;rsquo;s business, the millimetre will go. Since the education and rectification of &amp;ldquo;adhere to the political police, comprehensive and strict police&amp;rdquo;, the Jiuquan border management detachment Mahaishan border police station, as a pilot unit of education and rectification of the Gansu entry-exit border inspection terminus, has continuously improved its ideological awareness and innovated the practice of &amp;ldquo;1234&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Programming Cat [UNK] Chen Wanqing: The Real Barrier of an Enterprise Is Its Organizational Capability </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</guid>
      <description>Originally created by Azaka. Mustard pile view of education.
Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, speaks at the GET2020 conference on March 23rd.
♪ By Mustard Pile Ataku
♪ Editorial｜Mustard Pile View Education
On November 23rd, at the GET2020 Education Technology Conference hosted by Mustard Pile, with the theme of &amp;ldquo;Or Leap in the Abyss: Confidence and Development in Education&amp;rdquo;, Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, gave a keynote speech on &amp;ldquo;Organizational Thinking in Education Enterprises&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>