<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Breeding on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/breeding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Breeding on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/breeding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Concentrated inspection of pet sale business areas and residential communities. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</guid>
      <description>The new revision of the &amp;ldquo;Hohhot City Dog Management Regulations&amp;rdquo; from October 1 this year was formally implemented, the new rules clearly in the key dog management area, each household is limited to one dog, and may not keep a spirited dog and aggressive large dogs. In order to comprehensively promote the management of dog improvement work, strengthen the source control of large dogs and spirited dogs, over the past few days, the city public security bureau city management detachment joint Huimin District Public Security Branch of the Huanhe Street Police Station and Saihan District Public Security Branch of the University East Road Police Station, the pet sales business concentrated areas and residential neighborhoods to carry out a centralized inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you&#39;re looking for a job, what else can your silly dog do but be cute? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</guid>
      <description>Original: SME SME Technology Story
The physical differences in modern pet dogs are enormous. However, taxonomically, dogs and wolves all over the world belong to the same species. They are both capable of producing fertile offspring, whether in artificial or natural conditions.
But domestic dogs have made the right choice in abandoning wolfdogs. Today, there are only a few hundred thousand gray wolves in the wild, but domestic dogs are all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>