<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hyenas on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/hyenas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hyenas on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/hyenas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</guid>
      <description>Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two?
Nature can be very cruel, and one must always be on the lookout for animals that might sneak up on you, as this competition is the difference between life and death. In the African grasslands, there are two types of animals, hyenas and wild African dogs, which are about the same size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas are &#34;evil and scary&#34;? Hyenas haven&#39;t bitten anyone in 200 years in small Esse town </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7acc2891cfe125d18f9020aa44b6c682/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7acc2891cfe125d18f9020aa44b6c682/</guid>
      <description>The city has a long history of peaceful coexistence with hyenas. Centuries ago, these animals attacked people, sometimes even biting the townspeople to death. Then people made holes in the walls and threw food scraps in the holes, so the hyenas started to eat the rest of the food and stopped attacking people. According to the Harar people, there has not been another hyena attack on humans for 200 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Battle of the African Steppe for Ranking! Wild dog [UNK] hyena, who is the real African penis? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/23b5dee2e76c928174b89e0d3b7c8ff3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/23b5dee2e76c928174b89e0d3b7c8ff3/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to the little tyrant on the African grasslands, the &amp;ldquo;flat-headed brother&amp;rdquo; honey badger must be the one to beat. &amp;ldquo;Who could it be? Many people think of them as spotted hyenas, but when it comes to another fierce little bully, the spotted hyena is anything but.
The African Hyena is about 1 meter long and weighs up to 70 pounds, they look more like an adult Chinese Cavalier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why do hyenas often overstep their bounds? What animal is it afraid to mess with? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fa6dc331189857a7b4dc446e0708b319/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fa6dc331189857a7b4dc446e0708b319/</guid>
      <description>Probably one of the most feared and apex predators in sub-Saharan Africa, hyenas possess great strength, jaws capable of crushing bones, a bite second only to saltwater crocodiles and great white sharks, and incredible stamina, intelligence, and absolute strength. In fact, packs of hyenas are so strong that they often challenge lions and leopards, sometimes driving them out of their territory.
Hyenas are mostly scavengers, opportunists, and parasitic predators, meaning they steal food from the prey of other predators.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>