<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mr on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/mr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mr on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/mr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> An old man who adopted a pet dog as a child and immediately killed it for meat was sentenced to prison. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/adef3f9d4052436fa7c047f6a3d7118a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/adef3f9d4052436fa7c047f6a3d7118a/</guid>
      <description>Incheon District Court
A 74-year-old Korean man, Park Mok, adopted two dogs and promised the owners that he would &amp;ldquo;treat them like children,&amp;rdquo; but unexpectedly he killed the dogs less than two hours after adopting them and made them into a &amp;ldquo;tonic soup. On November 23, the Incheon District Court sentenced Mr. Park to six months in prison for &amp;ldquo;fraud&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;violating animal protection laws. However, this did not quell the public&amp;rsquo;s anger, as more than 62,000 Korean netizens have so far petitioned on the Cheong Wa Dae petition board, demanding that he be severely punished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shunde Longjiang Poly Man Killed Golden Retriever Poodle Owner Detained </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</guid>
      <description>In the past few years, the government has been trying to improve the quality of life for the people of Hong Kong.
The owner of the golden retriever, Mr. Wang, told reporters that his 70-year-old parents in the course of the dispute both sickness hospitalized, and the incident so far, the owner of the poodle and his family never apologized to himself and his parents, also from the future hospital to see his parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The chauffeur was chased up the hill by a pack of wild dogs in the early hours of the morning! He took a picture with his cell phone in the darkness and collapsed instantly </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/876841f843065726ba2812ef38a2453a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/876841f843065726ba2812ef38a2453a/</guid>
      <description>The chauffeur was chased up the hill by a pack of wild dogs in the early hours of the morning! He took a picture with his cell phone in the darkness and collapsed instantly&amp;hellip; 2020-08-17 17:46 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Media
In the early morning of August 17th, the police station in Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province, West Lake District received a tired voice: I&amp;rsquo;m a chauffeur, I&amp;rsquo;m being chased by wild dogs, in the mountains, I can&amp;rsquo;t get down!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Two horses snatched the golden retriever dog food through the cage, owner: never snatch in front of me. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/649f3070f7cf7f1097a8f935c10855ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/649f3070f7cf7f1097a8f935c10855ad/</guid>
      <description>To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that supports HTML5 video
Erha stole the golden retriever&amp;rsquo;s food through the cage, owner: Never steal in front of me! On November 22nd, Mr. Xie, in Xinxiang, Henan province, photographed his own husky expertly pouring dog food from the Golden Retriever tub next door into his own tub. Mr. Xie said the husky was only two years old and never grabbed it in front of him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>