<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dogs on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/dogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dogs on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/dogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A 4-year-old baby is as big as a pregnant woman and has 2 pounds of parasite fluid pumped out of her body! If you don&#39;t know this, don&#39;t keep pets with your kids! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</guid>
      <description>The director found that since when, jerking cats and rabbits has successfully led the new trend of child-skating.
A lot of parents like to take their babies to a variety of Netflix &amp;ldquo;cat jerking museum&amp;rdquo; to enjoy family time.
It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to play with cats and dogs.
The most important thing is to make sure that you have the right tools to do so.
01*
** 9 year old girl with multiple unexplained lumps on her body** **Causes related to cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Finnish Tour Company Gives Away Husky Dogs for Lack of Tourists </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/bede2ef602f265c7d6fce80016549c2f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/bede2ef602f265c7d6fce80016549c2f/</guid>
      <description>Husky &amp;amp; Co tourism company in Finnish Lapland posted an announcement on social networks that it was giving away 20 free husky dogs to caring people because there were no tourists during the new crown epidemic.
The message said, &amp;ldquo;Keep the huskies! We had to give away some of our dogs because of the coronavirus. We hope that these hardworking superheroes will find new homes while getting the love and care they deserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Vietnamese Puppy Wrote a Poem About a Cat Because It Looks Like a Cat </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</guid>
      <description>Dui, a Vietnamese dog, has quickly become popular on the Internet because it looks like a cat and is very cute, with netizens calling it &amp;ldquo;the funniest ball of fur&amp;rdquo; and speculating about its breed, according to a Feb. 26 report in the British newspaper Metro.
Dui is a cross between a Corgi and a Vietnamese Hmong dog, and some joked that he might be a mix of a Corgi and an English Shorthair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A civilized city can&#39;t tolerate stray dogs, it&#39;s better to control the uncivilized dog owners than to keep arresting them. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you hear me wailing? But I still have to cry out for my pain, bloodshed struggle, when bat after bat hit me on my body my head, do you know my blood tears themselves blurred my eyes, struggle, fear, blood dripping miserable barking tumbling try to stand up and fall down convulsions and gasp for breath mournful grief pale face, they howl, the whole world should listen to.
Recently, a city is now fighting and catching dogs again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A dog that is the sole pet of the wealthy &#34;queen of misery&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</guid>
      <description>123
There are a lot of rich people in the pet world, and there is a number one price tag. The $375 million German Shepherd, Gunther IV, and also Toby Rimes, the dog world&amp;rsquo;s celebrity poodle, are worth $12 million, one rich and the other impeccably beautiful.
WEALTH
Unlike them, today&amp;rsquo;s story is about a dog who is famous not only for his wealth, but also for his surprising way of being spoiled, for his owner who left a huge inheritance to his dog but not to his grandchildren, which is also the origin of his owner&amp;rsquo;s nickname &amp;ldquo;the queen of miserliness&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> African Wild Dogs Exercise &#34;Voting Rights&#34; by Sneezing Ideographs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0b1da1f091d84aaeb045c4150df50214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0b1da1f091d84aaeb045c4150df50214/</guid>
      <description>An international research team has found that African wild dogs exercise a &amp;ldquo;vote&amp;rdquo; by sneezing to determine whether the pack will hunt.
The endangered animal takes a break from hunting and then gathers for a &amp;ldquo;social gathering&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;negotiate&amp;rdquo; whether or not to launch a new hunt collectively.
The researchers observed and analyzed 68 &amp;ldquo;social gatherings&amp;rdquo; of five groups of African wild dogs in Botswana&amp;rsquo;s Okavango Delta and found that &amp;ldquo;sneezing plays a role in voting, and the more sneezes, the more likely the dogs are to set out on a hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Animal Ferocity: African Wild Dog Kills 16 Sheep and Deer in Night Attack </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday night, a pack of African wild dogs broke out of their enclosure at the West Midlands Safari Park and killed 16 sheep and deer at the zoo, including 10 Persian fallow deer and six barbarian sheep, according to the British newspaper The Sun.
When the keepers arrived at the scene of the incident, they were shocked by the bloodshed that had taken place.
A door separating the dogs from the other animals was blown down by high winds due to the storm of the century, and then 12 of the dogs ran into the living quarters of the other animals and carried out a horrific, dog-less slaughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</guid>
      <description>Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi?
Time：2018-06-07 19:36 Source：Today&amp;rsquo;s headlines Editor-in-charge：FoDuo
**The first thing I noticed is that there are a lot of different ways to get rid of a corgi. What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? Corgis are small, like a quiet environment, and never bark, making them perfect for families. So is a Corgi easy to keep?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:05:50 Source: Xiang Yang Psychology
Report
Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer.
Nowadays, many people have pugs and pit bulls because they have wrinkled faces and often look at people with innocent eyes, which makes them feel especially pitiful. In fact, pugs and bulls are two different kinds of pets, they are not the same species, but they are very similar in many aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Australian Wild Dogs Euthanized After Attacking Boy, Injuring Several People </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f7389de70a976f2d4d87a1af26674b39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f7389de70a976f2d4d87a1af26674b39/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Carex Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</guid>
      <description>Host: Ya&amp;rsquo;an Daily Media Group News Hotline: 0835-2222226 Advertising Hotline: 0835-2243318
##
Kerris Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! ##
Time： 2020-11-27 11:14:35 Source：Northwestern.com
The most important food for dogs can be said to be non-dog food, that comes in second is snacks, some people think snacks are unnecessary, but we humans also like to eat when nothing spicy chips and other snacks, not to mention the dog it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Concentrated inspection of pet sale business areas and residential communities. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</guid>
      <description>The new revision of the &amp;ldquo;Hohhot City Dog Management Regulations&amp;rdquo; from October 1 this year was formally implemented, the new rules clearly in the key dog management area, each household is limited to one dog, and may not keep a spirited dog and aggressive large dogs. In order to comprehensively promote the management of dog improvement work, strengthen the source control of large dogs and spirited dogs, over the past few days, the city public security bureau city management detachment joint Huimin District Public Security Branch of the Huanhe Street Police Station and Saihan District Public Security Branch of the University East Road Police Station, the pet sales business concentrated areas and residential neighborhoods to carry out a centralized inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Corgi is skinned and hung from a tree in a pile of meat. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c70ce53b7e024906658c07c4a1c92b19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c70ce53b7e024906658c07c4a1c92b19/</guid>
      <description>Original title: dog lost 2 hours later actually was skinned by people do not know how to say to the 2-year-old son &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
Photo of lost corgi and young owner.
The owner recognized the TOTO by the head pattern.
On the morning of April 6th, Ms. Li of Chengdu lost her Corgi that she had raised for two years. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m going to be able to do that, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m going to be able to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dog owners must understand these six points </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s important to be prepared before getting a dog!
**1, do not think that raising a dog is an easy thing **, although the dog can bring you a lot of happy time, but if you will not raise a dog, it will certainly bring you a lot of trouble.
2, before raising a dog, first consider their current living situation, whether the dog can provide a stable living environment, whether you have the economic strength to raise a dog, many college students on a whim, in the dormitory dog, in fact, this is very wrong, as long as you graduate, there is a certain economic strength, and a stable place to live and then proceed to consider raising a little guy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs and cats playing around accidentally catch fire! The next scene is a stunner! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</guid>
      <description>Dogs and cats playing around and getting burned! The next scene is a stunner! 2020-11-26 17:00 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
Recently, a surveillance video caused a lot of discussion among netizens.
In the video, dogs and cats are playing in the living room.
The cat&amp;rsquo;s tail accidentally caught on an open flame on the table.
The dog runs away immediately at the sight of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs know people from dogs, and shovelers&#39; personalities from dog ownership! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</guid>
      <description>There is a saying that &amp;ldquo;a dog knows a man by his dog&amp;rdquo;, and from the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior, you can probably know the character of the spade. We all know that the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior is directly related to the shovel, if the shovel is kinder, then the dog will not be fierce. If the shovel is more fierce, then the dog will not be kind. So let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the character of the shovelers who have several kinds of dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Except for Corgi, these are all short-legged dogs! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/4bb5ea8a5098d27a8f7aeb45d8d89ddb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/4bb5ea8a5098d27a8f7aeb45d8d89ddb/</guid>
      <description>When you think of short-legged dogs, the first thing that comes to mind is corgi dogs, whose most iconic parts are their short legs and butt! Their short legs and chubby body make them jumpy and happy as they walk. **The Corgi was originally a cattle dog, its name &amp;ldquo;Corgi&amp;rdquo; is Welsh for &amp;ldquo;corrci&amp;rdquo; petite. ** They are light as a feather and agile. Early on, they were used to herd cattle precisely because of their short legs, which prevented them from being kicked by cattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fatou swims and drowns, but not all dogs can swim! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</guid>
      <description>Now that the weather is getting hotter and hotter, many shovelers will take their dogs to the pet store or outdoors to go swimming in order to help them with the heat.
However, do you know that it is actually very dangerous to take your dog swimming at will?
Before that, a dog owner thought that his dog had hip problems, so he brought him to the pet swimming pool to swim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Five stray dogs actually gave up running when they were rounded up and chose to stay in place to guard their owner </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:55:19 Source: Big Love Puppy Control
Report
Recently, there was a photo that sparked a lot of discussion on the net.
In Kajang, Malaysia, in order to control stray dogs, a dog catching team was sent to the street to catch stray dogs&amp;hellip;.
But unlike other stray dogs, which would run away as soon as they saw someone chasing them, five of them not only didn&amp;rsquo;t run away, but also surrounded a homeless man sleeping on the ground&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Guangxi Yulin weighs more than 100 kg &#34;net red&#34; dog, usually in addition to sleeping is to eat! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 11:52:03 Source: xiaogu lookday
Report
A mention of Guangxi Yulin, you will think of what, will not think of &amp;ldquo;winter solstice fish raw summer solstice dog&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Yulin Lychee Dog Meat Festival&amp;rdquo; and so on. In fact, not everyone imagine that way, the dog meat festival just before the process down, so there has always been this festival, this festival, not what dogs are killed. Today (November 28), the editor to take a look at the county of Yulin, Guangxi Rong County, a net red dog, it lives for more than a decade, weighing more than 100 pounds, usually in addition to sleep is to eat, very prosperous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAVER DOG 2.[UNK] 4WD 4&#43;6 for all-terrain play </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</guid>
      <description>Recently, at the Guangzhou International Auto Show, Haval Dagoo &amp;ldquo;Chinese Garden Dog Edition&amp;rdquo; officially opened for pre-sale, which is the most cost-effective model among the Haval Dagoo 2.0T 4WD. As a target of &amp;ldquo;one more scale to pursue&amp;rdquo; by the high-end urban SUV enthusiasts, the Haval Dagoo 2.0T all-wheel drive model, once &amp;ldquo;out of the cage&amp;rdquo;, is armed with off-road performance comparable to that of SUVs of more than 300,000 joint ventures, making everyone very excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heartache! 5 stray dogs stay in place to protect homeless owners from escaping despite being rounded up! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/74c5bcbf0d0085237529444d7cfa93cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/74c5bcbf0d0085237529444d7cfa93cd/</guid>
      <description>Dogs are man&amp;rsquo;s most loyal friend! Kajang City, Malaysia, on the 20th of this month, the implementation of &amp;ldquo;dog catching operation&amp;rdquo;, sent to catch the dog brigade to the street to catch stray dogs, but just when all the stray dogs see humans and run away, there were 5 stray dogs are not afraid of being caught, but around a sleeping on the ground, choosing to stay next to the owner to protect him from bullying, photos were taken and uploaded on the network, triggering hot discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heroic Military Dogs Save Special Forces in Distress, Awarded Top Animal Honors </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e82e91e4d8591dca8a3f37a4cc61b83f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e82e91e4d8591dca8a3f37a4cc61b83f/</guid>
      <description>Kuno, a Belgian Shepherd from the British Special Forces, was able to save a number of British Special Forces soldiers when his unit was caught in a grenade attack and machine gun fire, according to a Nov. 24 article in the British newspaper Metro.
Unfortunately, Kuno was shot in both of his hind legs, and had to have one of his paws removed and be fitted with a custom-made prosthetic leg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How do I find a wild dog in Gangnam Park? Jiangnan Hundred Views Map of 4 Wild Dogs Location Coordinates Complete </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</guid>
      <description>Where are the wild dogs in Gangnam Hundred Views? There are many things to collect in Jiangnan Hundred Scenes, in addition to treasure chests, keys, big hens and four wild dogs. The following is the location of the four wild dog Jiangnan Hundred Views map is introduced, has not yet found all of the wild dog partners to see it!
Where are the wild dogs in the Gangnam Parkview?
We can find three wild dogs in the maze, and one at the end of the fog, as shown in the picture below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas attack a man in his home in Zimbabwe, leaving only the remains of his body in a brutal scene. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/686f2764a5793eacb508566cb4528e7c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/686f2764a5793eacb508566cb4528e7c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-23 17:03:02 Source: Financial Media Ticktock
Report
According to media reports on November 22nd, a tragic case occurred in Zimbabwe recently, a man was sleeping at home late at night, but was attacked by a pack of hyenas (liè) dogs, they tore the man into several pieces, the house was full of blood, can be described as gruesome, when people found, only the remains were left.
The victim, who was 46 years old, was out drinking with friends on the day of the attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I recently had the pleasure of hosting two surrogate Beagles and tell you what I know about Beagles! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</guid>
      <description>As people&amp;rsquo;s standard of living is getting better and better, the number of families with pet dogs is increasing, and lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing postings/questions from people asking about Beagles. It just so happens that recently I have received two surrogate training Beagles here, and I&amp;rsquo;ll state in advance that I have no previous experience with breeding or training Beagles, and this is my first experience with them, so today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about what I know about Beagles!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you&#39;re looking for a job, what else can your silly dog do but be cute? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</guid>
      <description>Original: SME SME Technology Story
The physical differences in modern pet dogs are enormous. However, taxonomically, dogs and wolves all over the world belong to the same species. They are both capable of producing fertile offspring, whether in artificial or natural conditions.
But domestic dogs have made the right choice in abandoning wolfdogs. Today, there are only a few hundred thousand gray wolves in the wild, but domestic dogs are all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s no longer difficult to choose dog food, take a look at the Aide Italia air dry food. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, food safety is such a serious problem that everything we eat must be safe. As for the dog food, there are some unscrupulous peddlers who, in order to earn money, make &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; at low prices to attract consumers. The dog eating &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; for a long time not only does not get good nutrition, but also may increase the risk of physical illness. So, the shovel officer in the dog selection dog food must be careful and careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Old man trains stray dog to pull himself, netizens: really bad  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 13:01:50 Source: Don&amp;rsquo;t let your heart fail you
Report
In the streets of Xi&amp;rsquo;an, Shaanxi Province, one often sees a small dog running along the road pulling an elderly man along.
However, unlike the stories we&amp;rsquo;ve seen before, the dog&amp;rsquo;s owner is not a disabled person, but an able-bodied person.
The dog is also the result of months of deliberate &amp;ldquo;training&amp;rdquo; by the old man.
The old man said, the dog is a stray dog, initially picked it up when it was very thin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pug dies after a week of illness, customer suspects pet store is selling &#34;Chow Chow&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</guid>
      <description>Ms. Wang and other customers are showing the pet purchase agreement form.
Chongqing Business News, a dog is the most loyal friend of mankind, with this idea, recently, living in Jiulongpo District, Ba Guo City, Ms. Wang spent 1450 yuan to buy a pug, but buy back less than a week, the dog died of infection virus. It&amp;rsquo;s not a coincidence, Xiao Wu and three other people from the same pet store to buy the dog has also fallen ill, they suspect, they are bought &amp;ldquo;week dog&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Recommended dog food for small dogs like Teddy and Bichon Frise! These brands of dog food are good quality and cheap! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1fd444133e588450b4780ed582f475d6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1fd444133e588450b4780ed582f475d6/</guid>
      <description>I have often seen many users ask questions about the choice of dog food for small dogs, and then go to believe those so-called dog food rankings.
In fact, there is no such thing as a dog food ranking, everyone&amp;rsquo;s consumption budget is different, the best is not necessarily the most suitable for you, the current recognized product quality is better ranking is the summit, craving for this kind of high-end brand is very good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Say &#34;No&#34; to Uncivilized Behavior】Don&#39;t Let Stray Dogs Become a Problem </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the reporter saw many stray dogs scurrying around the community in Qing Qi, which not only affects the cityscape, but also brings potential problems to the residents. I hope that dog owners do not abandon their pets, but also hope that the relevant departments to manage stray dogs.
Please consciously comply with →
The &amp;ldquo;Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region Regulations for the Promotion of Civilized Behavior&amp;rdquo; Article 24 of the city in the built-up areas of keeping dogs, to comply with the following code of conduct: (d) do not abuse, abandoned dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Science shows that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 23:07:16 Source: Basketball Bunny
Report
Scientific studies have shown that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the reasons why we say that!
In a study, Dog Ownership and Survival After a Major Cardiovascular Disease, the results of a study were published. In the paper, &amp;ldquo;Dog Ownership and Survival After Major Cardiovascular Events,&amp;rdquo; Swedish scientists tracked the mortality data of all patients aged 40 to 85 years who died of acute myocardial infarction and ischemic stroke from 2001 to 2012 and concluded that dog owners gained the following additional health benefits compared to those who did not own a dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Short-legged dog competition, who has the shortest legs, which one do you like the most? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f6aa857e17c20c34de0d6cd7766ed789/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f6aa857e17c20c34de0d6cd7766ed789/</guid>
      <description>In the human world, there are long-legged opahs and seven dwarfs, so naturally there are long-legged and short-legged woofers in the woof world too!
There was a long-legged woof Greeks before, Greeks elegant temperament, running smooth body line, growing is cute and lovely people like, so today we talk about a few small short legs in the woof world, short legs is always synonymous with cute, see if it is not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shovelers, do you know how to read your dog breed in English? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, I was standing on a small terrace in Wudaoying with a glass of hot red wine and a few friends, enjoying a leisurely life that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t dream of on a weekday. Suddenly one guy got up after looking at his watch with a serious expression, and just as we were trying to figure out which words were not in place, he said, &amp;ldquo;Sorry, the dog hasn&amp;rsquo;t left yet, I&amp;rsquo;ll go first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shunde Longjiang Poly Man Killed Golden Retriever Poodle Owner Detained </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</guid>
      <description>In the past few years, the government has been trying to improve the quality of life for the people of Hong Kong.
The owner of the golden retriever, Mr. Wang, told reporters that his 70-year-old parents in the course of the dispute both sickness hospitalized, and the incident so far, the owner of the poodle and his family never apologized to himself and his parents, also from the future hospital to see his parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Snowstorm Hits British Safari Park, African Wild Dogs Run Away, Killing 16 Animals </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of African wild dogs escaped from their yard and killed 16 animals in the Worcestershire Wildlife Park in England due to damage caused by Storm Siara, Sky News reported on February 14.
A park spokeswoman said that in the early morning hours of Feb. 9, 12 wild dogs entered a compound near the park, killing six Persian fallow deer and 10 Barbary sheep.
The park spokeswoman had previously said, &amp;ldquo;At no time was there a risk to public safety or any danger of animals escaping the park fence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sporting Dog [UNK] is a true sportsman! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</guid>
      <description>Breed Determines Character
Every type of dog has something in common, so &amp;ldquo;breed determines personality&amp;rdquo;. Most dog registries classify dogs according to their behavioral characteristics, instincts and family history. Currently, it is common worldwide to group dogs into seven distinctive categories: sporting dogs, hunting dogs with a keen sense of smell or sight, sheepdogs, working dogs, and dogs with a strong sense of smell or sight. Dogs, Toy Dogs and Family Dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Such a cute dog doesn&#39;t want to be touched? Shovel: Danger! It&#39;s aggressive! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</guid>
      <description>German Shepherd (German) The Shepherd is also used as a police dog, search and rescue dog, etc. due to its size, powerful appearance, and ability to work. In the UK, there was a German Shepherd who, despite being 4 years old, was still small enough to be a corgi and was often thought to be a puppy by passersby, but in fact he had a rare disease.
Tiger the German Shepherd suffers from dwarfism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The 5 most obvious phenomena of aging in a poodle are the ones that owners need to take care of, and they can give it a few more years of life! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c64becb6c14e70dd8ffa6d67bb31d893/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c64becb6c14e70dd8ffa6d67bb31d893/</guid>
      <description>Dogs, no matter how cute they are, will one day grow old, and pet owners should not let go.
However, if you can change the pace of your dog&amp;rsquo;s life as soon as you see him getting older, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to keep him alive for a long time.
If you have a poodle, how can you tell if your poodle is getting old? Let&amp;rsquo;s tell you about it here, so that you can pay attention to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 Cute Short-Legged Dogs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</guid>
      <description>1 - Corgi  When it comes to short legs, we have to mention the new web sensation in the dog world - the Corgi. By virtue of its rounded buttocks and limbs, the Corgi has become the new favorite of dog breeders.
The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s two main adorable points are its round butt, good feel and elasticity, and its legs are so short that even going upstairs is difficult, which is very cute and makes people want to hold it in their arms and jerk it off from head to toe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Try to avoid these 8 breeds of dog because it will cost the owner more money! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</guid>
      <description>Dogs are often called &amp;ldquo;man&amp;rsquo;s best friend&amp;rdquo;, we live with them, they give us unconditional love, and we provide them with a comfortable living environment and diet.
It is normal to provide the necessary expenses for a dog&amp;rsquo;s normal survival. However, there are some breeds of dogs that, because of their characteristics, can cost a dog parent more money.
The aggressive Rottweiler.
The list of dog breeds that are not recommended to be fed is made by a veterinarian who has returned to the United States after 20 years of practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What do you know about Corgi? Today we&#39;re going to discuss </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:26:26 Source: Abdominal Tearer&amp;rsquo;s Week
Report
The Corgi is very cute, easy to take care of, and takes up little time. The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s IQ is also very high, and he will quickly learn to master any skill he is taught, especially his appearance, and he is very good at playing tricks.
Looking online, I learned that there are roughly three types of Corgi: the first Cardigan-Welsh Corgi, the second Pembroke Welsh Corgi, and the third Swedish Corgi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is it like to own a Beagle? Beagle Personality Traits </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-19 09:44:11 Source: Mother &amp;amp; Baby Pie
Report
There are quite a few pet owners in China who have Beagles, and Petsky has met some Beagles and their owners in animal hospitals. ** Too lively! Too lively! Too lively! (Important point, say it three times.) **
In an animal hospital, you can come across all kinds of dogs, and almost all of them have their own unique characteristics that will make an impression on you in one way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is the best brand of dog food? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</guid>
      <description>Every dog shovel officer who brings home a dog, will love the cute dog. But for puppies in a new environment, the environment is already unfamiliar, and if the wrong dog food is chosen, it will directly affect the dog&amp;rsquo;s subsequent development. Choosing a suitable dog food for puppies is very critical, and an important way to continue the healthy growth of your dog is to choose a nutritionally rich and balanced, and safe and natural dog food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What should I do if my pug has diarrhea? Why do you have diarrhea? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</guid>
      <description>The silly and charming appearance of the pug has attracted many people&amp;rsquo;s attention, making it a popular pet dog nowadays. But in the process of caring for the pug, we can&amp;rsquo;t be sloppy. In the summer, it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for pugs to have diarrhea, and it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to know the relevant knowledge in advance. In the following, the editor of Porky.com will analyze the causes of diarrhea in pug dogs and the measures to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who is responsible for the death of 150 chickens, ducks, geese and ducks by 2 dogs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</guid>
      <description>2 dogs killed 150 chickens, ducks and geese. 2020-11-26 16:26 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
In rural areas
Many people like to have dogs.
Used as a &amp;ldquo;house keeper&amp;rdquo;
Dogs are more humane though.
But injuries do happen.
Dogs biting poultry is a common occurrence.
In the event of such an event
How should I be compensated?
Basic facts
In February 2020, Quanzhou County, a township in Quanzhou County, more than dog bites chicken and ducks, villagers will squat in the chicken farm, and then found the dog to bite the chicken, so the dog tracked to the Wen Mou home, after the villagers reported, the police processing, the organization of the two sides to negotiate unsuccessfully, then Wen Mou will sell the dog and does not admit that he is the dog, so the village Zhong Mou, He Mou and other 8 people will v.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You will never know what a short leg means to a dog. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</guid>
      <description>2019-02-22 17:07:32 Source: Searchwood
Report
As a short-legged dog, there are too many regrets and too many wishes that cannot be fulfilled in this life.
First of all, not being able to experience the sense of accomplishment that jumping brings to a dog!
When you&amp;rsquo;re camping with your buddies, running through the jungle, enjoying the summer breeze, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take long for you to discover a blow that&amp;rsquo;s too much for a dog to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>