<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Work on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Work on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> &#34;The shovelers wanted to work undisturbed, so they bought the same computer for the meow!&#34; Hahaha  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6a24426f9ce851df018c54b894db2976/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6a24426f9ce851df018c54b894db2976/</guid>
      <description>Shovelman: Well, Your Holiness, now that you have your own computer, don&amp;rsquo;t interrupt my work!
Shovel: You use your own computer!
Meow: Uh&amp;hellip;. You&amp;rsquo;re not fooling me, are you, shoveling shit?
Meow: What else does this thing do but take selfies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shovelers, do you know how to read your dog breed in English? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, I was standing on a small terrace in Wudaoying with a glass of hot red wine and a few friends, enjoying a leisurely life that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t dream of on a weekday. Suddenly one guy got up after looking at his watch with a serious expression, and just as we were trying to figure out which words were not in place, he said, &amp;ldquo;Sorry, the dog hasn&amp;rsquo;t left yet, I&amp;rsquo;ll go first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Wang Gou&#39;s private photos were exposed, wearing a sleeveless black dress with a [UNK] collar, sharp eyes and a good body full of stories </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6ad576d51c1cbe8d04a5ba8526102ae9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6ad576d51c1cbe8d04a5ba8526102ae9/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 14:22:04 Source: MoMoTravel
Report
Recently, a set of private photos of Wang Gu was exposed, in which she was wearing a V-neck sleeveless black dress lying on the bed, a gold chain belt around her waist, with sharp eyes and a good body full of stories.
Wang Ou&amp;rsquo;s face value has always been recognized, big eyes, high nose bridge, standard three court five eyes, this time with clothes and accessories decorations, the whole person more full of quality, look at the camera eyes full of story.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>