<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Family on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/family/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Family on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/family/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Five stray dogs actually gave up running when they were rounded up and chose to stay in place to guard their owner </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:55:19 Source: Big Love Puppy Control
Report
Recently, there was a photo that sparked a lot of discussion on the net.
In Kajang, Malaysia, in order to control stray dogs, a dog catching team was sent to the street to catch stray dogs&amp;hellip;.
But unlike other stray dogs, which would run away as soon as they saw someone chasing them, five of them not only didn&amp;rsquo;t run away, but also surrounded a homeless man sleeping on the ground&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is the dog food of love also genetic? The newest member of the family, Herman Ho, is the first to be appointed as the newest member of the family. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b032d7f4a7d55b5b74e9a59844d412d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b032d7f4a7d55b5b74e9a59844d412d8/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 13:25:44 Source: Oc Entertainment
Report
In &amp;ldquo;Three Times the Charm&amp;rdquo;, the combination of high school bully He Yuzun and supermodel Xi Mengyao&amp;rsquo;s sweetness and love together really is sweet.
#I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be able to do that.
The two of them wash dishes together, Lawrence Ho koala-style hug Xi Mengyao, kisses at every turn, sweet name is also casual.
The latest issue of the program, Lawrence Ho and Xi Mengyao two selling milk tea, men and women with the cooperation of the way, two words &amp;ldquo;not tired&amp;rdquo;, very grounded it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Meow Star&#34; Special: Gutiérrez Mari as &#34;Tinker Bell </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/34707847af5f00be40103fab08c7e901/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/34707847af5f00be40103fab08c7e901/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Meowth&amp;rdquo; Special: Gutiérrez and Mary as &amp;ldquo;Tinker Bell __
The Meowth Featurette Duration: 00:00 Source: Movie Network
Total 4 __
1905film.com The family film &amp;ldquo;The Meow Star&amp;rdquo;, directed by Chen Mucheng and starring Louis Koo, Mary Ma, Liu Chutian, Huang Xingjun, etc., has been released in theaters nationwide on July 14 (this Friday). The film tells the story of a cute appearance, with a clever and intelligent mind, easily get human favorites of the rhinoceros rhinoceros shouldering the mission to travel to Earth, but accidentally encountered a family of Kutian Le and Mary, and staged a scene of luck, meow interesting cat encounters.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>