<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Information on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/information/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Information on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/information/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Haver Dawg prices plummet and miss out on next year! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</guid>
      <description>Promotion Time: 2020/11/27-2020/11/30
Recently, the Great Wall Motor Haval store of Beijing Jishun Zhongda International Trade Co., Ltd. gave a cash discount of up to 20,000 yuan for its Haval big dog models. This activity is a limited-time special promotion, limited time and limited places, first-come, first-served! 4S store brand-new commercial vehicles National United Guarantee store car store tickets! Any manufacturer-authorized regular 4S store in the country free of charge and after maintenance, the day of purchase, the company can issue all the vehicle procedures (invoice, certificate of conformity, consistency certificate, vehicle information table, three-bag card) national licensing, warm tips: We take into account foreign customers to Beijing to buy a car far away, (successful purchase) can reimburse the one-way trip to Beijing [train tickets, high-speed rail tickets, air tickets (limited to owners).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hebei Forestry and Grass Bureau Issues Emergency Notice to Crack Down on Indiscriminate Hunting and Trafficking of Wildlife </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eff5864539a1b16d529b7bed89cf458d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eff5864539a1b16d529b7bed89cf458d/</guid>
      <description>Copyright and Disclaimer        Copyright and Disclaimer 1,All the works marked &amp;ldquo;Source: China Animal Husbandry Net&amp;rdquo; on this website belong to China Animal Husbandry Net, and may not be reproduced, excerpted or used in other ways without the authorization of this website. If the net has authorized the use of the works, it should be used within the scope of authorization, and indicate &amp;ldquo;Source: China Animal Husbandry Net&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Once a fierce warrior, now with an innocent expression, short legs and long body, guess who I am? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/559d62278b9f6a5044f67e07800664a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/559d62278b9f6a5044f67e07800664a9/</guid>
      <description>Once a fierce warrior, now with an innocent look and short legs and long body, guess who I am? -Dogipedia 2020-11-13 15:01 Source:Moe Family
Original title: once a fierce warrior, now the expression of innocence, short legs and long body guess who I am? -Dogipedia
__Back to Sohu for more
Responsible Editor.
Statement: The views expressed in this article represent the author&amp;rsquo;s own, Sohu is an information publishing platform, Sohu only provides information storage space services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>