<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Media on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/media/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Media on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/media/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A very spoiled brown husky that has traveled to all 48 states! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6aca539b52f168847abf2bd241a13749/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6aca539b52f168847abf2bd241a13749/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 09:46:40 Source: MiB Photography Community
Report
This distinctive husky made its debut on the social world section of the social media site Instagram. Unlike other huskies, this dog has a husky body and sapphire blue eyes, but his hair is brown. It&amp;rsquo;s very new, and it looks like a gray tree trunk.
&amp;ldquo;The Quoi Husky is actually not exactly brown in appearance. It still has a small white spot on its chest, and how many huskies do you see that look like it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Paralyzed Foreign Bulldog Gets New Life Standing and Walking with the Aid of a &#34;Wheelchair&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5b5bf20aeaf43898bfc879293a2d3be3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5b5bf20aeaf43898bfc879293a2d3be3/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 10:51:06 Source: Northeast Tourism
Report
Turkish Samsun, the paralyzed dog named Kara Simsek, also known as Knight. Rider, a French bulldog, was left in a stray rehabilitation center because of paralysis in his hind legs, and with the help of a walking wheelchair, he is back on his feet and walking again.
The paralyzed dog is named Kara Simsek, also known as Knight, in Samsun, Turkey. Rider, a French bulldog, was left in a stray rehabilitation center because of paralysis in his hind legs, and with the help of a walking wheelchair, he is back on his feet and walking again.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>