<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prices on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/prices/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prices on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/prices/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> English Dachshunds sold for nearly $17,000 during the epidemic, an 89% increase </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c70e5b50230b767f9531362ab929d1a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c70e5b50230b767f9531362ab929d1a1/</guid>
      <description>** CCTV Finance (reporter Wang Yongxi)** A survey has found that the price of puppies from Britain&amp;rsquo;s most popular breed has reached record levels, according to the website of Sky News UK. According to the data, the average price of a Dachshund rose to £1,838 in June this year, up 89 percent from £973 in March. English and French bulldog prices have also risen sharply. A review of the past three years of advertising on some of Britain&amp;rsquo;s largest classified advertising sites shows that the prices of English pugs, dachshunds and poodles have never been higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Haver Dawg prices plummet and miss out on next year! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</guid>
      <description>Promotion Time: 2020/11/27-2020/11/30
Recently, the Great Wall Motor Haval store of Beijing Jishun Zhongda International Trade Co., Ltd. gave a cash discount of up to 20,000 yuan for its Haval big dog models. This activity is a limited-time special promotion, limited time and limited places, first-come, first-served! 4S store brand-new commercial vehicles National United Guarantee store car store tickets! Any manufacturer-authorized regular 4S store in the country free of charge and after maintenance, the day of purchase, the company can issue all the vehicle procedures (invoice, certificate of conformity, consistency certificate, vehicle information table, three-bag card) national licensing, warm tips: We take into account foreign customers to Beijing to buy a car far away, (successful purchase) can reimburse the one-way trip to Beijing [train tickets, high-speed rail tickets, air tickets (limited to owners).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>