<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Little on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/little/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Little on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/little/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Dog mom gives birth to puppy, &#34;sleeping posture&#34; adorable master, can&#39;t put it down! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f7bc0a84f0d56961f563e52b1c9c89b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f7bc0a84f0d56961f563e52b1c9c89b7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 07:08:48 Source: Zhong Xin Chat Entertainment
Report
We are all irresistible to furry animals, they are very comfortable to touch, and they often give out some interaction to make their own defenseless, especially for girls, see these cute little guys are even more like, see the cute little life even lost soul, can&amp;rsquo;t wait to hide the cute little ones into their own arms.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been very fond of dogs since I was a child, and they grew up with me, and they would always stick to me no matter what, and they would accompany me wherever I went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Finished! Shiba Inu mimics its owner sitting and watching a video: this little short leg  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3b5d431c32bc97be646bc8145dcff7c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3b5d431c32bc97be646bc8145dcff7c1/</guid>
      <description>Pets can get a little carried away with their owners. Recently, a Shiba Inu who likes to sit and watch videos has gone viral on the Internet.
According to the introduction, the Shiba Inu, named Chiko, shocked everyone by indulging in watching videos at only 7 months old, while sitting upright on a bench.
According to his owner, Olesia Kuzmychova said that Chiko started watching TV with Olesia the first day she got home from Olesia&amp;rsquo;s house, and when Olesia went out, Olesia would also watch the TV so that Chiko could watch the show to her heart&amp;rsquo;s content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Owning a cat is a lot of fun, but it&#39;s also more expensive than you might think! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6753d22c9b600920f537b14902cb1d09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6753d22c9b600920f537b14902cb1d09/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:47:19 Source: What the hell is history?
Report
Owning a cat is a lot of fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also more expensive than you might think!
It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun to have a cat, and when you get home, you can see it lively running towards you, no matter what time it is, you will have such a cute little angel to accompany you, I also have a nutritious diet with cat food and cat snacks and some food, the little guy is healthy and lively, but, raising a cat is also more expensive than expected, I originally thought that raising a cat, only two hundred dollars a month cat food money, after five months of raising found that.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>