<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dog on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/dog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Dog on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/dog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A Vietnamese Puppy Wrote a Poem About a Cat Because It Looks Like a Cat </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</guid>
      <description>Dui, a Vietnamese dog, has quickly become popular on the Internet because it looks like a cat and is very cute, with netizens calling it &amp;ldquo;the funniest ball of fur&amp;rdquo; and speculating about its breed, according to a Feb. 26 report in the British newspaper Metro.
Dui is a cross between a Corgi and a Vietnamese Hmong dog, and some joked that he might be a mix of a Corgi and an English Shorthair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A civilized city can&#39;t tolerate stray dogs, it&#39;s better to control the uncivilized dog owners than to keep arresting them. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you hear me wailing? But I still have to cry out for my pain, bloodshed struggle, when bat after bat hit me on my body my head, do you know my blood tears themselves blurred my eyes, struggle, fear, blood dripping miserable barking tumbling try to stand up and fall down convulsions and gasp for breath mournful grief pale face, they howl, the whole world should listen to.
Recently, a city is now fighting and catching dogs again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A dog that is the sole pet of the wealthy &#34;queen of misery&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</guid>
      <description>123
There are a lot of rich people in the pet world, and there is a number one price tag. The $375 million German Shepherd, Gunther IV, and also Toby Rimes, the dog world&amp;rsquo;s celebrity poodle, are worth $12 million, one rich and the other impeccably beautiful.
WEALTH
Unlike them, today&amp;rsquo;s story is about a dog who is famous not only for his wealth, but also for his surprising way of being spoiled, for his owner who left a huge inheritance to his dog but not to his grandchildren, which is also the origin of his owner&amp;rsquo;s nickname &amp;ldquo;the queen of miserliness&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A guide dog with cancer fought to the death to return to its owner after dying (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</guid>
      <description>Guide dog Kermit is pictured with his blind owner, David.
A dog is man&amp;rsquo;s friend. A recent story from the United Kingdom proves this old adage once again. An eight-year-old guide dog named Kermit, who was suffering from cancer, did his best at the end of his life, trying with every fiber of his being to get his blind owner, David, from Birmingham to his home in Huddersfield before collapsing and taking his last breath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A monk saved more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats in 27 years: I was so busy that I didn&#39;t have time to pray. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</guid>
      <description>Originally I am the extraordinary gentleman.
About 50 kilometers from downtown Shanghai, Fengxian hides an old and dilapidated temple called the Annunciation Temple.
Unlike temples in the downtown area, there is no golden-hued palace, no solemn monks in robes, and no chanting of Buddhist scriptures.
But there is a monk in a red auto mechanic&amp;rsquo;s uniform who has rescued more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats.
This man is the abbot of the hospital, Zhixiang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A pack of African wild dogs drink from a river, a large hippo attacks, and the dogs withdraw. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2fc4a04d97cdd9a1942d1e85c0625783/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2fc4a04d97cdd9a1942d1e85c0625783/</guid>
      <description>The African wild dog is a very aggressive animal, although the wild dog is not very large and may not seem as big as our domestic dogs. However, the pack nature of the wild dog makes them one of the most important predators on the African savannah, and some people even consider them to be the third top predator in the African savannah besides lions and hyenas.
Wild dog packs are strictly disciplined, preying on animals several times their size through strength in numbers and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alternative dog &#34;laughs&#34; at corgi short legs, imitates its walking posture, laughing the netizens! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f98d90fdfacd37e554e0b5569531174b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f98d90fdfacd37e554e0b5569531174b/</guid>
      <description>Dog mimicry, sometimes super funny. This time the main character is a corgi, which is famous among many dogs for its &amp;ldquo;short legs&amp;rdquo; and is always being compared to other dogs in terms of height. One corgi was recently laughed at by his friends when an alternative dog lowered his body to mimic the way he walked, which made netizens laugh.
The two are good friends, but the mischievous Dustin always makes fun of Tayto, who has short limbs, and from time to time he will lower himself down to imitate Tayto&amp;rsquo;s walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Animal Ferocity: African Wild Dog Kills 16 Sheep and Deer in Night Attack </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday night, a pack of African wild dogs broke out of their enclosure at the West Midlands Safari Park and killed 16 sheep and deer at the zoo, including 10 Persian fallow deer and six barbarian sheep, according to the British newspaper The Sun.
When the keepers arrived at the scene of the incident, they were shocked by the bloodshed that had taken place.
A door separating the dogs from the other animals was blown down by high winds due to the storm of the century, and then 12 of the dogs ran into the living quarters of the other animals and carried out a horrific, dog-less slaughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</guid>
      <description>Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi?
Time：2018-06-07 19:36 Source：Today&amp;rsquo;s headlines Editor-in-charge：FoDuo
**The first thing I noticed is that there are a lot of different ways to get rid of a corgi. What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? Corgis are small, like a quiet environment, and never bark, making them perfect for families. So is a Corgi easy to keep?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:05:50 Source: Xiang Yang Psychology
Report
Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer.
Nowadays, many people have pugs and pit bulls because they have wrinkled faces and often look at people with innocent eyes, which makes them feel especially pitiful. In fact, pugs and bulls are two different kinds of pets, they are not the same species, but they are very similar in many aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Canine infestation control becomes a new test of urban civilization </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</guid>
      <description>The number of stray dogs without an owner is soaring, and the dog problem is poking at the city management &amp;ldquo;pain points &amp;ldquo;.
Dog control becomes the new test of urban civilization.
The reason why stray dogs have gradually become a &amp;ldquo;problem&amp;rdquo; in many cities is that owners have abandoned their dogs, lost their pets, and the uncontrolled breeding of stray dogs.
● As the number of urban pet dogs increases, the social problems caused by dog ownership are becoming more and more serious, and many deep-seated problems have not been fully exposed, nor have they attracted the attention of the legislative, law enforcement and epidemic prevention departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Carex Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</guid>
      <description>Host: Ya&amp;rsquo;an Daily Media Group News Hotline: 0835-2222226 Advertising Hotline: 0835-2243318
##
Kerris Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! ##
Time： 2020-11-27 11:14:35 Source：Northwestern.com
The most important food for dogs can be said to be non-dog food, that comes in second is snacks, some people think snacks are unnecessary, but we humans also like to eat when nothing spicy chips and other snacks, not to mention the dog it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Concentrated inspection of pet sale business areas and residential communities. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</guid>
      <description>The new revision of the &amp;ldquo;Hohhot City Dog Management Regulations&amp;rdquo; from October 1 this year was formally implemented, the new rules clearly in the key dog management area, each household is limited to one dog, and may not keep a spirited dog and aggressive large dogs. In order to comprehensively promote the management of dog improvement work, strengthen the source control of large dogs and spirited dogs, over the past few days, the city public security bureau city management detachment joint Huimin District Public Security Branch of the Huanhe Street Police Station and Saihan District Public Security Branch of the University East Road Police Station, the pet sales business concentrated areas and residential neighborhoods to carry out a centralized inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dog owners must understand these six points </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s important to be prepared before getting a dog!
**1, do not think that raising a dog is an easy thing **, although the dog can bring you a lot of happy time, but if you will not raise a dog, it will certainly bring you a lot of trouble.
2, before raising a dog, first consider their current living situation, whether the dog can provide a stable living environment, whether you have the economic strength to raise a dog, many college students on a whim, in the dormitory dog, in fact, this is very wrong, as long as you graduate, there is a certain economic strength, and a stable place to live and then proceed to consider raising a little guy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs know people from dogs, and shovelers&#39; personalities from dog ownership! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</guid>
      <description>There is a saying that &amp;ldquo;a dog knows a man by his dog&amp;rdquo;, and from the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior, you can probably know the character of the spade. We all know that the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior is directly related to the shovel, if the shovel is kinder, then the dog will not be fierce. If the shovel is more fierce, then the dog will not be kind. So let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the character of the shovelers who have several kinds of dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fatou swims and drowns, but not all dogs can swim! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</guid>
      <description>Now that the weather is getting hotter and hotter, many shovelers will take their dogs to the pet store or outdoors to go swimming in order to help them with the heat.
However, do you know that it is actually very dangerous to take your dog swimming at will?
Before that, a dog owner thought that his dog had hip problems, so he brought him to the pet swimming pool to swim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Five stray dogs actually gave up running when they were rounded up and chose to stay in place to guard their owner </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:55:19 Source: Big Love Puppy Control
Report
Recently, there was a photo that sparked a lot of discussion on the net.
In Kajang, Malaysia, in order to control stray dogs, a dog catching team was sent to the street to catch stray dogs&amp;hellip;.
But unlike other stray dogs, which would run away as soon as they saw someone chasing them, five of them not only didn&amp;rsquo;t run away, but also surrounded a homeless man sleeping on the ground&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Guangxi Yulin weighs more than 100 kg &#34;net red&#34; dog, usually in addition to sleeping is to eat! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 11:52:03 Source: xiaogu lookday
Report
A mention of Guangxi Yulin, you will think of what, will not think of &amp;ldquo;winter solstice fish raw summer solstice dog&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Yulin Lychee Dog Meat Festival&amp;rdquo; and so on. In fact, not everyone imagine that way, the dog meat festival just before the process down, so there has always been this festival, this festival, not what dogs are killed. Today (November 28), the editor to take a look at the county of Yulin, Guangxi Rong County, a net red dog, it lives for more than a decade, weighing more than 100 pounds, usually in addition to sleep is to eat, very prosperous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAVER DOG 2.[UNK] 4WD 4&#43;6 for all-terrain play </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</guid>
      <description>Recently, at the Guangzhou International Auto Show, Haval Dagoo &amp;ldquo;Chinese Garden Dog Edition&amp;rdquo; officially opened for pre-sale, which is the most cost-effective model among the Haval Dagoo 2.0T 4WD. As a target of &amp;ldquo;one more scale to pursue&amp;rdquo; by the high-end urban SUV enthusiasts, the Haval Dagoo 2.0T all-wheel drive model, once &amp;ldquo;out of the cage&amp;rdquo;, is armed with off-road performance comparable to that of SUVs of more than 300,000 joint ventures, making everyone very excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How do I find a wild dog in Gangnam Park? Jiangnan Hundred Views Map of 4 Wild Dogs Location Coordinates Complete </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</guid>
      <description>Where are the wild dogs in Gangnam Hundred Views? There are many things to collect in Jiangnan Hundred Scenes, in addition to treasure chests, keys, big hens and four wild dogs. The following is the location of the four wild dog Jiangnan Hundred Views map is introduced, has not yet found all of the wild dog partners to see it!
Where are the wild dogs in the Gangnam Parkview?
We can find three wild dogs in the maze, and one at the end of the fog, as shown in the picture below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I recently had the pleasure of hosting two surrogate Beagles and tell you what I know about Beagles! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</guid>
      <description>As people&amp;rsquo;s standard of living is getting better and better, the number of families with pet dogs is increasing, and lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing postings/questions from people asking about Beagles. It just so happens that recently I have received two surrogate training Beagles here, and I&amp;rsquo;ll state in advance that I have no previous experience with breeding or training Beagles, and this is my first experience with them, so today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about what I know about Beagles!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you&#39;re looking for a job, what else can your silly dog do but be cute? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</guid>
      <description>Original: SME SME Technology Story
The physical differences in modern pet dogs are enormous. However, taxonomically, dogs and wolves all over the world belong to the same species. They are both capable of producing fertile offspring, whether in artificial or natural conditions.
But domestic dogs have made the right choice in abandoning wolfdogs. Today, there are only a few hundred thousand gray wolves in the wild, but domestic dogs are all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s no longer difficult to choose dog food, take a look at the Aide Italia air dry food. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, food safety is such a serious problem that everything we eat must be safe. As for the dog food, there are some unscrupulous peddlers who, in order to earn money, make &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; at low prices to attract consumers. The dog eating &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; for a long time not only does not get good nutrition, but also may increase the risk of physical illness. So, the shovel officer in the dog selection dog food must be careful and careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Linda H. Gay admits to being in love with Lin Feng? A video of a kiss, with a message later is the person who has dog food to spread </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f0cd64c45ede2c8d92e084378f99b1ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f0cd64c45ede2c8d92e084378f99b1ad/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the two actresses Lin Huan and Yue Hsi Gay were photographed together at a dinner party, and their relationship is suspected to be exposed.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in a position to do this.
It is the first time I have ever been to a school. In the video, Yueh-Hsi Gai is holding a Corgi, which is probably her own pet, and as soon as the dog came to Yuehsi&amp;rsquo;s arms, it started licking her mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Old man trains stray dog to pull himself, netizens: really bad  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 13:01:50 Source: Don&amp;rsquo;t let your heart fail you
Report
In the streets of Xi&amp;rsquo;an, Shaanxi Province, one often sees a small dog running along the road pulling an elderly man along.
However, unlike the stories we&amp;rsquo;ve seen before, the dog&amp;rsquo;s owner is not a disabled person, but an able-bodied person.
The dog is also the result of months of deliberate &amp;ldquo;training&amp;rdquo; by the old man.
The old man said, the dog is a stray dog, initially picked it up when it was very thin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pug dies after a week of illness, customer suspects pet store is selling &#34;Chow Chow&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</guid>
      <description>Ms. Wang and other customers are showing the pet purchase agreement form.
Chongqing Business News, a dog is the most loyal friend of mankind, with this idea, recently, living in Jiulongpo District, Ba Guo City, Ms. Wang spent 1450 yuan to buy a pug, but buy back less than a week, the dog died of infection virus. It&amp;rsquo;s not a coincidence, Xiao Wu and three other people from the same pet store to buy the dog has also fallen ill, they suspect, they are bought &amp;ldquo;week dog&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&#39;s Mouth with His Own Hands </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</guid>
      <description>RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&amp;rsquo;s Mouth with His Own Hands
** CCTV news:** Recently, a 70-year-old man in Florida was walking his dog when an alligator suddenly emerged from a pond, grabbed the dog, and dragged it into the water. In a rush, the owner jumped into the pond, grabbed the alligator, and used his hand to break the alligator&amp;rsquo;s mouth open, and the dog was able to escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Say &#34;No&#34; to Uncivilized Behavior】Don&#39;t Let Stray Dogs Become a Problem </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the reporter saw many stray dogs scurrying around the community in Qing Qi, which not only affects the cityscape, but also brings potential problems to the residents. I hope that dog owners do not abandon their pets, but also hope that the relevant departments to manage stray dogs.
Please consciously comply with →
The &amp;ldquo;Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region Regulations for the Promotion of Civilized Behavior&amp;rdquo; Article 24 of the city in the built-up areas of keeping dogs, to comply with the following code of conduct: (d) do not abuse, abandoned dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Science shows that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 23:07:16 Source: Basketball Bunny
Report
Scientific studies have shown that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the reasons why we say that!
In a study, Dog Ownership and Survival After a Major Cardiovascular Disease, the results of a study were published. In the paper, &amp;ldquo;Dog Ownership and Survival After Major Cardiovascular Events,&amp;rdquo; Swedish scientists tracked the mortality data of all patients aged 40 to 85 years who died of acute myocardial infarction and ischemic stroke from 2001 to 2012 and concluded that dog owners gained the following additional health benefits compared to those who did not own a dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shovelers, do you know how to read your dog breed in English? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, I was standing on a small terrace in Wudaoying with a glass of hot red wine and a few friends, enjoying a leisurely life that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t dream of on a weekday. Suddenly one guy got up after looking at his watch with a serious expression, and just as we were trying to figure out which words were not in place, he said, &amp;ldquo;Sorry, the dog hasn&amp;rsquo;t left yet, I&amp;rsquo;ll go first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sitting down for a real romance with Lin Feng? The first time I saw a dog, I thought it was a dog. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f35b69f865291a94746edfe962a3a4cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f35b69f865291a94746edfe962a3a4cb/</guid>
      <description> Sitting down for a real romance with Lin Jianli? The first time I saw a dog, I thought it was a dog. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Snowstorm Hits British Safari Park, African Wild Dogs Run Away, Killing 16 Animals </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of African wild dogs escaped from their yard and killed 16 animals in the Worcestershire Wildlife Park in England due to damage caused by Storm Siara, Sky News reported on February 14.
A park spokeswoman said that in the early morning hours of Feb. 9, 12 wild dogs entered a compound near the park, killing six Persian fallow deer and 10 Barbary sheep.
The park spokeswoman had previously said, &amp;ldquo;At no time was there a risk to public safety or any danger of animals escaping the park fence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sporting Dog [UNK] is a true sportsman! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</guid>
      <description>Breed Determines Character
Every type of dog has something in common, so &amp;ldquo;breed determines personality&amp;rdquo;. Most dog registries classify dogs according to their behavioral characteristics, instincts and family history. Currently, it is common worldwide to group dogs into seven distinctive categories: sporting dogs, hunting dogs with a keen sense of smell or sight, sheepdogs, working dogs, and dogs with a strong sense of smell or sight. Dogs, Toy Dogs and Family Dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Such a cute dog doesn&#39;t want to be touched? Shovel: Danger! It&#39;s aggressive! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</guid>
      <description>German Shepherd (German) The Shepherd is also used as a police dog, search and rescue dog, etc. due to its size, powerful appearance, and ability to work. In the UK, there was a German Shepherd who, despite being 4 years old, was still small enough to be a corgi and was often thought to be a puppy by passersby, but in fact he had a rare disease.
Tiger the German Shepherd suffers from dwarfism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Talking Short Legged Dog Game Download </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e9c2cc5c4f880b623a28db7d17c85329/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e9c2cc5c4f880b623a28db7d17c85329/</guid>
      <description>Talking Short Legs is a dog game with cute, lovely and interesting graphics, this cute little dog can make all kinds of strange sounds, it is also very realistic.
The Talking Short-Legged Dog Game Features.  The picture is interesting, lively and lovely, liked by many players. 2.
 The scenes are colorful, and the color matching is perfect and realistic, bringing players the feeling of being in the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> There is a kind of &#34;plastic surgery&#34; called Pauline Lantern&#39;s asthma dog, now in uniform, handsome unrecognizable! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1dc478d9e8ebac1d075fb37ebf386085/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1dc478d9e8ebac1d075fb37ebf386085/</guid>
      <description>One drama that just aired and attracted a large number of fans and is now a household name is &amp;ldquo;Baolian Lantern&amp;rdquo;. When this drama was aired, the response was really great. The drama tells the story of the man, Shen Xiang, who uses an axe to chop the mountain to save his mother. Because of this drama, a lot of people have been fired, for example, the lead role of Erlang Shen, played by Jiao Junen, whose outstanding appearance made the audience think that he was the original Erlang Shen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 Cute Short-Legged Dogs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</guid>
      <description>1 - Corgi  When it comes to short legs, we have to mention the new web sensation in the dog world - the Corgi. By virtue of its rounded buttocks and limbs, the Corgi has become the new favorite of dog breeders.
The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s two main adorable points are its round butt, good feel and elasticity, and its legs are so short that even going upstairs is difficult, which is very cute and makes people want to hold it in their arms and jerk it off from head to toe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Try to avoid these 8 breeds of dog because it will cost the owner more money! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</guid>
      <description>Dogs are often called &amp;ldquo;man&amp;rsquo;s best friend&amp;rdquo;, we live with them, they give us unconditional love, and we provide them with a comfortable living environment and diet.
It is normal to provide the necessary expenses for a dog&amp;rsquo;s normal survival. However, there are some breeds of dogs that, because of their characteristics, can cost a dog parent more money.
The aggressive Rottweiler.
The list of dog breeds that are not recommended to be fed is made by a veterinarian who has returned to the United States after 20 years of practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What do you know about Corgi? Today we&#39;re going to discuss </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:26:26 Source: Abdominal Tearer&amp;rsquo;s Week
Report
The Corgi is very cute, easy to take care of, and takes up little time. The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s IQ is also very high, and he will quickly learn to master any skill he is taught, especially his appearance, and he is very good at playing tricks.
Looking online, I learned that there are roughly three types of Corgi: the first Cardigan-Welsh Corgi, the second Pembroke Welsh Corgi, and the third Swedish Corgi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is it like to own a Beagle? Beagle Personality Traits </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-19 09:44:11 Source: Mother &amp;amp; Baby Pie
Report
There are quite a few pet owners in China who have Beagles, and Petsky has met some Beagles and their owners in animal hospitals. ** Too lively! Too lively! Too lively! (Important point, say it three times.) **
In an animal hospital, you can come across all kinds of dogs, and almost all of them have their own unique characteristics that will make an impression on you in one way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is the best brand of dog food? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</guid>
      <description>Every dog shovel officer who brings home a dog, will love the cute dog. But for puppies in a new environment, the environment is already unfamiliar, and if the wrong dog food is chosen, it will directly affect the dog&amp;rsquo;s subsequent development. Choosing a suitable dog food for puppies is very critical, and an important way to continue the healthy growth of your dog is to choose a nutritionally rich and balanced, and safe and natural dog food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What should I do if my pug has diarrhea? Why do you have diarrhea? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</guid>
      <description>The silly and charming appearance of the pug has attracted many people&amp;rsquo;s attention, making it a popular pet dog nowadays. But in the process of caring for the pug, we can&amp;rsquo;t be sloppy. In the summer, it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for pugs to have diarrhea, and it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to know the relevant knowledge in advance. In the following, the editor of Porky.com will analyze the causes of diarrhea in pug dogs and the measures to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who is responsible for the death of 150 chickens, ducks, geese and ducks by 2 dogs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</guid>
      <description>2 dogs killed 150 chickens, ducks and geese. 2020-11-26 16:26 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
In rural areas
Many people like to have dogs.
Used as a &amp;ldquo;house keeper&amp;rdquo;
Dogs are more humane though.
But injuries do happen.
Dogs biting poultry is a common occurrence.
In the event of such an event
How should I be compensated?
Basic facts
In February 2020, Quanzhou County, a township in Quanzhou County, more than dog bites chicken and ducks, villagers will squat in the chicken farm, and then found the dog to bite the chicken, so the dog tracked to the Wen Mou home, after the villagers reported, the police processing, the organization of the two sides to negotiate unsuccessfully, then Wen Mou will sell the dog and does not admit that he is the dog, so the village Zhong Mou, He Mou and other 8 people will v.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You will never know what a short leg means to a dog. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</guid>
      <description>2019-02-22 17:07:32 Source: Searchwood
Report
As a short-legged dog, there are too many regrets and too many wishes that cannot be fulfilled in this life.
First of all, not being able to experience the sense of accomplishment that jumping brings to a dog!
When you&amp;rsquo;re camping with your buddies, running through the jungle, enjoying the summer breeze, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take long for you to discover a blow that&amp;rsquo;s too much for a dog to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Zoo feeds African wild dogs live sheep to keep them wild (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</guid>
      <description>Zoos feed African wild dogs to live sheep to keep them wild (Figure)
CCTV International www.cctv.com March 12, 2007, 10:50 Source.
New Business News
Zoo Feeds African Wild Dogs Live Sheep to Keep Them Wild
A frightened shivering sheep, a group of howling madly jumped on the African wild dogs &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; bloody, brutal, in the sheep tearing heart of the cry, it is the flesh of the wild dogs piece by piece to tear off, finally only left broken skeleton, and those who eat meat of the wild dogs, face covered with blood, the eyes of the fierce light.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>