<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Like on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/like/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Like on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/like/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</guid>
      <description>Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi?
Time：2018-06-07 19:36 Source：Today&amp;rsquo;s headlines Editor-in-charge：FoDuo
**The first thing I noticed is that there are a lot of different ways to get rid of a corgi. What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? Corgis are small, like a quiet environment, and never bark, making them perfect for families. So is a Corgi easy to keep?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cixi warned the Eight Allied Forces: I don&#39;t care if I occupy the land, I can&#39;t see the killings, but I won&#39;t do it! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/83cad9d5829da07bc327895f8e5a1c39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/83cad9d5829da07bc327895f8e5a1c39/</guid>
      <description>Directed by.
I once read an interesting article about what would happen if Empress Lu, Wu Zetian, and Cixi fought each other in court. The general opinion is that Empress Lu = Wu Zetian &amp;gt; Ci Xi, these three people are not in a dynasty can not be compared, but from these three people&amp;rsquo;s diplomacy and internal affairs, let alone Lu and Wu Zetian&amp;rsquo;s fighting power that is stronger, just put Ci Xi in the end, I believe there will not be many people will raise objections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Maine cat is facing Yi Yun Qianxi, is your cat the same model as the star? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</guid>
      <description>They are agile, a little sleepy, like to lick their own hair clean, and have a maverick personality. They are not always obedient to their masters, and are more like two equal friends than subordinates. Is the cat the same as the star?
1 Dusk. British Shorthair
British Shorthair cats are round and chubby, with short, coarse and well-developed limbs, a short, dense coat, a big head and a round face that looks cute, gentle and calm, very friendly and easy to feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The night life of cats is much more exciting than yours.  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago, Weibo was ablaze with a spoof video from YouTube.
In the cat&amp;rsquo;s first view, a mysterious day goes by unbeknownst to the shovelers.
As soon as the good cat in the video leaves the house-
Money is easy to rob.
The Hammer Man Hammering Away
But what the stupid humans don&amp;rsquo;t know is that the content of this video is actually not all that bad - it&amp;rsquo;s a spoof!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>