<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Cats with a short life span often have these six characteristics. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</guid>
      <description>A cat&amp;rsquo;s lifespan depends on many factors, but they all manifest themselves physically. Generally, cats with short life span tend to have these 6 characteristics, hopefully your cat will have none of them.
 Overweight  In both humans and cats, obesity can lead to many diseases. For example, diabetes, heart disease and other problems.
How can you tell if your cat is overweight? You can touch your cat near the chest with your hand, and if you can&amp;rsquo;t feel the ribs, then it can be said to be obese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [UNK] Haskell x Coca-Cola Retro Refrigerator with a Postmodernist Feel </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1ecf006a891fd92bda3da29650dcd936/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1ecf006a891fd92bda3da29650dcd936/</guid>
      <description>HCK Haskell, in order to satisfy consumers&amp;rsquo; pursuit of post-modern life, launched the HCK Coke Girl Mini-Refrigerator in cooperation with Coca-Cola, a big IP company. The beauty of real life is displayed in retro form.
HCK Haskell Cola girl small refrigerator appearance go retro light extravagant wind, polished one-piece heavy body highlighting the geometric beauty of the body arc, especially the HCK Haskell classic curved door design, give people a warm and delicate high-grade texture, is the designer spent years of time carefully carved out the precious masterpiece.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>