<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Niubi on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/niubi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Niubi on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/niubi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> &#34;The shovelers wanted to work undisturbed, so they bought the same computer for the meow!&#34; Hahaha  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6a24426f9ce851df018c54b894db2976/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6a24426f9ce851df018c54b894db2976/</guid>
      <description>Shovelman: Well, Your Holiness, now that you have your own computer, don&amp;rsquo;t interrupt my work!
Shovel: You use your own computer!
Meow: Uh&amp;hellip;. You&amp;rsquo;re not fooling me, are you, shoveling shit?
Meow: What else does this thing do but take selfies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> &#34;Yang&#39;s cat has been found, and they say it&#39;s used in this way, so come in and learn!&#34; Hahaha  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9be737e8c125821694a7f9cac80afa7b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9be737e8c125821694a7f9cac80afa7b/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I found a hot search on Weibo: #Yang Gao&amp;rsquo;s cat is lost#.
It is known that the golden gradient layer, called Tangerine, is a little baby raised by Yang Gao.
But on November 11, the little tangerine, which was placed in a relative&amp;rsquo;s home, suddenly ran away from home.
When she learned the news, her sister sent out a message at midnight asking for help: &amp;ldquo;Just be safe and don&amp;rsquo;t wander the streets!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 12 wins in the arena in May, the first Meowth 501 interview! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/73d5828d622f5048af9a1c10cdc4757d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/73d5828d622f5048af9a1c10cdc4757d/</guid>
      <description>Hearthstone Legend May arena 12 wins ranked number one mystery man &amp;ldquo;Meow 501&amp;rdquo; interview.
About Individuals
geyuan6: Hi 501, you&amp;rsquo;re #1 in the arena May rankings just released by China National Service, congratulations! I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;ve got the right stuff for you.
The first thing you need to do is to get your own copy of the book. A lot of people have been in the business for a long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5-year-old girl&#39;s behavior on bus infuriates netizens, psychologists: bear child is the victim </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c5fe0068e97d26302212b08ab0f7a397/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c5fe0068e97d26302212b08ab0f7a397/</guid>
      <description>The term &amp;ldquo;bear cub&amp;rdquo; is no stranger to us, and every time a news report about a bear cub comes out, it refreshes our perceptions, and someone has even said, &amp;ldquo;There is no such thing as a bear, only more bears!
The 5-year-old girl&amp;rsquo;s behavior on the bus angered netizens, multiple heated discussion
Recently, a short video has been widely discussed on the Internet.
It happened on a bus, a 5-year-old girl with her mother on the bus, holding a furry little thing in her hand, and a closer look revealed that it was a small hamster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 72 Battleships Completed, China&#39;s Naval Defense Upgraded! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/10a61e91f5d4f23a650b3581f18d31e4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/10a61e91f5d4f23a650b3581f18d31e4/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 14:48:11 Source: Global New Military
Report
Click on the arrow.
&amp;ldquo;Blue Letter&amp;rdquo;
Follow us!
The 056 ship ushers in the closing work, our newest 056A series frigate &amp;ldquo;Aba&amp;rdquo; is put into service and joins the Southern War Area Navy. With the full load displacement of less than 1500 tons, why are the Type 056 frigates so popular?
China&amp;rsquo;s coastline is too long and there are too many islands and reefs, so the purpose of building the 056 is to provide coastal defense and island patrol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A &#34;cat&#34; came to the house, with a fierce temper, and alarmed the police! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ab96a690d1a8b2ace91977c641067c37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ab96a690d1a8b2ace91977c641067c37/</guid>
      <description>Source: City Scene Chongqing News Channel
May not be reproduced without permission.
On November 24, a cat came to a resident&amp;rsquo;s home in Bai Shi Yi, Chongqing Hi-Tech Zone, and at first the resident wanted to tease the cat, but later, he had to call the police for help, what kind of cat still needs police action?
The cat, whose face resembled that of a leopard, also had spots and stripes that differed from those of a typical domestic cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A 4-year-old baby is as big as a pregnant woman and has 2 pounds of parasite fluid pumped out of her body! If you don&#39;t know this, don&#39;t keep pets with your kids! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e06484c3417f5f8ef6d31048f23af995/</guid>
      <description>The director found that since when, jerking cats and rabbits has successfully led the new trend of child-skating.
A lot of parents like to take their babies to a variety of Netflix &amp;ldquo;cat jerking museum&amp;rdquo; to enjoy family time.
It&amp;rsquo;s a good idea to play with cats and dogs.
The most important thing is to make sure that you have the right tools to do so.
01*
** 9 year old girl with multiple unexplained lumps on her body** **Causes related to cats!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Dog Named Prince exposes the plot of a four-panel comic strip with a cute little short-legged dog named Corgi everyday to adorable hearts [UNK][UNK]Time.com </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/93dc2762284b1a65f5cb8aea5af40503/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/93dc2762284b1a65f5cb8aea5af40503/</guid>
      <description>Time.com
Movies
A Dog Named Prince
Recently, a set of four-panel cartoons featuring Koji &amp;ldquo;The Prince&amp;rdquo; has been released. The cartoon uses an anthropomorphic approach to tell the story of &amp;ldquo;Prince&amp;rdquo;&amp;rsquo;s ridiculous moments and spoofs on his daily life, with a cute image and humorous writing style that makes people shout &amp;ldquo;I want more! &amp;ldquo;
Koji&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;short legs&amp;rdquo; has always been a popular &amp;ldquo;nudging point&amp;rdquo; and a &amp;ldquo;notch&amp;rdquo; used as a joke.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Finnish Tour Company Gives Away Husky Dogs for Lack of Tourists </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/bede2ef602f265c7d6fce80016549c2f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/bede2ef602f265c7d6fce80016549c2f/</guid>
      <description>Husky &amp;amp; Co tourism company in Finnish Lapland posted an announcement on social networks that it was giving away 20 free husky dogs to caring people because there were no tourists during the new crown epidemic.
The message said, &amp;ldquo;Keep the huskies! We had to give away some of our dogs because of the coronavirus. We hope that these hardworking superheroes will find new homes while getting the love and care they deserve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Hong Kong Poodle tested positive for a new crown and currently has no associated medical conditions. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e47a662cd33c21d5ac0716dc7c649ad3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e47a662cd33c21d5ac0716dc7c649ad3/</guid>
      <description>According to the Hong Kong East Daily News, the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department (AFCD) of the Hong Kong SAR Government said on Friday that it received a poodle whose sample tested positive for the new coronavirus.
The department said the poodle is from Tsuen Wan, and its owner is a close contact of the confirmed new cases of crown, so the poodle was sent to the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department last Friday (20) to undergo quarantine, and the sample taken showed positive results for the new crown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Hong Kong Poodle tested positive for a new crown with no associated symptoms. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/8f1516613ac736cc5e2d7cfd62ba1297/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/8f1516613ac736cc5e2d7cfd62ba1297/</guid>
      <description>According to the news just released by Hong Kong Eastweb, the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department of the Hong Kong SAR Government said on 25 October that it received a poodle whose sample tested positive for the new coronavirus.
According to the department, the poodle is from Tsuen Wan and its owner is a close contact with a confirmed case of neocrowning, so the poodle was sent to the Agriculture, Fisheries and Conservation Department for quarantine last Friday (20), and the sample taken showed positive results for neocrowning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Vietnamese Puppy Wrote a Poem About a Cat Because It Looks Like a Cat </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7da121417b0fb2f2e0e70f14cfb3e316/</guid>
      <description>Dui, a Vietnamese dog, has quickly become popular on the Internet because it looks like a cat and is very cute, with netizens calling it &amp;ldquo;the funniest ball of fur&amp;rdquo; and speculating about its breed, according to a Feb. 26 report in the British newspaper Metro.
Dui is a cross between a Corgi and a Vietnamese Hmong dog, and some joked that he might be a mix of a Corgi and an English Shorthair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A black-faced, bitter, ugly, ugly pug, do you like it? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/71ac7a9525d12e2974526d5217bf74bb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/71ac7a9525d12e2974526d5217bf74bb/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-21 07:56:48 Source: Enlightenment Education
Report
However, there is one kind of dog that looks bitter and unhappy, and this kind of dog is the Pug.
At first glance, the black face and furrowed brow of a pug always make you think that it is unhappy, and you can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel an urge to protect it. However, the personality of the Pug has nothing to do with this world-weary, sad appearance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A cat triggers an entrepreneurial boom </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c4d3c4439cfe0aeee30b7e54c8a22e08/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c4d3c4439cfe0aeee30b7e54c8a22e08/</guid>
      <description>**The reason for this is because of the fact that you can&amp;rsquo;t get a good deal of the money you&amp;rsquo;re going to need for your own business.
When she woke up early in the morning, Maomao used to pick up her cell phone and shoot short videos of the eight cats in the house, and sent them to the &amp;ldquo;family cat foster&amp;rdquo; group she had formed one by one to report to the parents that the &amp;ldquo;master&amp;rdquo; was safe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A civilized city can&#39;t tolerate stray dogs, it&#39;s better to control the uncivilized dog owners than to keep arresting them. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cae2216eac8fa8411afa2b26a25e0146/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Do you hear me wailing? But I still have to cry out for my pain, bloodshed struggle, when bat after bat hit me on my body my head, do you know my blood tears themselves blurred my eyes, struggle, fear, blood dripping miserable barking tumbling try to stand up and fall down convulsions and gasp for breath mournful grief pale face, they howl, the whole world should listen to.
Recently, a city is now fighting and catching dogs again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A dog that is the sole pet of the wealthy &#34;queen of misery&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/947bcafdbe8ef533391d96c7ce9f1ce1/</guid>
      <description>123
There are a lot of rich people in the pet world, and there is a number one price tag. The $375 million German Shepherd, Gunther IV, and also Toby Rimes, the dog world&amp;rsquo;s celebrity poodle, are worth $12 million, one rich and the other impeccably beautiful.
WEALTH
Unlike them, today&amp;rsquo;s story is about a dog who is famous not only for his wealth, but also for his surprising way of being spoiled, for his owner who left a huge inheritance to his dog but not to his grandchildren, which is also the origin of his owner&amp;rsquo;s nickname &amp;ldquo;the queen of miserliness&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A guide dog with cancer fought to the death to return to its owner after dying (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f11d9812eb9b061bddf59afb0ea8c5f9/</guid>
      <description>Guide dog Kermit is pictured with his blind owner, David.
A dog is man&amp;rsquo;s friend. A recent story from the United Kingdom proves this old adage once again. An eight-year-old guide dog named Kermit, who was suffering from cancer, did his best at the end of his life, trying with every fiber of his being to get his blind owner, David, from Birmingham to his home in Huddersfield before collapsing and taking his last breath.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A husky learning martial arts, a great show of walking on the eaves, the dog on the side of the side of the dog were all dumbfounded! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e02fb4c7bc5b063c91aa9928a268a63c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e02fb4c7bc5b063c91aa9928a268a63c/</guid>
      <description> A husky learns martial arts, shows off his ability to walk on walls, and the dog on the other side is dumbfounded. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A king&#39;s duel of powerhouse cadres! Briefly discussing the Boundary Scout and the Explorer </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2513f73ce4fe7fc569ccbf68ca86b0c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2513f73ce4fe7fc569ccbf68ca86b0c2/</guid>
      <description>With the increase of national income, more and more young people choose to buy cars to go to work. This not only shows that the standard of living has improved, but also the birth of cars has brought a lot of convenience to people&amp;rsquo;s lives. However, today we will talk about two models suitable for young people to drive and see what makes these cars attractive to them!
Appearance:
   Indicator Name Spotters Probe     Length[mm] 4646 4589   Width[mm] 1843 1860   Height[mm] 1695 1660    Wheelbase[mm] 2725 2731*   Ground weight [kg] 1710 1750    Interior Decoration:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A monk saved more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats in 27 years: I was so busy that I didn&#39;t have time to pray. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</guid>
      <description>Originally I am the extraordinary gentleman.
About 50 kilometers from downtown Shanghai, Fengxian hides an old and dilapidated temple called the Annunciation Temple.
Unlike temples in the downtown area, there is no golden-hued palace, no solemn monks in robes, and no chanting of Buddhist scriptures.
But there is a monk in a red auto mechanic&amp;rsquo;s uniform who has rescued more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats.
This man is the abbot of the hospital, Zhixiang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A pack of African wild dogs drink from a river, a large hippo attacks, and the dogs withdraw. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2fc4a04d97cdd9a1942d1e85c0625783/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2fc4a04d97cdd9a1942d1e85c0625783/</guid>
      <description>The African wild dog is a very aggressive animal, although the wild dog is not very large and may not seem as big as our domestic dogs. However, the pack nature of the wild dog makes them one of the most important predators on the African savannah, and some people even consider them to be the third top predator in the African savannah besides lions and hyenas.
Wild dog packs are strictly disciplined, preying on animals several times their size through strength in numbers and teamwork.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A pack of wild dogs wanted to eat the crocodile meat and set a trap by pretending to drink the water, and the crocodile took the bait! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/13930e1dbe5ec6fa7a7c12526d0106b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/13930e1dbe5ec6fa7a7c12526d0106b3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of wild dogs wanted to eat the crocodile&amp;rsquo;s meat and set a trap by drinking the water, and the crocodile took the bait!
Animals living in the wild have to worry about food almost every day, and under such cruel conditions, they have also mastered some tricks, this day a group of wild dogs wanted to eat crocodile meat, and set a trap by drinking water, and the crocodile successfully took the bait!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A state builds an &#34;animal overpass&#34; to protect wildlife on the highway (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cf4421d707b2eed410e849d30c551de9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cf4421d707b2eed410e849d30c551de9/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 13:15:06 Source: Overseas.com
Report
Utah State Government&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Animal Crossover&amp;rdquo; (Social Media)
Overseas.com, November 28, 2011. According to CNN (CNN) local time on the 27th, the Utah state government has built a wildlife &amp;ldquo;overpass&amp;rdquo; in order to protect local wildlife and reduce the risk of wildlife encountering traffic accidents on the highway. The bridge has reportedly seen initial results in a short period of time.
Wildlife crossing an overpass (video clip)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A stray cat climbs 25 floors every day and knocks on doors asking for food, how does he do it? How to remember the floors </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/35da6127cb17fedb905e6174f298bd88/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/35da6127cb17fedb905e6174f298bd88/</guid>
      <description>For example, a domestic cat will become a stray cat after being abandoned, and a stray cat will gradually become a domestic cat after being adopted, so in everyone&amp;rsquo;s subconscious mind, stray cats and domestic cats are the same kind of animal.
But as I understand more and more about stray cats, I find that stray cats and domestic cats are simply 2 different kinds of animals.
Because stray cats are so smart, they sometimes do things that would surprise a human being like me, but recently, I was shocked by a stray cat, and it happened to me.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A very spoiled brown husky that has traveled to all 48 states! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6aca539b52f168847abf2bd241a13749/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6aca539b52f168847abf2bd241a13749/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 09:46:40 Source: MiB Photography Community
Report
This distinctive husky made its debut on the social world section of the social media site Instagram. Unlike other huskies, this dog has a husky body and sapphire blue eyes, but his hair is brown. It&amp;rsquo;s very new, and it looks like a gray tree trunk.
&amp;ldquo;The Quoi Husky is actually not exactly brown in appearance. It still has a small white spot on its chest, and how many huskies do you see that look like it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A year ago, a 54-year-old man died of rabies in Zhejiang province after being bitten by a wild dog without vaccination. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ede33dee64408423dcf102c0b85969df/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ede33dee64408423dcf102c0b85969df/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the Emergency Department of the First Affiliated Hospital of Zhejiang University School of Medicine treated a 54-year-old Tiantai man who died of rabies one year after he was bitten by a wild dog and spent a week in the EICU (Emergency Intensive Care Unit). The lesson of blood and tears is heartbreaking.
&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s been almost a year since I was bitten by a wild dog, how can a person just lose it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Adorable! Zoo wildlife health check for winter </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e326bb20f5996bfbc4272420a917905e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e326bb20f5996bfbc4272420a917905e/</guid>
      <description>On November 26, Shandong Qingdao Forest Wildlife World conducted a physical examination of kangaroos, ring-tailed lemurs, lion cubs, golden pythons and other primate, carnivorous, herbivorous, omnivorous and two-reptile wildlife. A veterinarian is giving a physical examination to a kangaroo.
According to the introduction, as the temperature gets cooler after winter, small animals are more prone to gastrointestinal diseases, colds and other symptoms. Qingdao Forest Wildlife World carries out physical examinations and preventive measures for wild animals through physical observation, temperature measurement by auscultation, blood sampling, ultrasound testing, vaccination, feeding deworming drugs and other methods to ensure the health and safety of wild animals in winter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> African Wild Dogs Exercise &#34;Voting Rights&#34; by Sneezing Ideographs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0b1da1f091d84aaeb045c4150df50214/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0b1da1f091d84aaeb045c4150df50214/</guid>
      <description>An international research team has found that African wild dogs exercise a &amp;ldquo;vote&amp;rdquo; by sneezing to determine whether the pack will hunt.
The endangered animal takes a break from hunting and then gathers for a &amp;ldquo;social gathering&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;negotiate&amp;rdquo; whether or not to launch a new hunt collectively.
The researchers observed and analyzed 68 &amp;ldquo;social gatherings&amp;rdquo; of five groups of African wild dogs in Botswana&amp;rsquo;s Okavango Delta and found that &amp;ldquo;sneezing plays a role in voting, and the more sneezes, the more likely the dogs are to set out on a hunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> African wild dog eats two young lions alive, gutting them, leaving only an empty shell. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/64d0f60e9523a1904fb9c51d6a503803/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/64d0f60e9523a1904fb9c51d6a503803/</guid>
      <description>2017-10-12 01:13:42 Source: Games Without Borders
Report
In the grasslands, a group of hyenas were sharing their catch, and the hungry lions couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but try to grab it.
The hyenas were not vegetarians and would not allow the lions to take their food, so a great battle began.
The lion was so enraged that he had to eat the food that he grew up and fought the hyenas, but could the hyenas really win?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> After a new play in Hsu Jiaqi, he is still a cute pet idol! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/750de3ddb3292138783ccc450c84bea8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/750de3ddb3292138783ccc450c84bea8/</guid>
      <description>Xu Jiaqi is a very good girl, thanks to her participation in &amp;ldquo;Youth With You&amp;rdquo;, her light can not be completely hidden. The third place came out good, and now the resources are getting better and better, it turns out that she is a multi-talented girl with high face value and her popularity is very high, after participating in the program, there was a wave of enthusiasm, she got a lot of resources, although she is not a C-star, but her resources are much better than the first and second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alibaba&#39;s employee doubling appraisal categorized as a &#34;wild dog hound.&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/145228cb230ad3d3ab74c940d1e5b3f2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/145228cb230ad3d3ab74c940d1e5b3f2/</guid>
      <description>Reporter Wei Heping
The rapid expansion of employees often leads to a dilution of corporate culture, a problem that Alibaba Group, amid rumors of an IPO, has had to face.
&amp;ldquo;Alibaba employees have grown from 4,000 last year to 6,000 today, and according to the company&amp;rsquo;s human resources plan, it will reach 8,000 by the end of the year.&amp;rdquo; Deng Kangming, senior vice president of Alibaba Group, revealed in an interview with reporters a few days ago that after the rapid growth of the number of employees in the past few years, the number of employees in the group will double this year compared to last year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Alternative dog &#34;laughs&#34; at corgi short legs, imitates its walking posture, laughing the netizens! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f98d90fdfacd37e554e0b5569531174b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f98d90fdfacd37e554e0b5569531174b/</guid>
      <description>Dog mimicry, sometimes super funny. This time the main character is a corgi, which is famous among many dogs for its &amp;ldquo;short legs&amp;rdquo; and is always being compared to other dogs in terms of height. One corgi was recently laughed at by his friends when an alternative dog lowered his body to mimic the way he walked, which made netizens laugh.
The two are good friends, but the mischievous Dustin always makes fun of Tayto, who has short limbs, and from time to time he will lower himself down to imitate Tayto&amp;rsquo;s walking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> American Movie Emperor Beagle &#34;shot&#34; plays dead and will add his own drama </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5e907b10aecd92d0eed6e74c87b0979b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5e907b10aecd92d0eed6e74c87b0979b/</guid>
      <description>The Daily Mail published an anecdote on Feb. 13 about a dog owner in Las Vegas, Nevada, who aimed a gun at his Beagle and fired two shots.
__
In the video, the hostess poses with her thumb, index finger and middle finger in the shape of a gun and dubs herself &amp;ldquo;Bang! Bang!&amp;rdquo; The dog is very cooperative and emotional, howling twice as the owner &amp;ldquo;shoots,&amp;rdquo; as if imitating the sad scene in a gunfight movie where the main character is shot and about to collapse, and then collapses on the mat next to her.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> An old man who adopted a pet dog as a child and immediately killed it for meat was sentenced to prison. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/adef3f9d4052436fa7c047f6a3d7118a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/adef3f9d4052436fa7c047f6a3d7118a/</guid>
      <description>Incheon District Court
A 74-year-old Korean man, Park Mok, adopted two dogs and promised the owners that he would &amp;ldquo;treat them like children,&amp;rdquo; but unexpectedly he killed the dogs less than two hours after adopting them and made them into a &amp;ldquo;tonic soup. On November 23, the Incheon District Court sentenced Mr. Park to six months in prison for &amp;ldquo;fraud&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;violating animal protection laws. However, this did not quell the public&amp;rsquo;s anger, as more than 62,000 Korean netizens have so far petitioned on the Cheong Wa Dae petition board, demanding that he be severely punished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Animal Ferocity: African Wild Dog Kills 16 Sheep and Deer in Night Attack </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/daaa7d375dab41aa272e42c55298640d/</guid>
      <description>Last Saturday night, a pack of African wild dogs broke out of their enclosure at the West Midlands Safari Park and killed 16 sheep and deer at the zoo, including 10 Persian fallow deer and six barbarian sheep, according to the British newspaper The Sun.
When the keepers arrived at the scene of the incident, they were shocked by the bloodshed that had taken place.
A door separating the dogs from the other animals was blown down by high winds due to the storm of the century, and then 12 of the dogs ran into the living quarters of the other animals and carried out a horrific, dog-less slaughter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Anti-sexual frigidity: glamour and desire under maximalism </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ad778f17515dec28454af0ec0ab86927/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ad778f17515dec28454af0ec0ab86927/</guid>
      <description>Original Dobby Aesthetics
A few years ago, minimalism was on the rise, and I followed this trend and started to break away.
But by now, I&amp;rsquo;ve thrown away quite a few things, moved more and more things at a time, bought more and more, and have an unabated desire to shop.
Now it seems that minimalist living is not for everyone, and we should be cautious about following this trend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5fcb6d38a0040125ed67ca6ae22ce9d2/</guid>
      <description>Are Corgis easy to raise? What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi?
Time：2018-06-07 19:36 Source：Today&amp;rsquo;s headlines Editor-in-charge：FoDuo
**The first thing I noticed is that there are a lot of different ways to get rid of a corgi. What do you know about the personality traits of a Corgi? Corgis are small, like a quiet environment, and never bark, making them perfect for families. So is a Corgi easy to keep?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a3c67db4378e87303481be99b90b789d/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:05:50 Source: Xiang Yang Psychology
Report
Are pugs and bulldogs the same breed? This article gives you an answer.
Nowadays, many people have pugs and pit bulls because they have wrinkled faces and often look at people with innocent eyes, which makes them feel especially pitiful. In fact, pugs and bulls are two different kinds of pets, they are not the same species, but they are very similar in many aspects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> As we all know, the meow is a lively and energetic animal. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e13241002554c80c81898ab179f95f55/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e13241002554c80c81898ab179f95f55/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 22:58:30 Source: Litterbug
Report
With the first rays of the morning sun
Meow stretches its back
After making your bed and washing up, you&amp;rsquo;re ready to work for a living!
The meow is really a lively and energetic creature!
**No way! ***
The face is filled with anticipation for the job.
And the love of work
Just one year later
Why work?
Why do I always have to go to work?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Australian Wild Dogs Euthanized After Attacking Boy, Injuring Several People </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f7389de70a976f2d4d87a1af26674b39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f7389de70a976f2d4d87a1af26674b39/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BMI New Poem: &#34;One Hundred Sheep Flying Over My Head </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/89d3ff21c1b9cc1ff61a2dabff05eff8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/89d3ff21c1b9cc1ff61a2dabff05eff8/</guid>
      <description>BMI New Poem: &amp;ldquo;One Hundred Sheep Flying Over My Head
2020-11-27 17:07:45 Source: Nextpoint.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beagle breeders should be cautious, these &#34;6 major injuries&#34;, I believe only people who have owned a Beagle understand! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d6113fbb7302329d085fc8a1d35867ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d6113fbb7302329d085fc8a1d35867ea/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-20 11:55:22 Source: Mommy&amp;rsquo;s Classroom
Report
The Beagle, also known as the Miguelu Hound, is an excellent working dog and family companion, with an easy-going, gentle and well-behaved personality that is loved by many families. However, the Beagle should be kept with caution, because it has a lot of disadvantages, and you will feel very annoyed if you keep it, so let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at it.
Harm 1. Easily disturbing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Canine infestation control becomes a new test of urban civilization </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</guid>
      <description>The number of stray dogs without an owner is soaring, and the dog problem is poking at the city management &amp;ldquo;pain points &amp;ldquo;.
Dog control becomes the new test of urban civilization.
The reason why stray dogs have gradually become a &amp;ldquo;problem&amp;rdquo; in many cities is that owners have abandoned their dogs, lost their pets, and the uncontrolled breeding of stray dogs.
● As the number of urban pet dogs increases, the social problems caused by dog ownership are becoming more and more serious, and many deep-seated problems have not been fully exposed, nor have they attracted the attention of the legislative, law enforcement and epidemic prevention departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Carex Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/26d374289a6c931bb2db4bf412412bcc/</guid>
      <description>Host: Ya&amp;rsquo;an Daily Media Group News Hotline: 0835-2222226 Advertising Hotline: 0835-2243318
##
Kerris Dog Teething Bars - How to Raise a Well-Behaved Dog! ##
Time： 2020-11-27 11:14:35 Source：Northwestern.com
The most important food for dogs can be said to be non-dog food, that comes in second is snacks, some people think snacks are unnecessary, but we humans also like to eat when nothing spicy chips and other snacks, not to mention the dog it?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat Owner Sues for Nearly $9,000 in Damages for Accidental Death of Petting Cat </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/135bc6ab1d06907b1bb84a7973881d28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/135bc6ab1d06907b1bb84a7973881d28/</guid>
      <description>After being introduced by a friend, Mr. Wang sent his male cat to Mr. Liu to get a cat, and after just one month, the cat was injured, lost his hair, and eventually died after being treated by the veterinary hospital. Beichen- Beijing headline reporter learned on November 25, Beijing Xicheng Court finally ruled that Liu Mou compensate Wang Mou 8886 yuan.
In May 2018, Wang was introduced by a friend to a short male cat that was sent to Liu&amp;rsquo;s home, which was healthy and free of any disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat addiction, cat ownership &#34;causes poverty&#34;? The &#34;cat economy&#34; is being boosted by young people. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5bab22e9f39b975c482dab2e7b60b71c/</guid>
      <description>Cats are cute and can be carried around. Nowadays, cats as pets are more and more sought after by young people, cat breeding, go to the cat coffee jerk cat, &amp;ldquo;cloud sucking cat&amp;rdquo; has become the daily life of many young people.
For cats, the wallet is &amp;ldquo;thin &amp;ldquo;.
&amp;ldquo;I may not eat, but the cat must eat well.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Hard earned living for cat owners.&amp;rdquo; &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; &amp;ldquo;Cat Slave&amp;rdquo; They use all kinds of witty passages to ridicule the daily life of cat ownership.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat enjoys your groping, just like you? Wrong, wrong, wrong! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f43d5ed6862abcb918cc1c5be540b7fe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f43d5ed6862abcb918cc1c5be540b7fe/</guid>
      <description>Only by getting to know it can you make it like you more.
Careful shovelers may find that, for a cat that is not yet familiar or bad-tempered, or when the owner is not in a good mood, touching its belly, paws, tail and other sensitive parts of the cat is likely to result in a beating.
Cat: Don&amp;rsquo;t touch me!
But touching the top of the head and chin usually does not attract &amp;ldquo;blood&amp;rdquo;, as if the top of the head and chin is the &amp;ldquo;immunity zone&amp;rdquo; of the shovel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cat mummies, with live kittens? [UNK] Why a cat sacrifice? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b5ecb786a8f99a61bd37b51525f5c00b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b5ecb786a8f99a61bd37b51525f5c00b/</guid>
      <description>This blogger looks like a cat lover. However, cat mummies do have kittens, and many of them are kittens. Many of the cat mummies unearthed in Saqqara today are CT scanned to reveal the remains of a whole cat inside. (Ugh, that&amp;rsquo;s a sad answer) Not all cat mummies contain a cat. Sometimes there are only a few bones, and sometimes there is no cat at all, but cloth, resin, and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cats are fierce too! A 4-ton wild elephant in Thailand broke into a residential area to steal food and was scared off by the roar of a pet cat. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/de8e6a684866d91f0abb180c10909e5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/de8e6a684866d91f0abb180c10909e5a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 21:35:04 Source: Six Dimensions Nature
Report
In the food chain, herbivores have an instinctive fear of carnivores. In general, herbivores will choose to hide when they encounter carnivores. The wild elephant is dozens of times the size of a pet cat, so is the pet cat too fierce, or is the wild elephant too alert?
Description: The elephant is a wild male elephant. The elephant is also quite famous in the area, because at night, this elephant will go around breaking into people&amp;rsquo;s homes, looking for food, the local residents can not do anything, because wild elephants are protected animals, can only notify the relevant authorities, to drive it into the jungle again, but can not harm the elephant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cats with a short life span often have these six characteristics. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d943802703da75e39a4d72cdfe12aab/</guid>
      <description>A cat&amp;rsquo;s lifespan depends on many factors, but they all manifest themselves physically. Generally, cats with short life span tend to have these 6 characteristics, hopefully your cat will have none of them.
 Overweight  In both humans and cats, obesity can lead to many diseases. For example, diabetes, heart disease and other problems.
How can you tell if your cat is overweight? You can touch your cat near the chest with your hand, and if you can&amp;rsquo;t feel the ribs, then it can be said to be obese.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cibo: A dog food that shovelers can&#39;t miss! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a58c8cd3ebcd7e194a88027ff74ab5c2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a58c8cd3ebcd7e194a88027ff74ab5c2/</guid>
      <description>As one of the most popular dog food brands, Xibao&amp;rsquo;s strategic layout and development path has attracted a lot of attention since it has been ranked among the top selling dog food brands. In the Internet era, social media, such as live broadcast, short video, public, etc., has become a new development field for the brand. With the innovation and exploration of online channel operation, Cibo breaks the inherent mode of dog food sales, making consumers not only customers, but also friends, and becoming a group of warm-hearted family who love pets and life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> City Forestry Bureau Jointly Launches Wildlife Protection Publicity Campaign (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/21e9f3c66f695bcb797853305e76d1af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/21e9f3c66f695bcb797853305e76d1af/</guid>
      <description>Dajiang.com/Fuzhou Headlines Client News Correspondent Xiaofen Huang and Min Li Report: In order to further enhance the awareness of wildlife protection, on November 26th, the Fuzhou Forestry Bureau joined the Linchuan District Forestry Bureau, the City Public Security Bureau Forest Public Security Branch and the City Wildlife Protection Association to launch a wildlife protection campaign with the theme of &amp;ldquo;Protecting wildlife according to the law and building a green ecological home&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cixi warned the Eight Allied Forces: I don&#39;t care if I occupy the land, I can&#39;t see the killings, but I won&#39;t do it! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/83cad9d5829da07bc327895f8e5a1c39/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/83cad9d5829da07bc327895f8e5a1c39/</guid>
      <description>Directed by.
I once read an interesting article about what would happen if Empress Lu, Wu Zetian, and Cixi fought each other in court. The general opinion is that Empress Lu = Wu Zetian &amp;gt; Ci Xi, these three people are not in a dynasty can not be compared, but from these three people&amp;rsquo;s diplomacy and internal affairs, let alone Lu and Wu Zetian&amp;rsquo;s fighting power that is stronger, just put Ci Xi in the end, I believe there will not be many people will raise objections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Concentrated inspection of pet sale business areas and residential communities. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8dd2d063cc71cb7661142a12a8a1878/</guid>
      <description>The new revision of the &amp;ldquo;Hohhot City Dog Management Regulations&amp;rdquo; from October 1 this year was formally implemented, the new rules clearly in the key dog management area, each household is limited to one dog, and may not keep a spirited dog and aggressive large dogs. In order to comprehensively promote the management of dog improvement work, strengthen the source control of large dogs and spirited dogs, over the past few days, the city public security bureau city management detachment joint Huimin District Public Security Branch of the Huanhe Street Police Station and Saihan District Public Security Branch of the University East Road Police Station, the pet sales business concentrated areas and residential neighborhoods to carry out a centralized inspection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Corgi fall death follow-up: How was the Corgi killed? What&#39;s the follow-up? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/821f177b5e550c0033fa9a3e7fb7a7a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/821f177b5e550c0033fa9a3e7fb7a7a4/</guid>
      <description>threatens the safety and privacy of others.
Woman who fell dog and dog owner both detained.
The five people in the case are all being dealt with for violations committed via the Internet, the police said, and the corgi fall fatalities show once again that the Internet is an illegal place.
Li was administratively detained for distributing He&amp;rsquo;s cell phone number and other private information via Weibo.
The dog&amp;rsquo;s owner, Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Corgi is skinned and hung from a tree in a pile of meat. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c70ce53b7e024906658c07c4a1c92b19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c70ce53b7e024906658c07c4a1c92b19/</guid>
      <description>Original title: dog lost 2 hours later actually was skinned by people do not know how to say to the 2-year-old son &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
Photo of lost corgi and young owner.
The owner recognized the TOTO by the head pattern.
On the morning of April 6th, Ms. Li of Chengdu lost her Corgi that she had raised for two years. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m going to be able to do that, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure if I&amp;rsquo;m going to be able to do that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Covering the cat &#34;eat, drink, shit, sleep&#34; pet smart home is a gimmick or a windfall? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f1dbc650d7323180d35d23600f9ce43d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f1dbc650d7323180d35d23600f9ce43d/</guid>
      <description>Covering the cat&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;eat, drink, shit, sleep&amp;rdquo; is the pet smart home a gimmick or a windfall? ##
** Original title:**
The sensor detects when your pet is in the automatic cat toilet and flushes it automatically.
File photo
During the May Day holiday this year, Xiaosu left her two cats at home in Beijing. &amp;ldquo;The house is monitored by a &amp;lsquo;pet camera&amp;rsquo; in real time, as well as an automatic feeder and water dispenser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dog mom gives birth to puppy, &#34;sleeping posture&#34; adorable master, can&#39;t put it down! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f7bc0a84f0d56961f563e52b1c9c89b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f7bc0a84f0d56961f563e52b1c9c89b7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 07:08:48 Source: Zhong Xin Chat Entertainment
Report
We are all irresistible to furry animals, they are very comfortable to touch, and they often give out some interaction to make their own defenseless, especially for girls, see these cute little guys are even more like, see the cute little life even lost soul, can&amp;rsquo;t wait to hide the cute little ones into their own arms.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been very fond of dogs since I was a child, and they grew up with me, and they would always stick to me no matter what, and they would accompany me wherever I went.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dog owners must understand these six points </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c82b03310e54e5091f2648e0ea696348/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s important to be prepared before getting a dog!
**1, do not think that raising a dog is an easy thing **, although the dog can bring you a lot of happy time, but if you will not raise a dog, it will certainly bring you a lot of trouble.
2, before raising a dog, first consider their current living situation, whether the dog can provide a stable living environment, whether you have the economic strength to raise a dog, many college students on a whim, in the dormitory dog, in fact, this is very wrong, as long as you graduate, there is a certain economic strength, and a stable place to live and then proceed to consider raising a little guy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs and cats playing around accidentally catch fire! The next scene is a stunner! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/407cd1a0fff74ddbdd495bb84226ad5d/</guid>
      <description>Dogs and cats playing around and getting burned! The next scene is a stunner! 2020-11-26 17:00 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
Recently, a surveillance video caused a lot of discussion among netizens.
In the video, dogs and cats are playing in the living room.
The cat&amp;rsquo;s tail accidentally caught on an open flame on the table.
The dog runs away immediately at the sight of it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dogs know people from dogs, and shovelers&#39; personalities from dog ownership! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8c157714e22f3a8a29da13cbd6ceb17/</guid>
      <description>There is a saying that &amp;ldquo;a dog knows a man by his dog&amp;rdquo;, and from the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior, you can probably know the character of the spade. We all know that the dog&amp;rsquo;s behavior is directly related to the shovel, if the shovel is kinder, then the dog will not be fierce. If the shovel is more fierce, then the dog will not be kind. So let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the character of the shovelers who have several kinds of dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Don&#39;t let your dog get into the act when you&#39;re watching swans! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ab04f8d0e12c2c466549f38c0d4e2da1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ab04f8d0e12c2c466549f38c0d4e2da1/</guid>
      <description>On November 21, visitors bring their dogs to watch white swans in the White Swan Viewing Area of the Sanmenxia Yellow River Wetland. Currently, white swans in the Sanmenxia Yellow River Wetland are in peak season, which attracts a large number of tourists. Occasionally, we see some tourists bring their dogs to watch the white swans up close, which can scare the swans if they are not careful. We hope that visitors will be civilized and work together to create a quiet and good wintering environment for the white swans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Double Cut Pug Tour Download </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1353168770b31a25c7d4fcfd02242635/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1353168770b31a25c7d4fcfd02242635/</guid>
      <description>This game uses the classic horizontal adventure gameplay, in which players control a cute and nerdy pug dog, this dog can have a magical ability, players need to use this ability to complete a variety of challenges, rich and varied levels will surely bring players a richer experience.
&amp;ldquo;Double Cut Pug&amp;rdquo; Game Advantages.  Find purple coins hidden in the level and use them to unlock more items.
 unlock different props in the game, which can help players pass levels easily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Douluo Continent: Tang San Protects Little Dance, Eight Spider Spear Broken Again, Body Wounds Shockingly Sharp </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e5ac5b38a2406955c4d0496ba9a9c7b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e5ac5b38a2406955c4d0496ba9a9c7b7/</guid>
      <description>Tang San and Xiaodiao have been apart for five years, and during these five years Tang San has missed Xiaodiao every moment. It could be said that being able to protect Little Dance was Tang San&amp;rsquo;s greatest motivation. He followed Tang Hao&amp;rsquo;s training, braved the Killing Capital, and did everything to become stronger. Becoming stronger myself wasn&amp;rsquo;t so much a desire for power, it was just a desire to have the ability to protect you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> English Dachshunds sold for nearly $17,000 during the epidemic, an 89% increase </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c70e5b50230b767f9531362ab929d1a1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c70e5b50230b767f9531362ab929d1a1/</guid>
      <description>** CCTV Finance (reporter Wang Yongxi)** A survey has found that the price of puppies from Britain&amp;rsquo;s most popular breed has reached record levels, according to the website of Sky News UK. According to the data, the average price of a Dachshund rose to £1,838 in June this year, up 89 percent from £973 in March. English and French bulldog prices have also risen sharply. A review of the past three years of advertising on some of Britain&amp;rsquo;s largest classified advertising sites shows that the prices of English pugs, dachshunds and poodles have never been higher.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Except for Corgi, these are all short-legged dogs! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/4bb5ea8a5098d27a8f7aeb45d8d89ddb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/4bb5ea8a5098d27a8f7aeb45d8d89ddb/</guid>
      <description>When you think of short-legged dogs, the first thing that comes to mind is corgi dogs, whose most iconic parts are their short legs and butt! Their short legs and chubby body make them jumpy and happy as they walk. **The Corgi was originally a cattle dog, its name &amp;ldquo;Corgi&amp;rdquo; is Welsh for &amp;ldquo;corrci&amp;rdquo; petite. ** They are light as a feather and agile. Early on, they were used to herd cattle precisely because of their short legs, which prevented them from being kicked by cattle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fatou swims and drowns, but not all dogs can swim! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/63152259ffe5d9a7720f4480037106e8/</guid>
      <description>Now that the weather is getting hotter and hotter, many shovelers will take their dogs to the pet store or outdoors to go swimming in order to help them with the heat.
However, do you know that it is actually very dangerous to take your dog swimming at will?
Before that, a dog owner thought that his dog had hip problems, so he brought him to the pet swimming pool to swim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fewer than 300 of the Queen&#39;s favorite corgis in the UK make the vulnerable list </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/dfe836e8b2a1e99312d40f84881a9efe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/dfe836e8b2a1e99312d40f84881a9efe/</guid>
      <description>Click on the image to go to the next page
Corgi Image from the Internet
**Pembrokeshire Corgi, the Queen&amp;rsquo;s favorite dog, is the most popular dog in the UK, according to the media. The Corgi, now threatened with extinction, has been added to the British Kennel Club&amp;rsquo;s list of the most vulnerable breeds, the Singaporean newspaper Lianhe Zaobao reported on Feb. 9, citing the Sing Tao Daily website.
Singapore&amp;rsquo;s Lianhe Zaobao reported on Feb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Finished! Shiba Inu mimics its owner sitting and watching a video: this little short leg  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3b5d431c32bc97be646bc8145dcff7c1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3b5d431c32bc97be646bc8145dcff7c1/</guid>
      <description>Pets can get a little carried away with their owners. Recently, a Shiba Inu who likes to sit and watch videos has gone viral on the Internet.
According to the introduction, the Shiba Inu, named Chiko, shocked everyone by indulging in watching videos at only 7 months old, while sitting upright on a bench.
According to his owner, Olesia Kuzmychova said that Chiko started watching TV with Olesia the first day she got home from Olesia&amp;rsquo;s house, and when Olesia went out, Olesia would also watch the TV so that Chiko could watch the show to her heart&amp;rsquo;s content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> First time owning a cat? Teach you 3 points to choose reliable cat food </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2a261a7f1094a8b3798533061239ed5a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2a261a7f1094a8b3798533061239ed5a/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, pets have gradually become an indispensable part of every home, and more and more people are paying attention to the nutritional health of their pets. However, the quality of the various products on the market varies, and novice shovelers are always worried that they will encounter mines and step on pits, not knowing how to choose the right cat food for their cat owners. You know, if you don&amp;rsquo;t choose the right cat food, your cat&amp;rsquo;s owner will not only suffer from various diseases, but also shorten his life expectancy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Five stray dogs actually gave up running when they were rounded up and chose to stay in place to guard their owner </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eabf0e44da9408438d4791a6372ce1fb/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 21:55:19 Source: Big Love Puppy Control
Report
Recently, there was a photo that sparked a lot of discussion on the net.
In Kajang, Malaysia, in order to control stray dogs, a dog catching team was sent to the street to catch stray dogs&amp;hellip;.
But unlike other stray dogs, which would run away as soon as they saw someone chasing them, five of them not only didn&amp;rsquo;t run away, but also surrounded a homeless man sleeping on the ground&amp;hellip;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Galactic Fighting 2: After 18 years, Justus reappears and Goss Future takes on the Rainbow Dragon! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3bfcb518c7ac4db16dedf2af80cc5c54/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3bfcb518c7ac4db16dedf2af80cc5c54/</guid>
      <description>Galactic Combat 2 has officially aired, and in this story we see the appearance of the mysterious Tartarus. Of course, in the first story, Tartarus did nothing more than praise the Land of Light, and then disappeared again. The most miserable character in the first story is Max, who is not very lucky and encounters the Slann, the fiercest beast Herberos, the serpent Morgul, and Gordis.
In the preview of the second story, Gothic Ultraman and Justus Ultraman finally appear, a pair that hasn&amp;rsquo;t been on stage together since they fought side by side in the theatrical version of Gothic Ultraman.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Global Neocrown Outbreak Affects Wildlife Conservation </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c05644cffe85e45e22fe4c2501a7eba6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c05644cffe85e45e22fe4c2501a7eba6/</guid>
      <description>Dan Zhao
According to the Washington Post, wildlife refuges and ecotourism around the world are facing new threats as a result of the new crown epidemic, and the impact on wildlife and people is being felt and is expected to be far-reaching.
As a result of epidemic prevention and control measures such as border closures and visa restrictions in many countries, most of the world&amp;rsquo;s tourist destinations have been forced to shut down, including national parks, game reserves and wildlife sanctuaries in Africa, Asia and elsewhere, resulting in a significant decline in wildlife tourism revenues and a cutback in funding for programs that support wildlife conservation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Guangdong Cracks Down on Illegal Wildlife Markets and Trade, Has Dealt with 3,045 People </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7a723606a239f75c8d2631e6948c87d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7a723606a239f75c8d2631e6948c87d8/</guid>
      <description>Guangdong Crackdown on Illegal Wildlife Markets and Trade, Dealt with 3,045 People
JinYang.com by Hou MengFei 2020-11-26
As of November 6, more than 300,000 business establishments such as markets, restaurants and hotels have been cleaned up and fixed, and 2,085 cases involving wild animals have been established and 3,045 people have been dealt with.
Yangcheng Evening News Media reporter Hou Mengfei
On November 26, the reporter learned from the 26th meeting of the Standing Committee of the Provincial People&amp;rsquo;s Congress that: at present, Guangdong has continuously issued a number of policies and documents to ban all wildlife, and crack down on illegal wildlife markets and trade practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Guangxi Yulin weighs more than 100 kg &#34;net red&#34; dog, usually in addition to sleeping is to eat! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f291934cdfc2f3cbc7d672b1831638b7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 11:52:03 Source: xiaogu lookday
Report
A mention of Guangxi Yulin, you will think of what, will not think of &amp;ldquo;winter solstice fish raw summer solstice dog&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Yulin Lychee Dog Meat Festival&amp;rdquo; and so on. In fact, not everyone imagine that way, the dog meat festival just before the process down, so there has always been this festival, this festival, not what dogs are killed. Today (November 28), the editor to take a look at the county of Yulin, Guangxi Rong County, a net red dog, it lives for more than a decade, weighing more than 100 pounds, usually in addition to sleep is to eat, very prosperous.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gulou&#39;s First Case of Criminal Attached Civil Lawsuit for Wildlife Protection Opens in Court </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d016cf3a513b356fc22aecbfdb832ad5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d016cf3a513b356fc22aecbfdb832ad5/</guid>
      <description>Fuzhou News Network, November 27th (Fuzhou Daily Reporter) (Lai, Zhichang) Recently, Gulou District, the first case of criminal wildlife protection incidental civil public interest litigation case in court. The Gulou District Procuratorate to illegal acquisition, sale of precious and endangered wildlife crime on the case of the defendant Lin Mou public prosecution.
It is understood that, in May this year, Lin Mou through the network channels to buy a &amp;ldquo;sapphire&amp;rdquo; spider, and in a website to publish information for sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HAVER DOG 2.[UNK] 4WD 4&#43;6 for all-terrain play </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3ff25d5394df4d19cb4e3d8d1c4106b5/</guid>
      <description>Recently, at the Guangzhou International Auto Show, Haval Dagoo &amp;ldquo;Chinese Garden Dog Edition&amp;rdquo; officially opened for pre-sale, which is the most cost-effective model among the Haval Dagoo 2.0T 4WD. As a target of &amp;ldquo;one more scale to pursue&amp;rdquo; by the high-end urban SUV enthusiasts, the Haval Dagoo 2.0T all-wheel drive model, once &amp;ldquo;out of the cage&amp;rdquo;, is armed with off-road performance comparable to that of SUVs of more than 300,000 joint ventures, making everyone very excited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Haven&#39;t you been to the &#34;Mecca&#34; of the world of dentistry? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e09fa32ff698cdf3962078f726c64c8c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e09fa32ff698cdf3962078f726c64c8c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 07:17:39 Source: Qingdao Trip
Report
On November 5, the thirteen dynasties ancient capital of Xi&amp;rsquo;an added a new business card - located in the Third Affiliated Hospital of Air Force Military Medical University, the International Dental Museum held a grand opening ceremony, open to the public free of charge. So, some people have questions, why a museum can be called Xi&amp;rsquo;an&amp;rsquo;s new business card? The following contents will answer your questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Haver Dawg prices plummet and miss out on next year! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5a580ed19e4b0709d9a5048272719618/</guid>
      <description>Promotion Time: 2020/11/27-2020/11/30
Recently, the Great Wall Motor Haval store of Beijing Jishun Zhongda International Trade Co., Ltd. gave a cash discount of up to 20,000 yuan for its Haval big dog models. This activity is a limited-time special promotion, limited time and limited places, first-come, first-served! 4S store brand-new commercial vehicles National United Guarantee store car store tickets! Any manufacturer-authorized regular 4S store in the country free of charge and after maintenance, the day of purchase, the company can issue all the vehicle procedures (invoice, certificate of conformity, consistency certificate, vehicle information table, three-bag card) national licensing, warm tips: We take into account foreign customers to Beijing to buy a car far away, (successful purchase) can reimburse the one-way trip to Beijing [train tickets, high-speed rail tickets, air tickets (limited to owners).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heartache! 5 stray dogs stay in place to protect homeless owners from escaping despite being rounded up! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/74c5bcbf0d0085237529444d7cfa93cd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/74c5bcbf0d0085237529444d7cfa93cd/</guid>
      <description>Dogs are man&amp;rsquo;s most loyal friend! Kajang City, Malaysia, on the 20th of this month, the implementation of &amp;ldquo;dog catching operation&amp;rdquo;, sent to catch the dog brigade to the street to catch stray dogs, but just when all the stray dogs see humans and run away, there were 5 stray dogs are not afraid of being caught, but around a sleeping on the ground, choosing to stay next to the owner to protect him from bullying, photos were taken and uploaded on the network, triggering hot discussion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heavy! African wild dogs cruelly gutted the anus and ate pregnant antelope alive, even more vile than hyenas! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6282206c75c5b70220dfc871ed938a8f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6282206c75c5b70220dfc871ed938a8f/</guid>
      <description>Xian Suyuan still brushes her teeth with salt, Chen Hua can&amp;rsquo;t help but feel disgusted, no wonder her mouth has a strange taste!
Jiu Mi Mama 1&amp;rsquo;30&amp;rdquo; Open App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hebei Forestry and Grass Bureau Issues Emergency Notice to Crack Down on Indiscriminate Hunting and Trafficking of Wildlife </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eff5864539a1b16d529b7bed89cf458d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eff5864539a1b16d529b7bed89cf458d/</guid>
      <description>Copyright and Disclaimer        Copyright and Disclaimer 1,All the works marked &amp;ldquo;Source: China Animal Husbandry Net&amp;rdquo; on this website belong to China Animal Husbandry Net, and may not be reproduced, excerpted or used in other ways without the authorization of this website. If the net has authorized the use of the works, it should be used within the scope of authorization, and indicate &amp;ldquo;Source: China Animal Husbandry Net&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heroic Military Dogs Save Special Forces in Distress, Awarded Top Animal Honors </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e82e91e4d8591dca8a3f37a4cc61b83f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e82e91e4d8591dca8a3f37a4cc61b83f/</guid>
      <description>Kuno, a Belgian Shepherd from the British Special Forces, was able to save a number of British Special Forces soldiers when his unit was caught in a grenade attack and machine gun fire, according to a Nov. 24 article in the British newspaper Metro.
Unfortunately, Kuno was shot in both of his hind legs, and had to have one of his paws removed and be fitted with a custom-made prosthetic leg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How about the food for dogs? The food brings exclusive care, let the companionship longer! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/4ef888492ad94396a93558f6dac5747c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/4ef888492ad94396a93558f6dac5747c/</guid>
      <description>How about the food for dogs? The food brings exclusive care, let the companionship longer!
2020-11-24 11:42:06 Source: Nextpoint.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How do I find a wild dog in Gangnam Park? Jiangnan Hundred Views Map of 4 Wild Dogs Location Coordinates Complete </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2adaa33fc4d7b323f2b6ec095934e412/</guid>
      <description>Where are the wild dogs in Gangnam Hundred Views? There are many things to collect in Jiangnan Hundred Scenes, in addition to treasure chests, keys, big hens and four wild dogs. The following is the location of the four wild dog Jiangnan Hundred Views map is introduced, has not yet found all of the wild dog partners to see it!
Where are the wild dogs in the Gangnam Parkview?
We can find three wild dogs in the maze, and one at the end of the fog, as shown in the picture below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How do you train a pug? Master a few of these essentials </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1bd9ab3d33f21b2d65b17a523127750e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1bd9ab3d33f21b2d65b17a523127750e/</guid>
      <description>**The most important thing to remember is that there are different ways to train a pug, and there are different times and methods to train a pug. This is a very important part of the process.
 The content of training a pug should be from simple to difficult, from behavioral awareness training to skill training. Parents can first train the pug to develop a regular diet, excretion and sleeping habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How many interesting languages do you know about cats? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/596a5f4ded4afc58ca12ef818c8117a2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/596a5f4ded4afc58ca12ef818c8117a2/</guid>
      <description>Interesting Facts about Cats
Cats have a unique language. For those who like to have cats as pets, there are some interesting cat facts that can help you understand your pet better. It&amp;rsquo;s also interesting.
Cats communicate through their tails.
Cats communicate with their tails. Noticing a cat&amp;rsquo;s tail usually tells you its mood, and you can act accordingly. Different tail positions have different meanings and intentions.
Dragging tail: This can mean that your pet is scared or threatened.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How quickly can I get my family pet to accept a newly adopted cat? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b372b498dbab3169f62f8dd2046ad267/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b372b498dbab3169f62f8dd2046ad267/</guid>
      <description>Sometimes, people can be addicted to having a pet, and in the early stages, they may just have a cat or a dog, but after a while, they feel that one pet is too lonely again, and at this time, they may think of having a second pet. However, many people have some concerns before getting a second pet, that is, there may be fights between the new pet and the aboriginal pet, especially if the second pet is a cat, after all, cats are still theoretically solitary animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How should pet owners take care of Corgi during the &#34;golden period&#34; of 3~6 months? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/4ebc1902fc55a0108126085e416ac33a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/4ebc1902fc55a0108126085e416ac33a/</guid>
      <description>Corgi dogs are 3 months old, which is equivalent to a 6-year-old child, their physical and mental development will change a lot at this stage, and 3 to 6 months is the golden period of Corgi, seize this stage, the dog is well behaved and beautiful, so how should pet owners take care of them at this stage?
1、Form the habit of feeding at regular intervals.
After 3 months of age, a Corgi&amp;rsquo;s digestive system is generally more complete.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to get a cat or a doggy animal? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/93c6466c4c2fd40b65209ea679dc431b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/93c6466c4c2fd40b65209ea679dc431b/</guid>
      <description>Inarihime Tenho no Saki game pets is every little friend will want to get, play the game little friend should know Kai maru this character, he really likes to go out and doubt to make friends, get all kinds of small animals, including cats and ducks as well as puppies and so on, so how do you get these small animals? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at it below!
Inarihime Tenho no Saki game pets is every little friend will want to get, play the game little friend should know Kai maru this character, he really likes to go out and doubt to make friends, get all kinds of small animals, including cats and ducks as well as puppies and so on, so how do you get these small animals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Huskies and golden retrievers grab snacks, but the ending is hilarious! Netizens: together! Together! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/937231f4ac98530a8fd0f2a1363e66d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/937231f4ac98530a8fd0f2a1363e66d3/</guid>
      <description>How can the exaggerated romance of an idol drama take place in the real world?
If the heroine accidentally falls down and jumps into the hero&amp;rsquo;s arms, the chances of the two of them kissing after they fall to the ground are&amp;hellip;0.000001%! It&amp;rsquo;s about 0.000001%. For those of you who have this kind of fantasy, just wait!
▲ However, such a ridiculous scenario happened to two pooch dogs!
I&amp;rsquo;m so embarrassed that I&amp;rsquo;m blushing and embarrassed that I&amp;rsquo;m watching it all over again!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</guid>
      <description>Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two?
Nature can be very cruel, and one must always be on the lookout for animals that might sneak up on you, as this competition is the difference between life and death. In the African grasslands, there are two types of animals, hyenas and wild African dogs, which are about the same size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas are &#34;evil and scary&#34;? Hyenas haven&#39;t bitten anyone in 200 years in small Esse town </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7acc2891cfe125d18f9020aa44b6c682/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7acc2891cfe125d18f9020aa44b6c682/</guid>
      <description>The city has a long history of peaceful coexistence with hyenas. Centuries ago, these animals attacked people, sometimes even biting the townspeople to death. Then people made holes in the walls and threw food scraps in the holes, so the hyenas started to eat the rest of the food and stopped attacking people. According to the Harar people, there has not been another hyena attack on humans for 200 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas attack a man in his home in Zimbabwe, leaving only the remains of his body in a brutal scene. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/686f2764a5793eacb508566cb4528e7c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/686f2764a5793eacb508566cb4528e7c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-23 17:03:02 Source: Financial Media Ticktock
Report
According to media reports on November 22nd, a tragic case occurred in Zimbabwe recently, a man was sleeping at home late at night, but was attacked by a pack of hyenas (liè) dogs, they tore the man into several pieces, the house was full of blood, can be described as gruesome, when people found, only the remains were left.
The victim, who was 46 years old, was out drinking with friends on the day of the attack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I recently had the pleasure of hosting two surrogate Beagles and tell you what I know about Beagles! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6214910b900eb421171daf61f7dc34af/</guid>
      <description>As people&amp;rsquo;s standard of living is getting better and better, the number of families with pet dogs is increasing, and lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeing postings/questions from people asking about Beagles. It just so happens that recently I have received two surrogate training Beagles here, and I&amp;rsquo;ll state in advance that I have no previous experience with breeding or training Beagles, and this is my first experience with them, so today I&amp;rsquo;m going to talk about what I know about Beagles!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I&#39;m the King of Beasts, but how come I&#39;ve been taken out by a cow? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ce8b38ca6fef49f1ee1afbf6cb58e5b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ce8b38ca6fef49f1ee1afbf6cb58e5b9/</guid>
      <description>Original Luo Xiaofeng Species Calendar
In our days when black and white TVs were just replacing color TVs, if a boy born in early May and a boy born in early August were talking to each other, guess what they would most likely say? Which of the two golden gladiators, Arudibar of Taurus or Aeolian of Leo, is more powerful? Gladiator Seiya was on the air at the time. From the animation, Leo Aurelia seems to have the edge, and look at this August-born boy&amp;rsquo;s slightly smug grin!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If our country sells the remote-controlled [UNK]-[UNK] to Thailand, isn&#39;t it the same as showing it directly to the United States? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a5f3233c24578e4c532105e3670601b6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a5f3233c24578e4c532105e3670601b6/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 17:04:31 Source: Wild Carrot Yo
Report
In the field of infantry fighting vehicles, we started a little later, the earliest to learn from the Soviet Union, which is no surprise, in fact, today we see a lot of equipment platform, at the beginning is to learn from the Soviet Union, the big brother, naturally, will learn more, after all, we were poor. The VN-1C mentioned in the title is a performance of China&amp;rsquo;s northern industrial production of a relatively good infantry fighting vehicle, the most interesting feature is that its turret for unmanned operation, that is, the so-called remote control operation can be achieved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you even hold the cat in the wrong position, it&#39;s no wonder the cat likes you! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e54dcc50554b6b7aabe217a333404c21/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e54dcc50554b6b7aabe217a333404c21/</guid>
      <description>Some owners complain that their cats are not allowed to be kissed or hugged, as if they have a white wolf. Have you ever thought that if you even hold your cat in the wrong position, the cat will feel uncomfortable and like you? Today we&amp;rsquo;re going to take a look at the common ways to hold a cat wrong!
Common Errors in Cat Holding
 Carry-On  Some cats are heavier than others, and it is still a bit hard to hold them with one hand, so some owners will choose to carry them on their shoulders, which is very effortless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> If you&#39;re looking for a job, what else can your silly dog do but be cute? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/dcc3b937c307d3adad9ea7b78b9dec5b/</guid>
      <description>Original: SME SME Technology Story
The physical differences in modern pet dogs are enormous. However, taxonomically, dogs and wolves all over the world belong to the same species. They are both capable of producing fertile offspring, whether in artificial or natural conditions.
But domestic dogs have made the right choice in abandoning wolfdogs. Today, there are only a few hundred thousand gray wolves in the wild, but domestic dogs are all over the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Iguana: Joo Ji-hoon is just a little boy in front of Kim Hye-soo. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e7e3855c25ae0c80aea8f6ba24571889/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e7e3855c25ae0c80aea8f6ba24571889/</guid>
      <description>The new album, &amp;lsquo;Hyena&amp;rsquo; (also known as &amp;lsquo;Hyena&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Rich Debaters&amp;rsquo;), is a new movie by Jang Tae Yoo from &amp;lsquo;You from the Stars&amp;rsquo; and features Kim Hye Soo and Joo Ji Hoon as the main characters. In this movie, she will be playing the lead role of a man who is a woman of the same gender, and she will be playing a woman who is a woman of the same gender.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In Africa, Chinese Volunteers &#34;Bring Your Own Food&#34; to Fight Poaching </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c0aeb8c17804592cb266c87d114225cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c0aeb8c17804592cb266c87d114225cb/</guid>
      <description>Original title：If lions and elephants could talk, I would express my gratitude to them &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
Chinese Volunteers &amp;ldquo;Bring Your Own Food&amp;rdquo; to Fight Poaching in Africa
On June 15, Chinese volunteers and Manapus National Park Director Ah Liang pushed the power delta wing out of the hangar.
Chinese volunteers (from left to right) Wang Ke, Zhang Guangrui, Wang Yilin, Yu Yang and Liang Jiajun at the campground on June 15. All photos by Xinhua News Agency reporter Chen Yaqin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Intensive training to overcome the natural fear of heights, customized harnesses to ensure air stability, and skydiving &#34;canine soldiers&#34; are made this way! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5fa0430c14314e7ff7b647b38fcfd805/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5fa0430c14314e7ff7b647b38fcfd805/</guid>
      <description>Hi there!
Tinker Bell in training
Tinker Bell practicing airborne posture with the paratroopers.
The first time I was in the city, I was in the city, and the second time I was in the city.
Have you ever seen a military dog that can jump out of a plane? Airborne troops in Kaifeng a brigade&amp;rsquo;s dog Dingdong, recently in the airborne training with airborne troops from 1200 meters altitude parachute success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is pre-sale of real estate the same as fraud? The People&#39;s Daily speaks out and the developers are not sitting still! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/50e9bc3394a44cced3ef9d40b3c6752f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/50e9bc3394a44cced3ef9d40b3c6752f/</guid>
      <description>Now that winter is approaching everywhere, with snow already falling in some areas in the north and cooling temperatures and cold winds in the south, how are those living in rotten buildings doing in such weather conditions? With six wallets and a 30-year loan, they ended up with an empty concrete frame, some of which are still dirt pits to this day, and no water or electricity.
All of this comes from the pre-sale of real estate from outside the country into the inland system, but just 20 years, has become the industry norm, this system is intended to be good, objectively speaking for the real estate market construction cycle, scale expansion has certain positive effects, but &amp;ldquo;pre-sale&amp;rdquo; is more a test of the spirit of contract between people, trust!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is the Australian dingo an escaped stray or an intruder who never obeyed? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ca6c86856ae4a7b80f5f947649edc7ea/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ca6c86856ae4a7b80f5f947649edc7ea/</guid>
      <description>Are Australian dingoes (dingoes) runaways from home or intruders who never submit? | BMC Journal
Title: The Australian dingo: untamed or feral?
Journal: Frontiers in Zoology
By J. William O. Ballard and Laura A. B. Wilson
Published: 2019/02/13
Digital ID: 10.1186/s12983-019-0300-6
Link to original article: http://t.cn/Eo3igHg
We believe the link: https://mp.weixin.qq.com/s/wy63yERsTo1ABzPNXV4A3A
Is the Australian wild dog an escaped wild (feral) animal or an untamed animal that has never been tamed? It is important to clarify this issue because the Australian government has a policy that considers the Australian wild dog to be a wild animal and therefore allows for their widespread hunting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is the dog food of love also genetic? The newest member of the family, Herman Ho, is the first to be appointed as the newest member of the family. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b032d7f4a7d55b5b74e9a59844d412d8/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b032d7f4a7d55b5b74e9a59844d412d8/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 13:25:44 Source: Oc Entertainment
Report
In &amp;ldquo;Three Times the Charm&amp;rdquo;, the combination of high school bully He Yuzun and supermodel Xi Mengyao&amp;rsquo;s sweetness and love together really is sweet.
#I&amp;rsquo;m not going to be able to do that.
The two of them wash dishes together, Lawrence Ho koala-style hug Xi Mengyao, kisses at every turn, sweet name is also casual.
The latest issue of the program, Lawrence Ho and Xi Mengyao two selling milk tea, men and women with the cooperation of the way, two words &amp;ldquo;not tired&amp;rdquo;, very grounded it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is this &#34;cat&#39;s nest&#34; too luxurious? Silicon Valley Pet Cats Live in $1,500 Apartments </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/559440e623c10da58705f77083acde88/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/559440e623c10da58705f77083acde88/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It was once the &#34;mythical beast&#34; of China, and sold for millions and millions of dollars! Now it&#39;s a &#34;wild dog&#34; and no one wants it. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/65800b68e1843f8df944b6597d1f3aab/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/65800b68e1843f8df944b6597d1f3aab/</guid>
      <description>For the &amp;ldquo;smart&amp;rdquo; people of the country will not give up any opportunity to &amp;ldquo;build wealth&amp;rdquo;, and over the years the residents of China have proven that as long as this thing has the potential to &amp;ldquo;speculate&amp;rdquo; it It&amp;rsquo;s a good way to make money, but of course, those who come in later may become the &amp;ldquo;catcher&amp;rdquo;.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you still remember what was once considered a &amp;ldquo;mythical beast&amp;rdquo; by some residents of China.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s no longer difficult to choose dog food, take a look at the Aide Italia air dry food. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d62ed29003f7a9de5aae6a6779939dcd/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, food safety is such a serious problem that everything we eat must be safe. As for the dog food, there are some unscrupulous peddlers who, in order to earn money, make &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; at low prices to attract consumers. The dog eating &amp;ldquo;poisonous dog food&amp;rdquo; for a long time not only does not get good nutrition, but also may increase the risk of physical illness. So, the shovel officer in the dog selection dog food must be careful and careful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> It&#39;s so warm, I&#39;ll eat this dog food! Zhaotong netizens quickly give their blessings to this Hunan couple! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7fda1c501fb31043fc936385d41e6f45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7fda1c501fb31043fc936385d41e6f45/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s so warm, I&amp;rsquo;m eating this dog food! Zhaotong netizens quickly give their blessings to this Hunan couple! 2020-11-23 20:00 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Media
These two days
Hou Changliang who has been teaching for 10 years and Lei Yudan who has been teaching for 4 years.
Haizi Xiangyangping Primary School in Yiliang, Zhaotong
Video inviting students to witness their wedding photos goes viral online
Hou Changliang, 34, is from Shaoyang, Hunan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jiuquan Horsehair Mountain: &#34;1234&#34; Education Rectification Work System as the Leading System to Play the &#34;Safe Song&#34; at the Borderline </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ee898e6101a3ab41df5d7dc2f260bc5b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ee898e6101a3ab41df5d7dc2f260bc5b/</guid>
      <description>Jiuquan Horsehair Mountain: &amp;ldquo;1234&amp;rdquo; Education Rectification Work System as the Overall Leader, Playing the &amp;ldquo;Safe Song&amp;rdquo; at the Border Frontline 2020-11-28 11:19 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
Sounding the &amp;ldquo;Safe Song&amp;rdquo; at the Borderline
The people&amp;rsquo;s business, the hair will rise; the people&amp;rsquo;s business, the millimetre will go. Since the education and rectification of &amp;ldquo;adhere to the political police, comprehensive and strict police&amp;rdquo;, the Jiuquan border management detachment Mahaishan border police station, as a pilot unit of education and rectification of the Gansu entry-exit border inspection terminus, has continuously improved its ideological awareness and innovated the practice of &amp;ldquo;1234&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Lanzhou: Injured peregrine falcon settles in wildlife rescue station </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/67d0a9f968d2dd5defd16be32e16882f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/67d0a9f968d2dd5defd16be32e16882f/</guid>
      <description>Original title: Warm-hearted citizens timely rescued the injured peregrine falcon and made it &amp;ldquo;home&amp;rdquo; in the wildlife rescue station.
Injured peregrine falcon.
On November 26, Mr. Wang, a citizen, reported that he and his colleagues found an injured peregrine falcon on the rooftop of the Asia-Europe International (AEI) building, and they carried it back to the building and put it into a small cardboard box. In the afternoon, the injured peregrine falcon was accepted by the Gansu Lanzhou Wildlife Rescue Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Lighter moments of the day: what I eat at the beginning of the month, what the dog eats, and what the dog eats a week later. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/76e297ad9d843e6f345eb448a9a433c5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/76e297ad9d843e6f345eb448a9a433c5/</guid>
      <description>Lighter moments of the day: what I eat at the beginning of the month payday, what the dog eats, and what the dog eats a week later.
The beginning of the month payroll I eat what the dog eats, a week later the dog eats what I eat.
The end of the month to live can not go on, fast pay! You are my little apple, I can&amp;rsquo;t get enough of you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Linda H. Gay admits to being in love with Lin Feng? A video of a kiss, with a message later is the person who has dog food to spread </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f0cd64c45ede2c8d92e084378f99b1ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f0cd64c45ede2c8d92e084378f99b1ad/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the two actresses Lin Huan and Yue Hsi Gay were photographed together at a dinner party, and their relationship is suspected to be exposed.
It&amp;rsquo;s the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been in a position to do this.
It is the first time I have ever been to a school. In the video, Yueh-Hsi Gai is holding a Corgi, which is probably her own pet, and as soon as the dog came to Yuehsi&amp;rsquo;s arms, it started licking her mouth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Man Discovers &#34;Mystery Cave&#34;, Pours Coke in, and Out Came the &#34;Beast&#34;! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/44d4689cafcf082666cdd8cc9d241cc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/44d4689cafcf082666cdd8cc9d241cc3/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-24 20:31:37 Source: Colorful Kite Tour says
Report
**Man discovers &amp;ldquo;mystery cave&amp;rdquo;, pours Coke in, and out comes the &amp;ldquo;beast&amp;rdquo;! ***
Burrows are a great hiding place for many creatures. A small anteater was looking for ants when it was discovered by a hyena. The anteater was no match for the hyena and found a burrow when it was about to lose its life, and dug in to avoid the hyena&amp;rsquo;s pursuit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Man scalded pregnant mother cat with boiling water in the street: Animal cruelty is a disease, we have to use the rule of law! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1a61f4c95d709f08171a04061751c3e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1a61f4c95d709f08171a04061751c3e/</guid>
      <description>On October 19, a video of a man scalding a cat with boiling water in Taiyuan, Shanxi province, sparked outrage!
In the video, the man locked a white cat in a cage, with just boiled water and poured the cat, was found by the loving people passing by, immediately stopped and the police, the man was taken away by the police, the cat was sent to the veterinary hospital for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Meowth&#39;s Exclusive Music Debuts Worldwide in October </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0703a478206f9637037497c1a8fa75f1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0703a478206f9637037497c1a8fa75f1/</guid>
      <description>Shovelers will soon have a new way to pamper their meowers. The world&amp;rsquo;s first album of music written specifically for cats will be released by the famous Universal Records to help them calm their nerves and relieve their worries. The album consists of five tracks that combine soundscapes and classical music. Promoter David Tye believes that music is not only for the exclusive use of humans, but can be enjoyed by all mammals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New Tianshui-Wildlife Rescue in Action </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/693ff091ec8917b41c5777adbc999c25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/693ff091ec8917b41c5777adbc999c25/</guid>
      <description>Save the Wildlife We&amp;rsquo;re on the Move
New Tianshui-Tianshui Daily reporter Yan Rongfang
Introduction:
The mountains and rivers are lush, the air is clean and fresh, and the rivers and lakes are shallow. In recent years, as the city&amp;rsquo;s ecological civilization further promote the construction of ecological environment continues to improve, a large number of wild animals have come to Tianshui &amp;ldquo;settled&amp;rdquo;, some trapped, single or injured &amp;ldquo;in distress&amp;rdquo;. The wild animals also wandered into residential areas, industrial zones, schools and other places, and were found to be rescued by citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New scenes and such are weak? Let [UNK] Wild Dog tell you a little secret! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d2fb8bcd1b17cb89cc2607352408ece3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d2fb8bcd1b17cb89cc2607352408ece3/</guid>
      <description>Wang Yi, Founder of the 10 Billion Dollar Institute, Executive Director of Xi Guan Capital
Preface: This article began in late 2018, when China&amp;rsquo;s economy was in a state of crisis due to trade between the U.S. and China, capital chill in the primary market, and shrinking budgets for brand owners. When people forwarded the &amp;ldquo;2019 Advertising Agency Transformation Plan,&amp;rdquo; they asked, &amp;ldquo;In 2019, when people are tightening their belts, what is the way forward for advertising agencies?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ola Good Cat will go on sale tonight with a pre-sale price of RMB 10.50-14.50 million. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f22e4e8340dde685a83783f8eb85c5d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f22e4e8340dde685a83783f8eb85c5d0/</guid>
      <description>Easy Car Newsletter It is reported that the Ola Cat will go on sale tonight (November 24), and the new car is based on Great Wall Motor&amp;rsquo;s Lemon+Coffee intelligent platform. The new car will be available in two range-extended versions, and its announced pre-sale price is RMB 105,000-145,000.
The new car adopts a new design language, which is different from the simple &amp;ldquo;Q-moe&amp;rdquo; style of the Ola Black Cat and White Cat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Old man trains stray dog to pull himself, netizens: really bad  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/957d04cc050474e6b084707839ad2f0c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 13:01:50 Source: Don&amp;rsquo;t let your heart fail you
Report
In the streets of Xi&amp;rsquo;an, Shaanxi Province, one often sees a small dog running along the road pulling an elderly man along.
However, unlike the stories we&amp;rsquo;ve seen before, the dog&amp;rsquo;s owner is not a disabled person, but an able-bodied person.
The dog is also the result of months of deliberate &amp;ldquo;training&amp;rdquo; by the old man.
The old man said, the dog is a stray dog, initially picked it up when it was very thin.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Once a fierce warrior, now with an innocent expression, short legs and long body, guess who I am? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/559d62278b9f6a5044f67e07800664a9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/559d62278b9f6a5044f67e07800664a9/</guid>
      <description>Once a fierce warrior, now with an innocent look and short legs and long body, guess who I am? -Dogipedia 2020-11-13 15:01 Source:Moe Family
Original title: once a fierce warrior, now the expression of innocence, short legs and long body guess who I am? -Dogipedia
__Back to Sohu for more
Responsible Editor.
Statement: The views expressed in this article represent the author&amp;rsquo;s own, Sohu is an information publishing platform, Sohu only provides information storage space services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Owning a cat is a lot of fun, but it&#39;s also more expensive than you might think! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6753d22c9b600920f537b14902cb1d09/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6753d22c9b600920f537b14902cb1d09/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:47:19 Source: What the hell is history?
Report
Owning a cat is a lot of fun, but it&amp;rsquo;s also more expensive than you might think!
It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of fun to have a cat, and when you get home, you can see it lively running towards you, no matter what time it is, you will have such a cute little angel to accompany you, I also have a nutritious diet with cat food and cat snacks and some food, the little guy is healthy and lively, but, raising a cat is also more expensive than expected, I originally thought that raising a cat, only two hundred dollars a month cat food money, after five months of raising found that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Paralyzed Foreign Bulldog Gets New Life Standing and Walking with the Aid of a &#34;Wheelchair&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5b5bf20aeaf43898bfc879293a2d3be3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5b5bf20aeaf43898bfc879293a2d3be3/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 10:51:06 Source: Northeast Tourism
Report
Turkish Samsun, the paralyzed dog named Kara Simsek, also known as Knight. Rider, a French bulldog, was left in a stray rehabilitation center because of paralysis in his hind legs, and with the help of a walking wheelchair, he is back on his feet and walking again.
The paralyzed dog is named Kara Simsek, also known as Knight, in Samsun, Turkey. Rider, a French bulldog, was left in a stray rehabilitation center because of paralysis in his hind legs, and with the help of a walking wheelchair, he is back on his feet and walking again.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Peregrine Falcon&#39;s Desire for Nowhere to Rest - In 1960, experts helped save the peregrine falcon from extinction with &#34;sperm caps&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9b9b4207d548a549f497a6d4616e9b17/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9b9b4207d548a549f497a6d4616e9b17/</guid>
      <description>One pet that has been criticized in the pet world is the Teddy. Teddy is actually a grooming option for poodles, but over time has been called what they are called. The male Teddy, as an adult, has a lot of energy and an excessive thirst for the opposite sex, leading them to develop the habit of hugging their lap at home and doing too many things outside that cannot be seen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Personalized hand-painted art of [UNK] Pet Dogs and [UNK] [UNK] Pet Cats </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ba938e905969fb6f96370f1525abe596/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ba938e905969fb6f96370f1525abe596/</guid>
      <description>For a long time, Goyard has shown respect for traditional craftsmanship while maintaining a passion for innovation. This time, two exclusive personalized hand-painted designs pay homage to another classic Goyard creation - the Goyard&amp;rsquo;s Chic du Chien collection.
Goyard looks to its extensive historical archives for inspiration: SUPER The CAT pet cat was based on a cat in a vintage Goyard catalog and is lucky, mysterious, agile and independent, while the HULOT pet dog was designed by Edmond Derived from the blockbuster advertising campaign starring Mr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pet cat bath &#34;wash&#34; dead owner claims 40,000, shopkeeper: only worth 6300 yuan </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/5222978e8dfb458e2b5d78339d1e1265/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/5222978e8dfb458e2b5d78339d1e1265/</guid>
      <description>Modern Express News (Correspondent Dou Chun Ran, Wang Dani, trainee reporter) (Chai Junhu) Ms. Gao sent her pet cat to a pet store to take a bath, and it died of shock in the process. After the incident, Ms. Gao sued the owner of the pet store in court, claiming damages of 4 million dollars. million yuan. The Modern Express reporter learned that the Kunshan court recently heard the case.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pet cat&#39;s saliva stinks, cat saliva stinks is a disease, 3 easy solutions </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/27b664bb1613e73ac657ee52bc744f3e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/27b664bb1613e73ac657ee52bc744f3e/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 16:44:57 Source: Small Exhibits Big History
Report
If you have a pet cat at home, most people like to pick the cat up and kiss it. Many pet owners also find that their cats actually have bad breath, or that their saliva smells bad, and after licking their fur, the whole body smells like saliva. There are several reasons for this situation, which pet owners can compare and then deal with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pets also acupuncture, facial recognition Market size may exceed $240 billion! Netizens: Stop cloud sucking cats! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/550363696e2d5d7ccd87c914b7817962/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/550363696e2d5d7ccd87c914b7817962/</guid>
      <description>CCTV Financial News November 26, 2020 As more and more pets come into the home, many industries are heating up, such as veterinary hospitals, which are becoming more and more numerous, and which have changed a lot from previous years.
Pet care &amp;ldquo;just in time &amp;ldquo;.
Over 15,000 veterinary hospitals on the ground.
On Sunday, the busiest day of the week came at an animal hospital located outside the North 4th Ring Road in Beijing, where a chinchilla&amp;rsquo;s teeth were pulled and a corgi&amp;rsquo;s acupuncture was administered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Poor Baboon Attacked by African Wild Dogs and Instantly Torn Apart in Cruelty </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aceca2827e19c14ef660a3ee4d2cdd28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aceca2827e19c14ef660a3ee4d2cdd28/</guid>
      <description>The African wild dog is the most efficient predator in Africa, yet these animals changed their feeding habits and started hunting primates like never before, the Daily Mail reported Nov. 28.
According to the report, 55-year-old wildlife photographer Nicholas Dale, who was born in the United States, was the first African wild dog to be killed. (Dyer) is the photographer of these images. Born and raised in Kenya, he has spent the last six years on foot in remote Manatan, Zimbabwe, stalking and photographing these animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Programming Cat [UNK] Chen Wanqing: The Real Barrier of an Enterprise Is Its Organizational Capability </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ef2ccd6a1edeebd1623b76d8e0f90f85/</guid>
      <description>Originally created by Azaka. Mustard pile view of education.
Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, speaks at the GET2020 conference on March 23rd.
♪ By Mustard Pile Ataku
♪ Editorial｜Mustard Pile View Education
On November 23rd, at the GET2020 Education Technology Conference hosted by Mustard Pile, with the theme of &amp;ldquo;Or Leap in the Abyss: Confidence and Development in Education&amp;rdquo;, Wanqing Chen, COO of Programming Cat, gave a keynote speech on &amp;ldquo;Organizational Thinking in Education Enterprises&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pug dies after a week of illness, customer suspects pet store is selling &#34;Chow Chow&#34; </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b122c2a435916bf8add6c09bb5b5d140/</guid>
      <description>Ms. Wang and other customers are showing the pet purchase agreement form.
Chongqing Business News, a dog is the most loyal friend of mankind, with this idea, recently, living in Jiulongpo District, Ba Guo City, Ms. Wang spent 1450 yuan to buy a pug, but buy back less than a week, the dog died of infection virus. It&amp;rsquo;s not a coincidence, Xiao Wu and three other people from the same pet store to buy the dog has also fallen ill, they suspect, they are bought &amp;ldquo;week dog&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Qingdao 78-year-old man with recurrent fever for 8 days also had a heart attack, actually related to pet dogs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/8c4bf904afc90f135019728a1e0ff968/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/8c4bf904afc90f135019728a1e0ff968/</guid>
      <description>Qingdao 78-year-old man with recurrent fever for 8 days had a heart attack, but it was related to his pet dog! 2020-11-28 10:10 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Media
The Peninsula All Media Reporter Qi Juan Correspondent Feng Ping
Recently, a 78-year-old man named Gao Da (a pseudonym) in Qingdao had a recurring fever for eight days and worried everyone in his family. He has muscle and joint pain, abdominal discomfort, loss of appetite, and medication that can only temporarily control his temperature, but who is the culprit?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&#39;s Mouth with His Own Hands </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/35a975ed9cc440bc2a103618924ddff9/</guid>
      <description>RAW! Pet Dog Attacked by Crocodile, Elderly American Breaks Open Crocodile&amp;rsquo;s Mouth with His Own Hands
** CCTV news:** Recently, a 70-year-old man in Florida was walking his dog when an alligator suddenly emerged from a pond, grabbed the dog, and dragged it into the water. In a rush, the owner jumped into the pond, grabbed the alligator, and used his hand to break the alligator&amp;rsquo;s mouth open, and the dog was able to escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Recommended dog food for small dogs like Teddy and Bichon Frise! These brands of dog food are good quality and cheap! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1fd444133e588450b4780ed582f475d6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1fd444133e588450b4780ed582f475d6/</guid>
      <description>I have often seen many users ask questions about the choice of dog food for small dogs, and then go to believe those so-called dog food rankings.
In fact, there is no such thing as a dog food ranking, everyone&amp;rsquo;s consumption budget is different, the best is not necessarily the most suitable for you, the current recognized product quality is better ranking is the summit, craving for this kind of high-end brand is very good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Rolls-Royce umbrellas cost 100,000 a piece, but that&#39;s a lie, the real price is! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c45ad443bdd42533a3826234bc34f00c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c45ad443bdd42533a3826234bc34f00c/</guid>
      <description>Dr. One minute, posture rising
- End of period -
I am Dr. Curious.
Nice to meet you.
Special Note: The above content (including images and videos, if any) is uploaded and published by users of the media platform &amp;ldquo;NetEase&amp;rdquo;, and this platform only provides information storage services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Say &#34;No&#34; to Uncivilized Behavior】Don&#39;t Let Stray Dogs Become a Problem </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/971a39a71631775a0ea0ceeabe428aa0/</guid>
      <description>Recently, the reporter saw many stray dogs scurrying around the community in Qing Qi, which not only affects the cityscape, but also brings potential problems to the residents. I hope that dog owners do not abandon their pets, but also hope that the relevant departments to manage stray dogs.
Please consciously comply with →
The &amp;ldquo;Inner Mongolia Autonomous Region Regulations for the Promotion of Civilized Behavior&amp;rdquo; Article 24 of the city in the built-up areas of keeping dogs, to comply with the following code of conduct: (d) do not abuse, abandoned dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Science shows that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b8eba83b8cf3e94540ac22c551e1e272/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 23:07:16 Source: Basketball Bunny
Report
Scientific studies have shown that owning a dog is good for longevity, do you believe it? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the reasons why we say that!
In a study, Dog Ownership and Survival After a Major Cardiovascular Disease, the results of a study were published. In the paper, &amp;ldquo;Dog Ownership and Survival After Major Cardiovascular Events,&amp;rdquo; Swedish scientists tracked the mortality data of all patients aged 40 to 85 years who died of acute myocardial infarction and ischemic stroke from 2001 to 2012 and concluded that dog owners gained the following additional health benefits compared to those who did not own a dog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sending 4 cats to herd sheep, but when I went to see them again, I was disgusted: This is a very good lazy thief! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aba68643b6890fe0b68fa104adf168ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aba68643b6890fe0b68fa104adf168ad/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 13:00:30 Source: Veterinarian Videos
Report
What a beautiful picture of the sky and the wilderness, the grass blowing in the wind and the cows and sheep. If possible, the veterinarian would like to get away from the chaotic city and go to the grassland to graze cattle and sheep. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter what kind of environment you live in, it&amp;rsquo;s important to be open-minded, isn&amp;rsquo;t it?
I&amp;rsquo;m sure we&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of sheepdogs, so has anyone heard of sheepdogs and cats?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Short-legged dog competition, who has the shortest legs, which one do you like the most? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f6aa857e17c20c34de0d6cd7766ed789/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f6aa857e17c20c34de0d6cd7766ed789/</guid>
      <description>In the human world, there are long-legged opahs and seven dwarfs, so naturally there are long-legged and short-legged woofers in the woof world too!
There was a long-legged woof Greeks before, Greeks elegant temperament, running smooth body line, growing is cute and lovely people like, so today we talk about a few small short legs in the woof world, short legs is always synonymous with cute, see if it is not?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shovelers, do you know how to read your dog breed in English? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/447f1f0b215e06c23e6f5a363bc50231/</guid>
      <description>Last weekend, I was standing on a small terrace in Wudaoying with a glass of hot red wine and a few friends, enjoying a leisurely life that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t dream of on a weekday. Suddenly one guy got up after looking at his watch with a serious expression, and just as we were trying to figure out which words were not in place, he said, &amp;ldquo;Sorry, the dog hasn&amp;rsquo;t left yet, I&amp;rsquo;ll go first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shunde Longjiang Poly Man Killed Golden Retriever Poodle Owner Detained </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cb910a701601ceda9a4849fa6c73551d/</guid>
      <description>In the past few years, the government has been trying to improve the quality of life for the people of Hong Kong.
The owner of the golden retriever, Mr. Wang, told reporters that his 70-year-old parents in the course of the dispute both sickness hospitalized, and the incident so far, the owner of the poodle and his family never apologized to himself and his parents, also from the future hospital to see his parents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sitting down for a real romance with Lin Feng? The first time I saw a dog, I thought it was a dog. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/f35b69f865291a94746edfe962a3a4cb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/f35b69f865291a94746edfe962a3a4cb/</guid>
      <description> Sitting down for a real romance with Lin Jianli? The first time I saw a dog, I thought it was a dog. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Snowstorm Hits British Safari Park, African Wild Dogs Run Away, Killing 16 Animals </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of African wild dogs escaped from their yard and killed 16 animals in the Worcestershire Wildlife Park in England due to damage caused by Storm Siara, Sky News reported on February 14.
A park spokeswoman said that in the early morning hours of Feb. 9, 12 wild dogs entered a compound near the park, killing six Persian fallow deer and 10 Barbary sheep.
The park spokeswoman had previously said, &amp;ldquo;At no time was there a risk to public safety or any danger of animals escaping the park fence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sporting Dog [UNK] is a true sportsman! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aa5a92ae8f1baac2b3fc7923dd395169/</guid>
      <description>Breed Determines Character
Every type of dog has something in common, so &amp;ldquo;breed determines personality&amp;rdquo;. Most dog registries classify dogs according to their behavioral characteristics, instincts and family history. Currently, it is common worldwide to group dogs into seven distinctive categories: sporting dogs, hunting dogs with a keen sense of smell or sight, sheepdogs, working dogs, and dogs with a strong sense of smell or sight. Dogs, Toy Dogs and Family Dogs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Spotted Hyena was once all over China (group photo) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fe735c25dcefb5bb9179b28deb7459c0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fe735c25dcefb5bb9179b28deb7459c0/</guid>
      <description>The spotted hyena became extinct 11,000 years ago in China and across Asia and Europe.
Currently, many Africans are feeding spotted hyenas as pets.
African spotted hyena fighting with wolf packs
The fossilized head of a spotted hyena has been found in Qinhuangdao, which is expected to solve the mystery of the extinction of the megafauna 11,000 years ago&amp;hellip;.
Recently, the excavation of 21 nearly intact fossilized spotted hyena skulls, which had been extinct in Asia and Europe, at Lingxian Cave near Banchangyu Village in northern Fanning County, Qinhuangdao City, has attracted widespread attention from archaeologists and the media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Such a cute dog doesn&#39;t want to be touched? Shovel: Danger! It&#39;s aggressive! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b675135ff79b8cadeda18a03b9661f37/</guid>
      <description>German Shepherd (German) The Shepherd is also used as a police dog, search and rescue dog, etc. due to its size, powerful appearance, and ability to work. In the UK, there was a German Shepherd who, despite being 4 years old, was still small enough to be a corgi and was often thought to be a puppy by passersby, but in fact he had a rare disease.
Tiger the German Shepherd suffers from dwarfism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Talking Short Legged Dog Game Download </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e9c2cc5c4f880b623a28db7d17c85329/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e9c2cc5c4f880b623a28db7d17c85329/</guid>
      <description>Talking Short Legs is a dog game with cute, lovely and interesting graphics, this cute little dog can make all kinds of strange sounds, it is also very realistic.
The Talking Short-Legged Dog Game Features.  The picture is interesting, lively and lovely, liked by many players. 2.
 The scenes are colorful, and the color matching is perfect and realistic, bringing players the feeling of being in the real world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The &#34;Trio of Happiness 3&#34; Wu Jing and his wife&#39;s archery hands-on teaching, netizens: archery and dog food. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/72103a6de85cff0256ef864d68cf0fd6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/72103a6de85cff0256ef864d68cf0fd6/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 11:09:59 Source: Project Pushing Stars
Report
The new episode of &amp;ldquo;Three Times the Charm&amp;rdquo; has been aired, and in a traditional festival, the Mid-Autumn Festival has been celebrated with a variety of folk activities and country fairs, and the festivities are everywhere, and everyone&amp;rsquo;s face is really full of smiles and joy.
As three pairs of celebrity couples, definitely want to join this grand Mid-Autumn Festival celebration, they are starting to get busy, Wu Jing and Xie Nan finished their lunch early, they eat when they also said why are cabbage tofu, Xie Nan said a particularly funny one said: &amp;ldquo;cabbage tofu to keep the peace,&amp;rdquo; the two also eat up!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The 42-year-old Queen of Thailand is possessed by a little devil? High heels are so colorful and tacky, Sotirida misses the mark! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/24c30a836f01b3f04b510bb8d4739f82/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/24c30a836f01b3f04b510bb8d4739f82/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 16:02:55 Source: NerdsmithingYo
Report
On the evening of November 25, local time, King Maha Vajiralongkorn and Queen Sultan Suthep attended the Rama VI ceremony.
Queen Suthep&amp;rsquo;s jewelry looked exactly the same as the day before when she went to the Sirikit Foundation on official business, and although the jewelry remained the same, the change in clothing was very obvious.
Queen Sirikit&amp;rsquo;s jewelry is unmatched by the Queen&amp;rsquo;s collection, but her incomparable gems are not available to the wife of the current king.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The 5 most obvious phenomena of aging in a poodle are the ones that owners need to take care of, and they can give it a few more years of life! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c64becb6c14e70dd8ffa6d67bb31d893/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c64becb6c14e70dd8ffa6d67bb31d893/</guid>
      <description>Dogs, no matter how cute they are, will one day grow old, and pet owners should not let go.
However, if you can change the pace of your dog&amp;rsquo;s life as soon as you see him getting older, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to keep him alive for a long time.
If you have a poodle, how can you tell if your poodle is getting old? Let&amp;rsquo;s tell you about it here, so that you can pay attention to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Battle of the African Steppe for Ranking! Wild dog [UNK] hyena, who is the real African penis? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/23b5dee2e76c928174b89e0d3b7c8ff3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/23b5dee2e76c928174b89e0d3b7c8ff3/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to the little tyrant on the African grasslands, the &amp;ldquo;flat-headed brother&amp;rdquo; honey badger must be the one to beat. &amp;ldquo;Who could it be? Many people think of them as spotted hyenas, but when it comes to another fierce little bully, the spotted hyena is anything but.
The African Hyena is about 1 meter long and weighs up to 70 pounds, they look more like an adult Chinese Cavalier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The China Pet Consumption Trend Report 2019: Which &#34;shovelers&#34; are busy &#34;jerking off&#34;? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7b2ccf57e175f206095ae1e70a562bc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7b2ccf57e175f206095ae1e70a562bc3/</guid>
      <description>On November 19, Fan Tianyang, General Manager of Pet Procurement Department of Jingdong Retail Consumer Products Division, released the 2019 China Pet Consumption Trend Report (the &amp;ldquo;Report&amp;rdquo;) at the China International Pet &amp;amp; Aquarium Show (CIPS) Gala Dinner. According to the Report, China&amp;rsquo;s pet market has continued to expand in recent years, and the pet industry will continue to maintain a growth rate of over 14% in the next 3-5 years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Evolution of the Adorable Meowth </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/cef2160acbe3bcf6af1f766e68cece57/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/cef2160acbe3bcf6af1f766e68cece57/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Meowth&amp;rdquo; is a warm-hearted online show that portrays the evolution of cute pets. __
The Evolution of Meowth Duration: 02:26 Source: Movie Network
Total 7 __
1905film.com The family film &amp;ldquo;The Meow Star&amp;rdquo; directed by Chen Mucheng and starring Gutenberg, Mary Ma, Liu Chutian, Huang Xingvis, etc. will be released on July 7, 2017 during the summer season nationwide. The movie tells the story of the &amp;ldquo;Meow Star Guest&amp;rdquo; Rhinoceros, who comes to Earth in a spaceship and unwittingly becomes the new member of the Kutian Le and Mary&amp;rsquo;s family and the series of hilarious stories that follow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Little Milk Cat Becomes a Fat Uncle after Adulthood, Netizens Take a Look at the Color: Orange Cat&#39;s Gene Isn&#39;t Bragging </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3a540b72fdfd3a4950104dca808691ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3a540b72fdfd3a4950104dca808691ed/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 06:16:22 Source: Flowers, plants and pets
Report
Cats are the most common animals in our lives, even if we don&amp;rsquo;t have cats at home, we are still likely to meet stray cats on the road.
Even if you don&amp;rsquo;t own a cat, you are still likely to meet stray cats on the road. What do the stray cats you see look like? Even though they are fed by their mothers, many stray cats are still relatively thin and weak, and their pitiful appearance makes people want to take them home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Little Sisters of the Heroes of the Grasslands, a children&#39;s ballet that reaffirms collectivism from a new perspective </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/395abf1bcca6f757b72294c88a56dfbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/395abf1bcca6f757b72294c88a56dfbe/</guid>
      <description>The heroic deeds of the Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes have influenced generations, are the pride of Baotou, and are our role models. We need to dig deep into the spirit of the &amp;ldquo;Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes&amp;rdquo; spirit of the times, the &amp;ldquo;Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes&amp;rdquo; story told from generation to generation, education and guidance of today&amp;rsquo;s youth as a good inheritor of the red gene, practitioner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Maine cat is facing Yi Yun Qianxi, is your cat the same model as the star? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ee0d5bc5502fa80e6ee344f2c3648611/</guid>
      <description>They are agile, a little sleepy, like to lick their own hair clean, and have a maverick personality. They are not always obedient to their masters, and are more like two equal friends than subordinates. Is the cat the same as the star?
1 Dusk. British Shorthair
British Shorthair cats are round and chubby, with short, coarse and well-developed limbs, a short, dense coat, a big head and a round face that looks cute, gentle and calm, very friendly and easy to feed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Meow Star&#34; Special: Gutiérrez Mari as &#34;Tinker Bell </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/34707847af5f00be40103fab08c7e901/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/34707847af5f00be40103fab08c7e901/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The Meowth&amp;rdquo; Special: Gutiérrez and Mary as &amp;ldquo;Tinker Bell __
The Meowth Featurette Duration: 00:00 Source: Movie Network
Total 4 __
1905film.com The family film &amp;ldquo;The Meow Star&amp;rdquo;, directed by Chen Mucheng and starring Louis Koo, Mary Ma, Liu Chutian, Huang Xingjun, etc., has been released in theaters nationwide on July 14 (this Friday). The film tells the story of a cute appearance, with a clever and intelligent mind, easily get human favorites of the rhinoceros rhinoceros shouldering the mission to travel to Earth, but accidentally encountered a family of Kutian Le and Mary, and staged a scene of luck, meow interesting cat encounters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Mutant &#34;Weird&#34; Sphinx Cat, So Gentle! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/ea605cf97e57ef538a2f6310cc2b566a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/ea605cf97e57ef538a2f6310cc2b566a/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s like something out of the movie &amp;ldquo;ET&amp;rdquo;. It, with its unique and bizarre shape, has a scowl written all over it. It, with wrinkles as if it were a genetic mutation monster. It, the Sphinx cat.
The Sphinx, also known as the Canadian Hairless Cat, is loved beyond words by some people, while those who are used to furry cats may find the Sphinx&amp;rsquo;s appearance too frightening. The Sphinx is gentle, intelligent and agile, and is loved by people with cat hair allergies, but the Sphinx is not completely hairless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Past and Present of the Transparent Chassis </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/91fee926568ab432c53ed3b49c5466b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/91fee926568ab432c53ed3b49c5466b3/</guid>
      <description>What if I see ants on the road? Do you hide or press? This is not a test of humanity, but a test of &amp;ldquo;eyesight&amp;rdquo;. How refreshing. Who can see ants in a car? That requires a X-ray eye plus a high magnifying glass! Well, there is indeed such a device, it is called transparent chassis, this technology was first applied by the Land Rover, but now is played by the Harvard big dog to play out the flower, today will pick up the history of this thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The actual story, I spent $380,000 to get my dog cloned. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/bdec11a1b5b6e3f408cca5bd91502498/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/bdec11a1b5b6e3f408cca5bd91502498/</guid>
      <description>When she was a teenager, an 85-year-old Shanghai girl adopted a neighbor&amp;rsquo;s abandoned dog named Ni Ni and kept it for 17 years until last fall, when she was 19 years old. When old Nene died of organ failure, she decided to have a clone, and the new Nene was born.
I don&amp;rsquo;t know if you&amp;rsquo;ve seen the 1982 movie Blade Runner.
The amazing thing is that we are now in the month of November 2019, which is when the first part of this movie takes place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The chauffeur was chased up the hill by a pack of wild dogs in the early hours of the morning! He took a picture with his cell phone in the darkness and collapsed instantly </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/876841f843065726ba2812ef38a2453a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/876841f843065726ba2812ef38a2453a/</guid>
      <description>The chauffeur was chased up the hill by a pack of wild dogs in the early hours of the morning! He took a picture with his cell phone in the darkness and collapsed instantly&amp;hellip; 2020-08-17 17:46 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Media
In the early morning of August 17th, the police station in Hangzhou, Zhejiang Province, West Lake District received a tired voice: I&amp;rsquo;m a chauffeur, I&amp;rsquo;m being chased by wild dogs, in the mountains, I can&amp;rsquo;t get down!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The cute and sweet Teddy is a hound, but it&#39;s a good thing I didn&#39;t mess with him, or else I&#39;d be in trouble! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/34bee1af25e5784cfd4b1a05bb6f7ca7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/34bee1af25e5784cfd4b1a05bb6f7ca7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-25 20:51:07 Source: Abdominal Tearer&amp;rsquo;s Week
Report
Would you believe it if someone told you that your Teddy is actually a hunting dog? I know most people think it&amp;rsquo;s impossible, but how can a small, litter-ridden dog be a ferocious hound? Let me tell you then, based on the history of the Teddy&amp;rsquo;s origins and the tracing of its lineage, it really is a terrier.
For the record, the Teddy is not a breed of dog, it&amp;rsquo;s just one of the dogs of the Poodle, just like one of the lipstick shades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The difference between a poodle and a teddy, after reading this, I finally understand! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d2cb28887d9278bf4fe4166d2a84f4a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d2cb28887d9278bf4fe4166d2a84f4a/</guid>
      <description>Many people are still confused about the relationship between a poodle and a teddy, so what is the difference between a poodle and a teddy? After reading the following, I finally understand, have you figured out how they are related?
I. What is a Poodle?
The Poodle, also known as the &amp;ldquo;Poodle&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Poodle Curl&amp;rdquo;, is known for its water hunting and is a water hound. Poodles are classified by AKC standards as Standard, Miniature and Toy based on their size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The first time I saw you, I thought I&#39;d be the one to tell you about it. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fa7b4e3603bce5c66195420992aec4d7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fa7b4e3603bce5c66195420992aec4d7/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:28:09 Source: Xiao Jing Entertainment
Report
Recently the coat brother&amp;rsquo;s son, Zhu Xiaowei, dried a video on the Internet and wrote a text saying, wife&amp;rsquo;s ponytail is not very magical ah.
It seems that the wooden and plain Zhu Xiaowei is enlightened, actually can be online so show couple love. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a matter of time, but it&amp;rsquo;s also a matter of time before you get to the point where you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to see and hear a lot of things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The first time I&#39;ve been in a relationship with a woman, I&#39;ve been in one. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/8ebef841d334ab92eeade9ec0039d23f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/8ebef841d334ab92eeade9ec0039d23f/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 23:14:01 Source: Culture Traveler says
Report
On November 26th, actress Yueh-Hsi Gai updated a status on top of her social media platform, and the video shows Yuehsi Gai in home clothes, with the words &amp;ldquo;I am also a person who has dog food to sprinkle. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty sweet.
On November 25, a suspected love affair between Yueh-Hsien Gai and Lin update has caught everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention. The reason for the incident is because someone filmed Lin and Yue Hsi in a private party, and there is a close relationship between them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The good drive and smart &#34;refined brother&#34;, with face and strength, who can hide? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/741e70d8ec518eedc2e740bc3685ad11/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/741e70d8ec518eedc2e740bc3685ad11/</guid>
      <description>In this day and age, buying a car is all about value for money and quality.
If you want to enjoy the senses as well as the product features, what choice do you have?
stamp vision frequency*.
The new generation of Regal 5x is coming with high energy.
The new generation of Ruihu 5x will be a great success.
The new generation of Ruihu 5x, the much-anticipated new Ruihu 5x High Power Edition, is coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The location of the wild dog maze in the Hundred Views of Jiangnan </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/2015d29781a43f2744886f54c5ea56e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/2015d29781a43f2744886f54c5ea56e3/</guid>
      <description>The location of the wild dog maze in Jiangnan Hundred Scenes of Jiangnan. Author：Internet Source：JiuYou Release Time：2020-11-19 09:45:00 Mobile Subscribe
Tags: Labyrinth
Where are the wild dogs in Gangnam Hundred Views? Many players don&amp;rsquo;t know where to look for them, but they are generally distributed inside the wild dog maze, and there are three of them, and the location of each one may not be so detailed.
Summary of the Hundred Views of Jiangnan Maze of Wild Dogs Location Map</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The more strange, the more users adopted a short-legged little black dog, half a year later, it actually turned into a long-legged big-nosed dog! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/60b651608f0026e996a036c25e13f9f4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/60b651608f0026e996a036c25e13f9f4/</guid>
      <description>The more strange the breeding, the more the netizens adopted a short-legged little black dog, half a year later, it turned into a long-legged big-nosed dog! Last June
The netizen Ms. Huang adopted a small earth dog from the Internet.
and named it Brown Sugar.
Brown sugar is only 20 centimeters long when it first arrives at home.
The little ones are especially cute.
But I didn&amp;rsquo;t expect to keep it for only half a year or so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The net exposes Fan Bingbing&#39;s sky-priced cat, experts say around 200,000 yuan, which is really a financial strength. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0ba303d1c50bba614b38884ee53d0f3b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0ba303d1c50bba614b38884ee53d0f3b/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 07:54:54 Source: Beast Love Entertainment
Report
Hello, I&amp;rsquo;m your candy cane baby, I&amp;rsquo;m here to update you daily with fun and interesting articles, follow me if you like!
Recently, the net exposed the big beauty Fan Bingbing in her personal social media platform sun sky cat, I have to admit that the network spread really fast, immediately experts said that the brown one price in about 200,000.
The next step is to take a look at Fan Bingbing and her cats with the sugar-coated baby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The newest member of the family, Mr. Chen Guanxi, has a family photo by the beach and Qin Shupei is wearing a couple of shoes. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d116b446e15db1b0cd5e8bd909d0a07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d116b446e15db1b0cd5e8bd909d0a07/</guid>
      <description>On November 24, Chen Guanxi showed a family photo of the three of them sitting on a reef in his personal social media platform. In the photo, Chen Guanxi and Qin Shubei are wearing couple&amp;rsquo;s shoes together and secretly spreading dog food.
In the photo shared by Chen Guanxi, the three of them gestured the same gesture, and the couple also wore couple shoes in a low-key manner, showing a secret show of love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The newest member of the family, Zega: Tang YiXin attended the event and wore a mint green cake dress with a sweet effect. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/48424d6189c4713cf864466e0b6c0dc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/48424d6189c4713cf864466e0b6c0dc1/</guid>
      <description>On Nov. 25, Tang YiXin wore a mint green cake dress to the opening ceremony of the Golden Rooster Awards, bringing a touch of mint green in the winter, as if dancing lightly, revealing a superior shoulder and neck line.
It&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to show off the beauty of your body, and it&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to show off the beauty of your body,&amp;rdquo; she said.
It&amp;rsquo;s not just a matter of time and space, it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of time and space, and it&amp;rsquo;s also a matter of time and space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The night life of cats is much more exciting than yours.  </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/525b6c70f936de37cb6407538d81cf45/</guid>
      <description>Not long ago, Weibo was ablaze with a spoof video from YouTube.
In the cat&amp;rsquo;s first view, a mysterious day goes by unbeknownst to the shovelers.
As soon as the good cat in the video leaves the house-
Money is easy to rob.
The Hammer Man Hammering Away
But what the stupid humans don&amp;rsquo;t know is that the content of this video is actually not all that bad - it&amp;rsquo;s a spoof!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The pet dog [UNK] cleans meticulously, the pet cat follows along full of curiosity </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e21637f5f5800ea3e5ae20c45987dcf1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e21637f5f5800ea3e5ae20c45987dcf1/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-22 22:45:10 Source: Surprise Nature
Report
I&amp;rsquo;ll give you a full review.
Famous actress Christy 2020 posted on her personal social media platform on November 22, 2020 at 17:33 PM.
My booBoo help me hahahahaha!
At the same time, Zhong Li Ti also dried out a short video for 0:44 seconds, in which Zhong Li Ti mainly filmed the family&amp;rsquo;s pet dog dog to clean up their own, there are pet cats interspersed with back and forth, in short, this is a very loving, super warm picture and video, we&amp;rsquo;ll see it below!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The ugliest dog in the dog world, with a face so ugly that no one dared to go near it! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/41377eedd46a6112a0acfd4eaa102410/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/41377eedd46a6112a0acfd4eaa102410/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:01:32 Source: Abdominal Tearer&amp;rsquo;s Week
Report
I&amp;rsquo;ve seen ugly dogs, I&amp;rsquo;ve never seen such an ugly dog, they say bulldogs are already very ugly, but after seeing this dog, I found that bulldogs are already quite beautiful dogs, this dog is dark and ugly.
Of course, although this dog is very ugly, the owner also likes it, so he likes its ugliness.
Everyone&amp;rsquo;s interest is different, although the dog is ugly, but still acceptable range, unlike some people have pigs as pets, that is really a bit unbearable, after all, the dog is still man&amp;rsquo;s best friend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> There is a kind of &#34;plastic surgery&#34; called Pauline Lantern&#39;s asthma dog, now in uniform, handsome unrecognizable! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1dc478d9e8ebac1d075fb37ebf386085/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1dc478d9e8ebac1d075fb37ebf386085/</guid>
      <description>One drama that just aired and attracted a large number of fans and is now a household name is &amp;ldquo;Baolian Lantern&amp;rdquo;. When this drama was aired, the response was really great. The drama tells the story of the man, Shen Xiang, who uses an axe to chop the mountain to save his mother. Because of this drama, a lot of people have been fired, for example, the lead role of Erlang Shen, played by Jiao Junen, whose outstanding appearance made the audience think that he was the original Erlang Shen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> There was a dog&#39;s head on the driver&#39;s side of the car, and I thought it was a dog driving the car, but when I saw it, I realized it was a mistake. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7b5b852b8261a32016e9168fcc0722b9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7b5b852b8261a32016e9168fcc0722b9/</guid>
      <description>Nowadays, living conditions have become better and private cars are no longer rare, which makes it much easier for people to travel. Especially for those who have elderly people, children and pets at home, there is no need to worry about them not being able to go out because of the inconvenience of the car. However, the most important thing about driving is to pay attention to safety, as the saying goes: driving is not standardized, family members two lines of tears ah.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> These Lab Beagles Just Got Promoted to the National Team </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0dcfad7a4936f10b410669aedc8c36d0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0dcfad7a4936f10b410669aedc8c36d0/</guid>
      <description>Wen/Tu JinYang reporter Chen Zeyun
After special breeding and training, some of them are sent to customs to become quarantine dogs, while others are sent to universities or research institutions to become teaching dogs or dogs for scientific research. &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
On June 13, the reporter learned from GPG that the &amp;ldquo;National Canine Laboratory Animal Resource Bank&amp;rdquo; of its Guangzhou General Institute of Pharmaceutical Sciences was included in the list of national science and technology resource sharing service platforms, which is also the first national science and technology resource sharing service platform in the Greater Bay Area of Guangdong, Hong Kong and Macao.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 Cute Short-Legged Dogs </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1f23d7c4532787b04b7f339b21b182d4/</guid>
      <description>1 - Corgi  When it comes to short legs, we have to mention the new web sensation in the dog world - the Corgi. By virtue of its rounded buttocks and limbs, the Corgi has become the new favorite of dog breeders.
The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s two main adorable points are its round butt, good feel and elasticity, and its legs are so short that even going upstairs is difficult, which is very cute and makes people want to hold it in their arms and jerk it off from head to toe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Try to avoid these 8 breeds of dog because it will cost the owner more money! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a714657ae5fa3c82c7b7218b7c6b26a4/</guid>
      <description>Dogs are often called &amp;ldquo;man&amp;rsquo;s best friend&amp;rdquo;, we live with them, they give us unconditional love, and we provide them with a comfortable living environment and diet.
It is normal to provide the necessary expenses for a dog&amp;rsquo;s normal survival. However, there are some breeds of dogs that, because of their characteristics, can cost a dog parent more money.
The aggressive Rottweiler.
The list of dog breeds that are not recommended to be fed is made by a veterinarian who has returned to the United States after 20 years of practice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Two horses snatched the golden retriever dog food through the cage, owner: never snatch in front of me. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/649f3070f7cf7f1097a8f935c10855ad/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/649f3070f7cf7f1097a8f935c10855ad/</guid>
      <description>To view this video please enable JavaScript, and consider upgrading to a web browser that supports HTML5 video
Erha stole the golden retriever&amp;rsquo;s food through the cage, owner: Never steal in front of me! On November 22nd, Mr. Xie, in Xinxiang, Henan province, photographed his own husky expertly pouring dog food from the Golden Retriever tub next door into his own tub. Mr. Xie said the husky was only two years old and never grabbed it in front of him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> U.S. Delivers Drones, Missiles to Philippines, Top Officials Speak on South China Sea </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9ef14b4e81245225c8a7773fb66cd9de/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9ef14b4e81245225c8a7773fb66cd9de/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 18:20:43 Source: Global Military Times
Report
The U.S. delivered weapons worth nearly $33 million to the Philippines this week, including 100 wire-guided missiles, 12 thermal imaging systems, 24 500-pound bombs and an unmanned surveillance aircraft, the State Department said, according to the U.S. Army&amp;rsquo;s Stars and Stripes newspaper of 25 March.
Robert O&amp;rsquo;Brien (center) inspects a TOW-2A missile system in Manila.
A $14.79 million ScanEagle unmanned aerial vehicle was turned over to the Philippine Navy on Wednesday to enhance its maritime surveillance and border security capabilities, according to a statement released the same day by the U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> United Engine｜What is a big dog with two legs and a wild dog with four legs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/4bc50cb8fc06a6c5692dba1898121e07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/4bc50cb8fc06a6c5692dba1898121e07/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps the 2020 epidemic has exacerbated the winter in the auto market, further amplifying the pressure on car companies. Even the domestic SUV leaders are beginning to show signs of weakness. Although Haval SUVs are still able to maintain a certain lead in the market, they have begun to lack momentum. In particular, the Haval H6, from March to August &amp;ldquo;stable&amp;rdquo; play, sustained performance of more than 20,000 units, did not achieve a greater increase in sales, but also to the successor CS75 PLUS sees the hope of overtaking in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Veterinarians can&#39;t stand it, and many owners make these mistakes, are you still raising Corgis this way? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d0663b90ade254581ba7cb25ef4c1946/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d0663b90ade254581ba7cb25ef4c1946/</guid>
      <description>When you first start to breed a Corgi, you don&amp;rsquo;t even realize that sometimes the actions of the pet owners may harm the dog. Therefore, we advise pet owners that they should not continue to keep their Corgi like this, or they will only harm their Corgi!
Not taking Corgi out for sports
Although Corgi is short-legged, he used to be a cattle dog, but his physical activity level is as good as any other dog&amp;rsquo;s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Wang Gou&#39;s private photos were exposed, wearing a sleeveless black dress with a [UNK] collar, sharp eyes and a good body full of stories </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6ad576d51c1cbe8d04a5ba8526102ae9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6ad576d51c1cbe8d04a5ba8526102ae9/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 14:22:04 Source: MoMoTravel
Report
Recently, a set of private photos of Wang Gu was exposed, in which she was wearing a V-neck sleeveless black dress lying on the bed, a gold chain belt around her waist, with sharp eyes and a good body full of stories.
Wang Ou&amp;rsquo;s face value has always been recognized, big eyes, high nose bridge, standard three court five eyes, this time with clothes and accessories decorations, the whole person more full of quality, look at the camera eyes full of story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What Versailles literature? Isn&#39;t it just the daily life of a meow! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/867f263eb45348969e0e5178359c9428/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/867f263eb45348969e0e5178359c9428/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what to make of the Versailles literature, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what to make of it if it&amp;rsquo;s available to meowers.
For those of you who don&amp;rsquo;t know what Versailles literature is, please take a look at the following science diagram, which can be skipped if you are a Versailles student: &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;
I can&amp;rsquo;t say that cat nests are an IQ tax, but cardboard boxes do get more meowing than anything else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What are the fastest animals in the world? Top 10 Fastest Animals, See Who&#39;s Faster </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9b513b861282a70bfeff8714dd2a066c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9b513b861282a70bfeff8714dd2a066c/</guid>
      <description>There are many animals in the world that run. The lion, for example, is the most dominant animal of the African savannah and is known as the &amp;ldquo;King of the Beasts&amp;rdquo;. But what most people don&amp;rsquo;t know is that lions are also very fast. Most of the time, fast running animals will dare to hunt prey that runs at the same or even much faster than them. Do you know what the fastest animals are?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What do you know about Corgi? Today we&#39;re going to discuss </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a2ae7ed10148531a329512b1060c974a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 16:26:26 Source: Abdominal Tearer&amp;rsquo;s Week
Report
The Corgi is very cute, easy to take care of, and takes up little time. The Corgi&amp;rsquo;s IQ is also very high, and he will quickly learn to master any skill he is taught, especially his appearance, and he is very good at playing tricks.
Looking online, I learned that there are roughly three types of Corgi: the first Cardigan-Welsh Corgi, the second Pembroke Welsh Corgi, and the third Swedish Corgi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a70df66667aae83914a0e0e96fe68fdb/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a70df66667aae83914a0e0e96fe68fdb/</guid>
      <description>What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow?
Time：2015-03-24 21:10 Source：hongwang.com Editor：Mao Qingqing
Chuanbei Online Core Tip: What does it mean to be a meow? What is the best way to keep a meow? &amp;mdash;
Meowers, an Internet buzzword, dubs cats as aliens who come to Earth from the distant planet Meow from outer space and use their cute appearance to trick humans into trusting them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is it like to own a Beagle? Beagle Personality Traits </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/877c0997c8c7811b3358fb6f1a2620da/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-19 09:44:11 Source: Mother &amp;amp; Baby Pie
Report
There are quite a few pet owners in China who have Beagles, and Petsky has met some Beagles and their owners in animal hospitals. ** Too lively! Too lively! Too lively! (Important point, say it three times.) **
In an animal hospital, you can come across all kinds of dogs, and almost all of them have their own unique characteristics that will make an impression on you in one way or another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What is the best brand of dog food? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/042b91d0d8fe09c116ba7c2a11be7040/</guid>
      <description>Every dog shovel officer who brings home a dog, will love the cute dog. But for puppies in a new environment, the environment is already unfamiliar, and if the wrong dog food is chosen, it will directly affect the dog&amp;rsquo;s subsequent development. Choosing a suitable dog food for puppies is very critical, and an important way to continue the healthy growth of your dog is to choose a nutritionally rich and balanced, and safe and natural dog food.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What should I do if my pug has diarrhea? Why do you have diarrhea? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/eb4473d46bcea9c7871b36e2de8ab4b5/</guid>
      <description>The silly and charming appearance of the pug has attracted many people&amp;rsquo;s attention, making it a popular pet dog nowadays. But in the process of caring for the pug, we can&amp;rsquo;t be sloppy. In the summer, it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon for pugs to have diarrhea, and it&amp;rsquo;s necessary to know the relevant knowledge in advance. In the following, the editor of Porky.com will analyze the causes of diarrhea in pug dogs and the measures to deal with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> When the Soviet Union secretly built the Warrior of the Apes, five female volunteers participated, what happened to them? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/7d06ffdb744e0a16010a426fca68405c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/7d06ffdb744e0a16010a426fca68405c/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-28 08:16:51 Source: mango pudding dairy
Report
I&amp;rsquo;m sure many of you have seen Planet of the Apes, Rise of the Planet of the Apes and other Hollywood blockbusters, in which the gorilla warriors also left a deep impression on everyone. In terms of individual power, humans are far less powerful than these animals. If we could use the power of the orangutan for human beings, we could create a group of &amp;ldquo;super soldiers&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Where can I get a cracked version of Shy Comics? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b2c605fb8caa7ed79bb58de3a326efb3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b2c605fb8caa7ed79bb58de3a326efb3/</guid>
      <description>Shy comic where to get cracked version - Low pollution bleaching process of two kinds of cotton short staple pulp
Featured Websites &amp;ldquo;Fei Xian understands.&amp;rdquo; He was good enough for her, how could she protest that he didn&amp;rsquo;t set aside more time for her. May God thunder down upon you!&amp;rdquo; Jasmine holds up a dagger higher than Mona. 2.
 Jasmine then runs to the stables, looking for someone who can escort them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Where is the location of the wild dog in Jiangnan Hundred View Map? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c98b326e7b65d73936a70b98b861c6ce/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c98b326e7b65d73936a70b98b861c6ce/</guid>
      <description>Where is the location of the wild dog in the Jiangnan Parkview?
Time：2020-11-12 16:42 Source：YiYouwang Editor：MoDuo
Chuanbei Online Core Tip: Original title: Jiangnan Hundred Views map wild dog location where Jiangnan Hundred Views map wild dog location with you to share Jiangnan Hundred View map wild dog location, the partners must want to know it, the next tour editor brought to you a hundred scenes of Jiangnan wild dog location sharing, I hope you like.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who is responsible for the death of 150 chickens, ducks, geese and ducks by 2 dogs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</guid>
      <description>2 dogs killed 150 chickens, ducks and geese. 2020-11-26 16:26 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
In rural areas
Many people like to have dogs.
Used as a &amp;ldquo;house keeper&amp;rdquo;
Dogs are more humane though.
But injuries do happen.
Dogs biting poultry is a common occurrence.
In the event of such an event
How should I be compensated?
Basic facts
In February 2020, Quanzhou County, a township in Quanzhou County, more than dog bites chicken and ducks, villagers will squat in the chicken farm, and then found the dog to bite the chicken, so the dog tracked to the Wen Mou home, after the villagers reported, the police processing, the organization of the two sides to negotiate unsuccessfully, then Wen Mou will sell the dog and does not admit that he is the dog, so the village Zhong Mou, He Mou and other 8 people will v.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who is responsible for the death of a cat after a bath at a pet store? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b91984ae2ec81af813454df026246931/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b91984ae2ec81af813454df026246931/</guid>
      <description>Newsletters In recent years, more and more people are taking their pets to pet stores for services such as grooming, bathing, and boarding. However, if a pet dies while receiving services at a pet store, how is liability determined and how is property damage defined? Recently, the People&amp;rsquo;s Court of Kunshan City, Jiangsu Province, heard such a case.
On the afternoon of March 11, Ms. Gao took her 2-year-old American short-haired cat to a pet store to take a bath, charging 120 yuan per session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who should get the pets in a divorce? The judge ruled this way for the emotional well-being of the dogs and cats! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d1ac4c72fa376c96f5564729d989657a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d1ac4c72fa376c96f5564729d989657a/</guid>
      <description>[
Online transmission of audiovisual programs license (0106168)
] [
京ICP备证040655号
] [京公网安备:110102003042-1] [
京ICP备05004340号-1
] Switchboard: 86-10-87826688
Copyright ©1999- 2020 chinanews.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why can&#39;t Border Collies be police dogs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/be58513f9b0539328fc25245e3e644dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/be58513f9b0539328fc25245e3e644dc/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-27 11:27:07 Source: Military Hunting Qi
Report
Good afternoon, shovelers!
Do you also worry about your fur baby getting older and having joint problems? Today&amp;rsquo;s recommendation is for bone and joint health screenings for dogs and cats, at a subsidized price of just $69, click below to purchase.
For more daily shovel family antics
Shovel Grower
This issue&amp;rsquo;s header image.
Special Note: The content above (including the pictures and videos if any) is uploaded and published by users of the media platform &amp;ldquo;NetEase&amp;rdquo;, which only provides information storage services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why do hyenas often overstep their bounds? What animal is it afraid to mess with? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fa6dc331189857a7b4dc446e0708b319/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fa6dc331189857a7b4dc446e0708b319/</guid>
      <description>Probably one of the most feared and apex predators in sub-Saharan Africa, hyenas possess great strength, jaws capable of crushing bones, a bite second only to saltwater crocodiles and great white sharks, and incredible stamina, intelligence, and absolute strength. In fact, packs of hyenas are so strong that they often challenge lions and leopards, sometimes driving them out of their territory.
Hyenas are mostly scavengers, opportunists, and parasitic predators, meaning they steal food from the prey of other predators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Why don&#39;t many people want to own a Garfield? The reason is too real, no money can really afford it! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/3edd5e20964eae089e7a71c0e214a71a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/3edd5e20964eae089e7a71c0e214a71a/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 17:00:48 Source: War Cheat Sheet
Report
I&amp;rsquo;m sure most people really like Garfield! Garfield not only looks cute, but also has a very cute personality. The Garfield I&amp;rsquo;ve seen is super clingy and never messes up, and when there&amp;rsquo;s nothing to do, he just lies quietly by the side and sleeps and stares, so he&amp;rsquo;s really a good pet. However, my friends who have had cats for many years have told me that many people are actually reluctant to raise Garfield, although they are indeed very pleasant to look at, but they can&amp;rsquo;t afford to do so because they are too realistic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> World of Warcraft 9.0 Faerie Night Covenant Skill Soul Transformation Form Source List! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c0285064b4d36f2b71fce7ffc15c84ec/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c0285064b4d36f2b71fce7ffc15c84ec/</guid>
      <description>1
Spirit of the Horned Horse
11 Prestige Rank unlocks the French Night Covenant Campaign: the Curse of the Moonlit Warlord, with quest completion rewards.
2
Spirit of the Incandescent Blue Moth
22 Prestige Rank unlocks the French Night Covenant Campaign: return to Druster, reward for completing the mission.
3
Spirit of the Wolf
The Court of the Enchanted Night&amp;rsquo;s Reputation is friendly and can be purchased at 59.6 in the Winter Woods Valley and 52.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Xi Mengyao and Lawrence Ho set up a stall to sell the first cup of milk tea after the first snow, the Tang Monk: the first dog food after the first snow has been eaten! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/0c0f5dcd24eda293efac92760acd583e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/0c0f5dcd24eda293efac92760acd583e/</guid>
      <description>Recently the Internet is very popular &amp;ldquo;autumn&amp;rsquo;s first cup of milk tea&amp;rdquo;, there is a saying: &amp;ldquo;It does not matter whether you drink the first cup of milk tea in autumn, but you must be deeply aware that if you do not work hard to make money, then you will be able to drink the first mouthful of northwest wind in winter!&amp;rdquo;. Then followed a lot of fads, like &amp;ldquo;autumn&amp;rsquo;s first bag&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;autumn&amp;rsquo;s first grapefruit&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;autumn&amp;rsquo;s first dog food&amp;rdquo; and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Xiao Zhan faces &#34;husky&#34;, Peter Pan&#39;s brain is too big! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b1eafc243300655c9c0e4e8b17ca4667/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b1eafc243300655c9c0e4e8b17ca4667/</guid>
      <description>I have to say that this face clash of wolves is really a fan&amp;rsquo;s brain, Xiao Zhan fans do not know that some time ago, Wang Hailin also took His Highness Hashchi a wave of Xiao Zhan connotation?
This kind of gives Xiao Zhan the feeling of taking a seat, but Xiao Zhan not only clashed with the husky, but also clashed with the gourd baby&amp;rsquo;s sleeping pose, so I have to say that Xiao Zhan is instantly very cute.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You know what? The &#34;clinginess&#34; of male and female cats is not the same! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/fc6588b59a52efe7dd81476f9db2a70f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/fc6588b59a52efe7dd81476f9db2a70f/</guid>
      <description>Why are other cats so clingy, but your cat is a bit cold and impersonal?
No matter how nice you are to your cat, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t seem to want to come near you.
In fact, the degree of a cat&amp;rsquo;s clinginess is related to many factors.
For example, the gender of the cat, the temperature of the weather, and whether the cat has needs.
-01
Male cats are more clingy than female cats.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> You will never know what a short leg means to a dog. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/e51d8af6629b2221ac8c0957e5bc0a59/</guid>
      <description>2019-02-22 17:07:32 Source: Searchwood
Report
As a short-legged dog, there are too many regrets and too many wishes that cannot be fulfilled in this life.
First of all, not being able to experience the sense of accomplishment that jumping brings to a dog!
When you&amp;rsquo;re camping with your buddies, running through the jungle, enjoying the summer breeze, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take long for you to discover a blow that&amp;rsquo;s too much for a dog to handle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Zoo feeds African wild dogs live sheep to keep them wild (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</guid>
      <description>Zoos feed African wild dogs to live sheep to keep them wild (Figure)
CCTV International www.cctv.com March 12, 2007, 10:50 Source.
New Business News
Zoo Feeds African Wild Dogs Live Sheep to Keep Them Wild
A frightened shivering sheep, a group of howling madly jumped on the African wild dogs &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; bloody, brutal, in the sheep tearing heart of the cry, it is the flesh of the wild dogs piece by piece to tear off, finally only left broken skeleton, and those who eat meat of the wild dogs, face covered with blood, the eyes of the fierce light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [90-second method] Feeding dog food? That&#39;s a legal liability, too. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</guid>
      <description>Stray dogs and cats can always be found in the streets, and most of them have experienced hardships and a rough fate. Fortunately, there are many kind-hearted people who will provide these homeless little ones with a full meal or even temporary shelter. **Wild shovelers, be aware that improper feeding can lead to legal risks! ***
Related Cases
On September 20, 2019, Zanzan, a man in his 60s in Zunyi, was knocked down by a dog on his way home and was diagnosed with multiple right-sided rib fractures, and was rated as having a Grade 10 disability after treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [UNK] Generation youth exclusive goodies! [UNK] Haskell x Coca-Cola Co-branded Ice Bar </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/6d6c1ae00c8d82d4dcf4ffac97838a2b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/6d6c1ae00c8d82d4dcf4ffac97838a2b/</guid>
      <description>Designed by POP Art&amp;rsquo;s representative designer, the Coke bottle cap is paired with Coca-Cola&amp;rsquo;s classic red, plus HCK Haskell&amp;rsquo;s classic square ice bar that has been selling well in Europe and America for decades. It is a blend of retro trends and new age technology, a classic and avant-garde lifestyle that belongs to the Z era.
HCK Haskell&amp;rsquo;s Ice Bar has a long history. As a classic product that has been selling well in Europe and America for decades, it has a good reputation and the quality is guaranteed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [UNK] Haskell x Coca-Cola Retro Refrigerator with a Postmodernist Feel </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/1ecf006a891fd92bda3da29650dcd936/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/1ecf006a891fd92bda3da29650dcd936/</guid>
      <description>HCK Haskell, in order to satisfy consumers&amp;rsquo; pursuit of post-modern life, launched the HCK Coke Girl Mini-Refrigerator in cooperation with Coca-Cola, a big IP company. The beauty of real life is displayed in retro form.
HCK Haskell Cola girl small refrigerator appearance go retro light extravagant wind, polished one-piece heavy body highlighting the geometric beauty of the body arc, especially the HCK Haskell classic curved door design, give people a warm and delicate high-grade texture, is the designer spent years of time carefully carved out the precious masterpiece.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>