<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stray Dogs on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/stray-dogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stray Dogs on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/stray-dogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> A monk saved more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats in 27 years: I was so busy that I didn&#39;t have time to pray. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/417f143fbeb16c9955fd1fb6630588d3/</guid>
      <description>Originally I am the extraordinary gentleman.
About 50 kilometers from downtown Shanghai, Fengxian hides an old and dilapidated temple called the Annunciation Temple.
Unlike temples in the downtown area, there is no golden-hued palace, no solemn monks in robes, and no chanting of Buddhist scriptures.
But there is a monk in a red auto mechanic&amp;rsquo;s uniform who has rescued more than 5,500 stray dogs and cats.
This man is the abbot of the hospital, Zhixiang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Canine infestation control becomes a new test of urban civilization </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/81cf390c65c3286e1d4c9bf9075d422a/</guid>
      <description>The number of stray dogs without an owner is soaring, and the dog problem is poking at the city management &amp;ldquo;pain points &amp;ldquo;.
Dog control becomes the new test of urban civilization.
The reason why stray dogs have gradually become a &amp;ldquo;problem&amp;rdquo; in many cities is that owners have abandoned their dogs, lost their pets, and the uncontrolled breeding of stray dogs.
● As the number of urban pet dogs increases, the social problems caused by dog ownership are becoming more and more serious, and many deep-seated problems have not been fully exposed, nor have they attracted the attention of the legislative, law enforcement and epidemic prevention departments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The number of unsolicited stray dogs in Wuxi has increased dramatically, and the dog infestation has hit the city management &#34;pain point&#34;. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1937986db14198cb032faf14bb79896/</guid>
      <description>Recently, a video of a stray dog being beaten with a stick in Wuxi, Jiangsu province has been circulating on the Internet, triggering some domestic pet protection organizations to voice their doubts, resulting in the formation of &amp;ldquo;support for cleaning up stray dogs&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;against the abuse of stray dogs&amp;rdquo;. &amp;ldquo;and other almost opposing viewpoints, in the online public opinion forum formed a heated debate between dog lovers and dog-averse netizens.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>