<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Animals on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/animals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Animals on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/animals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> 5-year-old girl&#39;s behavior on bus infuriates netizens, psychologists: bear child is the victim </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/c5fe0068e97d26302212b08ab0f7a397/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/c5fe0068e97d26302212b08ab0f7a397/</guid>
      <description>The term &amp;ldquo;bear cub&amp;rdquo; is no stranger to us, and every time a news report about a bear cub comes out, it refreshes our perceptions, and someone has even said, &amp;ldquo;There is no such thing as a bear, only more bears!
The 5-year-old girl&amp;rsquo;s behavior on the bus angered netizens, multiple heated discussion
Recently, a short video has been widely discussed on the Internet.
It happened on a bus, a 5-year-old girl with her mother on the bus, holding a furry little thing in her hand, and a closer look revealed that it was a small hamster.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A pack of wild dogs wanted to eat the crocodile meat and set a trap by pretending to drink the water, and the crocodile took the bait! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/13930e1dbe5ec6fa7a7c12526d0106b3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/13930e1dbe5ec6fa7a7c12526d0106b3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of wild dogs wanted to eat the crocodile&amp;rsquo;s meat and set a trap by drinking the water, and the crocodile took the bait!
Animals living in the wild have to worry about food almost every day, and under such cruel conditions, they have also mastered some tricks, this day a group of wild dogs wanted to eat crocodile meat, and set a trap by drinking water, and the crocodile successfully took the bait!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to get a cat or a doggy animal? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/93c6466c4c2fd40b65209ea679dc431b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/93c6466c4c2fd40b65209ea679dc431b/</guid>
      <description>Inarihime Tenho no Saki game pets is every little friend will want to get, play the game little friend should know Kai maru this character, he really likes to go out and doubt to make friends, get all kinds of small animals, including cats and ducks as well as puppies and so on, so how do you get these small animals? Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at it below!
Inarihime Tenho no Saki game pets is every little friend will want to get, play the game little friend should know Kai maru this character, he really likes to go out and doubt to make friends, get all kinds of small animals, including cats and ducks as well as puppies and so on, so how do you get these small animals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/496bc073d44f2a8b1d3d22e29cfda77e/</guid>
      <description>Hyenas and African wild dogs are similar in size, but why do they say that the wild dog must win in a race between the two?
Nature can be very cruel, and one must always be on the lookout for animals that might sneak up on you, as this competition is the difference between life and death. In the African grasslands, there are two types of animals, hyenas and wild African dogs, which are about the same size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Man scalded pregnant mother cat with boiling water in the street: Animal cruelty is a disease, we have to use the rule of law! </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/a1a61f4c95d709f08171a04061751c3e/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/a1a61f4c95d709f08171a04061751c3e/</guid>
      <description>On October 19, a video of a man scalding a cat with boiling water in Taiyuan, Shanxi province, sparked outrage!
In the video, the man locked a white cat in a cage, with just boiled water and poured the cat, was found by the loving people passing by, immediately stopped and the police, the man was taken away by the police, the cat was sent to the veterinary hospital for treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who is responsible for the death of 150 chickens, ducks, geese and ducks by 2 dogs? </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/d9acc3609458ada70a0dc457e3bc952b/</guid>
      <description>2 dogs killed 150 chickens, ducks and geese. 2020-11-26 16:26 Source: Breaking News - Breaking News - Politics
In rural areas
Many people like to have dogs.
Used as a &amp;ldquo;house keeper&amp;rdquo;
Dogs are more humane though.
But injuries do happen.
Dogs biting poultry is a common occurrence.
In the event of such an event
How should I be compensated?
Basic facts
In February 2020, Quanzhou County, a township in Quanzhou County, more than dog bites chicken and ducks, villagers will squat in the chicken farm, and then found the dog to bite the chicken, so the dog tracked to the Wen Mou home, after the villagers reported, the police processing, the organization of the two sides to negotiate unsuccessfully, then Wen Mou will sell the dog and does not admit that he is the dog, so the village Zhong Mou, He Mou and other 8 people will v.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Zoo feeds African wild dogs live sheep to keep them wild (Figure) </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/78871803c3c08b3c29acedb2c6fc4898/</guid>
      <description>Zoos feed African wild dogs to live sheep to keep them wild (Figure)
CCTV International www.cctv.com March 12, 2007, 10:50 Source.
New Business News
Zoo Feeds African Wild Dogs Live Sheep to Keep Them Wild
A frightened shivering sheep, a group of howling madly jumped on the African wild dogs &amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; bloody, brutal, in the sheep tearing heart of the cry, it is the flesh of the wild dogs piece by piece to tear off, finally only left broken skeleton, and those who eat meat of the wild dogs, face covered with blood, the eyes of the fierce light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [90-second method] Feeding dog food? That&#39;s a legal liability, too. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9404eef1086cad5bcfaa1c8b1702fab3/</guid>
      <description>Stray dogs and cats can always be found in the streets, and most of them have experienced hardships and a rough fate. Fortunately, there are many kind-hearted people who will provide these homeless little ones with a full meal or even temporary shelter. **Wild shovelers, be aware that improper feeding can lead to legal risks! ***
Related Cases
On September 20, 2019, Zanzan, a man in his 60s in Zunyi, was knocked down by a dog on his way home and was diagnosed with multiple right-sided rib fractures, and was rated as having a Grade 10 disability after treatment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>