<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newest Member on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/newest-member/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newest Member on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/newest-member/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> The newest member of the family, Mr. Chen Guanxi, has a family photo by the beach and Qin Shupei is wearing a couple of shoes. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9d116b446e15db1b0cd5e8bd909d0a07/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9d116b446e15db1b0cd5e8bd909d0a07/</guid>
      <description>On November 24, Chen Guanxi showed a family photo of the three of them sitting on a reef in his personal social media platform. In the photo, Chen Guanxi and Qin Shubei are wearing couple&amp;rsquo;s shoes together and secretly spreading dog food.
In the photo shared by Chen Guanxi, the three of them gestured the same gesture, and the couple also wore couple shoes in a low-key manner, showing a secret show of love.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The newest member of the family, Zega: Tang YiXin attended the event and wore a mint green cake dress with a sweet effect. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/48424d6189c4713cf864466e0b6c0dc1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/48424d6189c4713cf864466e0b6c0dc1/</guid>
      <description>On Nov. 25, Tang YiXin wore a mint green cake dress to the opening ceremony of the Golden Rooster Awards, bringing a touch of mint green in the winter, as if dancing lightly, revealing a superior shoulder and neck line.
It&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to show off the beauty of your body, and it&amp;rsquo;s also a great way to show off the beauty of your body,&amp;rdquo; she said.
It&amp;rsquo;s not just a matter of time and space, it&amp;rsquo;s a matter of time and space, and it&amp;rsquo;s also a matter of time and space.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>