<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Killed on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/killed/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Killed on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/killed/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> Poor Baboon Attacked by African Wild Dogs and Instantly Torn Apart in Cruelty </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/aceca2827e19c14ef660a3ee4d2cdd28/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/aceca2827e19c14ef660a3ee4d2cdd28/</guid>
      <description>The African wild dog is the most efficient predator in Africa, yet these animals changed their feeding habits and started hunting primates like never before, the Daily Mail reported Nov. 28.
According to the report, 55-year-old wildlife photographer Nicholas Dale, who was born in the United States, was the first African wild dog to be killed. (Dyer) is the photographer of these images. Born and raised in Kenya, he has spent the last six years on foot in remote Manatan, Zimbabwe, stalking and photographing these animals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Snowstorm Hits British Safari Park, African Wild Dogs Run Away, Killing 16 Animals </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/b7e2fa21c5282644ac0d99616a9339c3/</guid>
      <description>A pack of African wild dogs escaped from their yard and killed 16 animals in the Worcestershire Wildlife Park in England due to damage caused by Storm Siara, Sky News reported on February 14.
A park spokeswoman said that in the early morning hours of Feb. 9, 12 wild dogs entered a compound near the park, killing six Persian fallow deer and 10 Barbary sheep.
The park spokeswoman had previously said, &amp;ldquo;At no time was there a risk to public safety or any danger of animals escaping the park fence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>