<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Long on Docs</title>
    <link>./tags/long/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Long on Docs</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <managingEditor>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="./tags/long/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title> The Little Sisters of the Heroes of the Grasslands, a children&#39;s ballet that reaffirms collectivism from a new perspective </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/395abf1bcca6f757b72294c88a56dfbe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/395abf1bcca6f757b72294c88a56dfbe/</guid>
      <description>The heroic deeds of the Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes have influenced generations, are the pride of Baotou, and are our role models. We need to dig deep into the spirit of the &amp;ldquo;Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes&amp;rdquo; spirit of the times, the &amp;ldquo;Little Sisters of the Grassland Heroes&amp;rdquo; story told from generation to generation, education and guidance of today&amp;rsquo;s youth as a good inheritor of the red gene, practitioner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The first time I&#39;ve been in a relationship with a woman, I&#39;ve been in one. </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/8ebef841d334ab92eeade9ec0039d23f/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/8ebef841d334ab92eeade9ec0039d23f/</guid>
      <description>2020-11-26 23:14:01 Source: Culture Traveler says
Report
On November 26th, actress Yueh-Hsi Gai updated a status on top of her social media platform, and the video shows Yuehsi Gai in home clothes, with the words &amp;ldquo;I am also a person who has dog food to sprinkle. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty sweet.
On November 25, a suspected love affair between Yueh-Hsien Gai and Lin update has caught everyone&amp;rsquo;s attention. The reason for the incident is because someone filmed Lin and Yue Hsi in a private party, and there is a close relationship between them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> What are the fastest animals in the world? Top 10 Fastest Animals, See Who&#39;s Faster </title>
      <link>./post/2020-12-01/9b513b861282a70bfeff8714dd2a066c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>youremail@domain.com (Some Person)</author>
      <guid>./post/2020-12-01/9b513b861282a70bfeff8714dd2a066c/</guid>
      <description>There are many animals in the world that run. The lion, for example, is the most dominant animal of the African savannah and is known as the &amp;ldquo;King of the Beasts&amp;rdquo;. But what most people don&amp;rsquo;t know is that lions are also very fast. Most of the time, fast running animals will dare to hunt prey that runs at the same or even much faster than them. Do you know what the fastest animals are?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>